Previously on Gilmore Girls.
- Oh, my God, I'm going to Chilton?
- You did it, babe. You got in.
- I told Mom you're changing schools.
- Is she thrilled?
The party's on Friday.
Are you moving?
No, just my books are.
- Ready?
- Yes.
Headmaster Charleston will see you.
You may have been the smartest
at Stars Hollow, but it's different here.
You'll never catch up,
and you'll never beat me.
There's a good chance you will fail.
- Who's that?
- New girl.
Stay out of my way.
I will make this school a living hell for you.
See you tomorrow, Mary.
- They kept calling me Mary.
- Mary, like Virgin Mary.
What if I had looked like a slut?
They might have added
a "Magdalene" to it.
- Shopping for school supplies. Party.
- Nobody demanded that you come.
Are you kidding?
How often do you do things like this?
While we're going crazy,
we should get toilet paper and a plunger.
I'll do this later.
- No, I'm teasing. Get that list of yours.
- Okay.
- I need legal pads...
- Got it.
...tons of pens, some number 2 pencils,
three highlighters, an eraser...
a staple remover, and a folder.
- You need three highlighters?
- Yes.
- That's a very random number.
- It is not random.
How did you get to the number three?
One dries up, one gets lost, I have one left.
- You've really thought this out.
- Yes.
What came first, the chicken or the egg?
- Can we get back to the list?
- All right. Hey, legal pads.
- No. Those are purple.
- Yes. Purple is festive.
- I can't have purple.
- You can. They're on sale.
I'm going to a serious school.
I need serious paper.
- Paper is paper.
- Not at Chilton.
- All right, fine. Here's your serious paper.
- Thank you.
And here are your somber highlighters,
your maudlin pencils...
- your manic-depressive pens.
- Mom.
These erasers are on lithium.
So they seem cheerful...
but we caught them trying to
shove themselves in the pencil sharpener.
- I'm going home.
- No, wait.
We're gonna stage an intervention
with the neon Post-its...
and make them give up
their wacky, crazy ways.
You're never
coming shopping with me again.
Here's a card tray. Everything is gonna...
Decent effort by most.
Good effort by some.
Exceptional effort by two.
Ms. Geller. Ms. Grant.
Mr. Graham. Ms. Gilmore.
Take these home.
Learn from your mistakes.
Look at the large red circles
around various parts of your papers...
as friendly reminders that to err is human.
And that here at Chilton, we try to
beat that humanity right out of you.
Okay, next up, the test.
The dreaded test. Shakespeare!
The man we've been droning on about
for the last three weeks...
finally comes back to haunt us on Friday.
This is a big one, my friends.
Multiple-choice, with an essay section...
that will count for 20% of your grade
this semester.
Don't be fooled by my kind face
and charming personality.
This test will be hard,
and there will be no make-ups.
Refer to the study materials
I gave you at the beginning of the month...
and those extensive notes
I know you've been taking.
- Hard paper.
- Killer.
- How did you do?
- "A."
Me, too!
- Small world.
- Isn't it?
- Madeline, what did you get?
- You know I got a "B."
- A "B's" not bad. It's respectable even.
- Not at all.
I'd be proud.
A "D," however,
that would be cause for concern.
A cry for help.
A job application at McDonald's.
"Would you like fries with that?"
Hey, you know,
not everybody can be smart.
As my mother always says,
"Somebody has to answer the phones."
I have no idea
what you two are talking about.
No, but Rory does.
Hey, Mary!
And it just keeps getting better.
- You look sad.
- I'm fine.
- Bad grade?
- I have to go.
Mary, I just can't figure out
why we're not friends.
I think it's because I make you nervous.
I think it's because
you can't learn my name.
- Do you have a boyfriend?
- None of your business.
- Is that a no?
- Is there no one else you can bother?
I think you like me.
You just don't know how to say it.
- So what are you doing Friday night?
- I'm busy.
What, you gotta be back
at the convent by 5:00?
Please leave me alone.
All right. Since you said "please."
Later, Mary.
- You imbecile!
- Back off, chevalier.
- You're stupid, blind, and clumsy.
- At least I'm not French.
- What's going on?
- She ran over my shoe.
- He got in the way.
- You aimed for me.
- Hold on.
- She scratched my shoes.
- What a baby.
- These are $300 Italian loafers.
I wonder if Versace makes a pacifier.
- You're fired.
- You can't fire me.
- Then I dock your pay. Can I kill her?
- Not before high tea.
Fine. Then I will curse you constantly
and in several languages.
- I'm going for the other foot.
- Don't! Drella, to your corner now.
I win.
Michel, you're a grown man.
Now go to your desk and act like one.
Oh, my God.
- Okay, just a minute.
- I've got it.
The review?
- It's here.
- Where is it?
- I'm looking.
- Hurry.
Behold, in theaters now,
The Thing That Reads A Lot.
- Chocolate?
- Glass measuring cup.
- Lorelai, look.
- I'm sorry.
- Jeez, who's naked?
- Lucien Mills, food critic.
Yeah? How's his butt?
He was supposed to review the restaurant.
Here it is.
Is it good? Is he mean? Should I cry?
Here we go.
"The words "divine,"
"delectable," and "delirious"..."
"don't begin to describe
the delicious experience..."
"of dining at the Independence Inn."
I'm smelling rave.
Really?
"Only Chef Sookie St. James
could make a simple salad..."
"of hothouse tomatoes and assorted fresh
herbs seem like a religious experience."
"Her lobster bisque is worth
every sinful, cream-filled, rich sip."
See, I don't use that much cream. I just
use a very concentrated lobster stock.
- And it really makes it...
- He's not here.
Okay, go on.
"The entrees are
as heavenly as the starters."
"Though the much-lauded risotto
was perfectly fine..."
"it was the handkerchief pasta
with brown sage in a butter sauce..."
"that sent me through the roof."
This is unbelievable! I'm gonna
have this framed for the dining room!
Yeah, that'd be swell.
Can I see that again?
So we should celebrate tonight, huh?
Girls on the town?
I can't. I have to study.
I should really get started
on this shopping list.
What is going on here?
We are young and fiery women.
Studying? Shopping lists?
Where's "To hell with it all"?
Where's "Throwing caution to the wind"?
Where... Shoot, the linen delivery.
You go, girl.
...and the Person of the Week segment.
- News is on!
- One sec.
For our top story tonight, a grisly,
horrible thing happened in a small town...
where no grisly, horrible things
ever happen. Everyone's shocked!
House slides down hill.
Liposuction kills. Stay fat.
Hey, let's get ice cream. I'm bored.
Hello?
Mom, I'm studying.
But I'm talking ice cream.
Can't you take a break?
- I can't take a break right now.
- Okay. When?
- Are you four?
- No, I'm hungry.
- Have some more pizza.
- It's cold.
- Heat it up.
- It's not the same.
Lorelai, go to your room!
Wow, smart girls are mean.
If you let me study now,
I'll play with you this weekend.
- Promise?
- Yes. We can do anything you want.
- Will you go to the shoe sale with me?
- Yes.
- Will you let me try on anything I want?
Will you help push people away
if they go for my size?
I'll even run interference for you.
- All right, you've got a deal.
- Good.
So, I'm sorry. Where did we land
on the whole ice cream issue?
What?
- Right or left?
- Left.
I thought you said left.
- Sorry. My left, your right.
- Okay.
Marco.
Polo.
Hey, Marco.
Hey, Polo.
- You're late.
- Sorry.
What is that?
12 calories.
- Here.
- Oh, my God. Bless you.
- Man, what's that?
- My notes.
Really?
I don't think Shakespeare
knew himself this well.
I like. How much?
- $500.
- Is that the best you can do?
- $450.
- I'm not so sure.
$375 and you take it right now.
- Sold.
- We appreciate your business.
Move.
I really miss Stars Hollow High.
- You're kidding, right?
- No. Chilton's just...
I don't know, hard.
What do you care? You were always
Miss Everything's-So-Easy-At-School.
This should be a snap for you.
Nope. This is sold. Move.
- What's that?
- That's mine.
That is chocolate-covered death.
With a creamy caramel surprise.
- So, this guy asked about you today.
- What guy?
The new kid. Tall, perfect.
- What did he want to know?
- Where you were.
What did you say?
I told him you were too smart for us
and you had to go to the genius school.
He really liked that.
I guess he's into brainy chicks.
I'll keep my eyes open for one for him.
- No. Sold. Move.
- Mom.
- Where do you want us to go?
- Library.
I hate sales.
No Black Sabbath.
No one's listening.
No Black Sabbath, no Steely Dan,
no Boston, and no Queen.
What happened to make you so cold?
- You like that Mozart.
- I am the Artie Shaw of harpists.
- Sookie, I need coffee to go.
- There's fresh over there.
Good.
Fresh in my first lifetime as Joan of Arc.
Sorry. I thought I made fresh. Here.
Bless you. I'm so exhausted,
and I have to drive to Hartford tonight...
- to go to a parent-teacher meeting.
- Sounds great.
This school is so different
from Stars Hollow.
They send home a thousand pages
of updates every week.
It's a very intense place.
Last week, there was this huge debate...
over whether plaid scrunchies
were acceptable headwear.
People took sides. Things got ugly.
The scrunchy motion finally passed...
- and I like to think I was the tiebreaker.
- That's nice.
Hey, what's the matter, sweetie?
- He said it was fine.
- Who said it was fine?
- Lucien Mills.
- The restaurant critic?
- He said my risotto was fine.
- Isn't it?
No, it's not fine.
Fine is a word you use
when someone stops you on the street...
that you know,
but you don't want to talk to.
They ask you how you are,
and you say "Fine."
That's enough so they don't have to keep
talking to you, "cause they don't want to.
Then they can feel good because
they've been considerate enough to ask...
and if, God forbid,
something actually is wrong...
they'll sit down, take time and listen,
even if they don't want to.
I don't think he meant fine
as a slam or as a monologue.
He couldn't have meant it any other way.
I hate to see you get so upset
over one little review.
This is pride, Lorelai.
I mean, you know about this risotto.
- On my mother's deathbed...
- You made the risotto...
- and she lived three more years.
- She was supposed to be dead.
The doctor said
she wouldn't live through the night.
And she lived because of the risotto,
the magic risotto.
And this guy had the nerve to say
it was fine.
I don't think he knew the story.
Okay. Before you get all goofy on me,
I don't have your porcinis.
I forgot them.
I don't have any other excuse,
other than plain, old, stupid human error.
I have the morels, which I know you
don't want, so come on, let me have it.
Morels are fine.
Did anyone else feel the shift
in the space-time continuum?
- A reviewer didn't like the risotto.
- The magic risotto? You're kidding.
I gotta go.
So try and cheer her up, would you?
Sure.
Sweetie, please don't worry about it.
Everyone knows you're the best.
So...
I hear the huckleberry crop"s
gonna totally suck this year.
We are gonna be focusing
on Elizabethan literature.
Shakespeare, Marlowe, Bacon,
Ben Jonson, John Webster.
Is Marlowe really that significant?
We want to give
as complete an overview as possible.
Yes, but will he be included
on the advanced placement test?
We can't know exactly
what will be on the AP test...
but it will be important
when your kids hit their universities.
But to get there
they need to pass the AP test.
Right, it's all important.
It could all be on the test.
How do we find out?
You could bribe somebody
on the AP Committee.
I was kidding. I'm just kidding.
I'm so sorry.
I had a terrible pothole incident.
You don't care. So please, go on.
What in the world?
You okay?
- I'll just sit now.
- I don't think we've met.
I'm Lorelai Gilmore. Rory's mom.
Glad you could join us.
Rory's one of our new students.
How nice. Now, the AP test.
Right. Well, we are preparing them
as best we can.
I've hired a tutor for Bethany.
Always a valid option.
Jesus, Mary, Joseph, and the camel!
This is really bad coffee.
So, this AP test,
what are we gonna do about it?
The next test is scheduled for next month.
The 25th, Saturday, at 7:00 a.m.
- Ms. Gilmore?
- Where is the test?
- It will be given here.
- Here?
- Right.
- Great.
- Any other questions?
- Yeah.
Can parents come?
What?
Yeah, it's a big, exciting test.
So I just thought...
- I'm sorry. Is that stupid?
- No, it's not stupid.
I just thought
I'd like to see the excitement.
- It's a test.
- Yeah, I know.
What's exciting about a test?
- Do you play golf?
- Yes, I do.
- You explain yours, I'll explain mine.
- Why not get back to the meeting?
That's the one who voted
for the scrunchies.
Must be a scholarship student.
Excuse me.
You know what? I think this would be
a good time for a break.
There's coffee in the back.
What were you gonna do? Hit her?
No. I had some
good verbal comebacks ready.
- It just keeps getting worse.
- Not drinking it is always an option.
Not in my world.
- I'm Max Medina.
- Nice to meet you.
I apologize for the behavior
of some of our guests tonight.
It's a tense time for some people.
- The SAT season?
- The waking hours.
- Are you this nice to my kid?
- It's easy.
- Rory's a sweet girl.
- Yeah, she is.
How is she liking Chilton?
- She loves it.
- Really?
Yeah. It's an adjustment, of course.
But she's always wanted to go to Harvard.
- This is how she'll get there.
- Harvard?
Ever since she could crawl,
I've really wanted her to go there.
It's a great school.
I bought her a Harvard sweatshirt
when she was four.
Of course, it was way too big for her.
So she used it as a blanket for a while,
and then as a diaper on this shopping trip.
And now I've told you a story
that would so mortify her...
she'll kill me
when she finds out you know.
- Don't tell her then. It'll be our secret.
- I appreciate that.
So, are you a B-52's girl?
What?
No, I'm a klutz girl who should not drive
with coffee in her hand.
I had this in the car.
I hope Rory adjusts to this place.
We need her here.
Thank you. That's so nice.
I hope she's not too disappointed
about her paper.
It's very hard to catch up
on all that reading material.
- I know a "D" seems pretty dismal...
- Rory got a "D"?
- Yeah, but...
- She's never gotten a "D."
It's the first paper she's turning in.
She's bound to falter a little.
This totally explains
the no ice-cream thing.
- God, I'm such an idiot.
- The ice-cream thing?
Look, I've gotta go.
I'm sorry if I said something to offend you.
No. If Rory got a "D,"
she's not feeling too good right now.
- And I'd really like to be there.
- I understand.
So, it was nice meeting you.
You, too.
- Keep up the good work.
- I will.
- Don't ever make coffee ever again.
- I won"t, I promise.
Thanks.
- Bye.
- Here.
- What's that?
- You look like you need pie.
- I do?
Violent pencil-tossing
usually signals a need for pie.
What if I'd thrown a pen?
- I would've brought you a trout.
- What?
I don't make the rules,
I just carry them out.
Hey, backwards baseball hat.
New look for you.
She's eating pie?
Did she even have dinner?
You raised her. I just serve.
- Hello, bookworm.
- Finally.
- Where were you?
- Well, actually, I was in Hartford.
Why?
I was there for the...
Parent-teacher meeting.
Oh, my God, I forgot.
It went very well.
I was extremely charming.
I won the whole crowd over.
They made me queen.
So, I guess you talked to Mr. Medina.
Why did you let me whine
about ice cream and shoe sales...
when you had something major going on?
I know.
I hate when I'm an idiot and don't know it.
I like to be aware of my idiocy.
To revel in it, take pictures. We've missed
a prime Christmas-card opportunity.
I'm sorry.
You should have told me.
I couldn"t.
You couldn't tell me?
You tell me everything.
It was too humiliating.
Honey, you once told me that you loved
Saved By the Bell.
What could be more humiliating than that?
I couldn't form the words.
I couldn't even say it.
I couldn't even comprehend it.
It was a "D." I got a "D."
- I've never gotten a "D." Ever.
- I know.
Even when I broke my arm
and couldn't write for a month...
I got an "A" minus.
- That was a different school.
- I know. It was Stars Hollow High.
A "D" at Stars Hollow
is like an "F" at Chilton.
It's worse. It's like a "G" or a "W."
So I'm guessing
the spelling test didn't go well either?
A "D."
I suck.
You don't suck.
- I can't do this.
- Listen, a "D" is bad, okay?
But this talk about "I suck,"
"I can't do this," and self-pity...
that's worse. That's not you.
You didn't feel sorry for yourself...
when it took you three months
to learn how to ride a bike.
Four months.
It took me four months
to learn how to ride a bike.
Really? Four months?
Yeah. You wanna
belabor the conversation?
Forget about the bike.
Listen, a "D" is one grade.
It's not the end of the world.
You'll catch up, you'll do better.
You are of hardy, stubborn stock.
If there's one thing I gave you,
it's stubbornness.
- I'm not stubborn.
- You are.
- I'm not.
- Fine. You're not.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You can do this, and I'll help you.
I'll get you through this.
Now put the "D" behind you.
- What's next?
- I have a test on Friday.
- A test. Great!
- On Shakespeare.
The bard with a beard. Love it.
- It's 20% of my grade.
- Just makes life interesting.
Now what do we have to do
to get you an "A" on that test?
Do you really think I can do this?
I bet you $1.
That's it? That's all my future's worth, $1?
Well, you did get a "D."
"Let me not to the marriage of true minds
Admit impediments
"Love is not love
Which alters when it alteration finds
"Or bends with the remover to remove
"O, no! It is an ever-fixed mark
"That looks on tempests
and is never shaken
"It is the star to every wandering bark
"Whose worth's unknown
although his height be taken"
You're going down.
Sookie, do you know
what the menu's gonna be...
- Good?
- Hot.
Wait. I got another one.
- Better?
- Hotter.
Wait. I got one more.
What's with all the risotto?
Have we gone theme now?
Is it gonna be like the Scotch tape store?
Look, I've made 40 recipes, okay? 40.
And every single time,
I come back to the same conclusion.
That yours is better.
- Yes.
- It is.
- You were looking for me?
- Yes!
Three weeks ago,
a guy comes in here, Lucien Mills...
orders the risotto, doesn't like it.
- The magic risotto? You're kidding.
- Not helping.
He's a restaurant critic.
He ordered lots of things,
probably didn't finish them.
In his review,
he said his waiter had a goatee.
You've got a goatee,
so you waited on him, and I need info.
- What did he look like?
- Like he was unhappy with the risotto!
Maybe he had an annoying companion...
that wouldn't let him
concentrate on his eating.
- I serve a lot of people.
- He had a beard, false teeth, or a wig...
or the glasses with the big nose.
- May I be fired now?
- Absolutely.
What about a guy with
an annoying companion and a fake wig...
sitting underneath
an air-conditioning vent...
next to a woman
with too much perfume on?
- The Comedy of Errors: Written?
- 1590.
- Published?
- 1698.
- 1623. Close.
- How is 1623 close?
- You got the 16 part right.
- I was off by 75 years.
Anything under 100 is close.
- What kind of a rule is that?
- I'm running the study session here.
- Okay. Richard III.
- 1591.
"93?"96?
Okay, that's getting really annoying now.
Go on. I'm listening.
The sonnets are 154 poems of 14 lines.
- Except?
- Except for 126, which is 12 lines.
Good.
They're written in iambic pentameter.
- Except?
- Except for 145, which is in tetrameter.
- Rock on, sister.
- Really?
- Not one mistake. How do you feel?
- Nauseous.
I don't think the fries
and the horseradish sauce...
was the best idea we ever had.
It was satisfying in the moment, though.
You're gonna
blow that class away tomorrow.
- You think?
- I think.
What do you say we call it a night
and get some beauty sleep?
You go. I wanna review my notes
one more time.
- That's okay. I'll stay up.
- Mom, go to sleep.
No. I'm not even tired.
I was just thinking of you.
No!
Oh, jeez.
This was such a bad sleeping idea.
- I'm late!
- What?
- I'm late! I woke up late!
- Rory, calm down.
I can't calm down!
I missed my bus! Get up!
Mommy can't get up right now.
Mommy's been sleeping
at a right angle all night.
- I'm gonna miss the test!
- No, you're not.
I'll get the keys.
We'll go right now. Let's go!
- I can't take you.
- You have to!
- I have a meeting at the Inn at 8:00!
- Mom!
Okay, wait. Think. Listen. Here. You drive.
- What?
- You drive. I'll get a ride from Sookie.
Take the phone. Take the keys. Go!
- Are you sure?
- Go!
- I'm gone!
- Good luck!
Hello?
Did I leave a set of notes at your house?
- Where are you?
- I'm driving to school.
I need to check something
and I can't find some of my notes.
Okay, hold on. Let me check.
- I don't see anything.
- What did I do with them?
- Maybe it's downstairs in the store?
- Maybe. I just...
- Oh, my God!
- Are you all right?
- I just got hit by a deer!
- You hit a deer?
- No! I got hit by a deer.
- How do you get hit by a deer?
I was at a stop sign, and he hit me!
Oh, my God!
Was it a four-way stop?
- What does that matter?
- I don't know.
I don't know what to ask
after you've been hit by a deer.
- I don't see him.
- Put salt down. Deer love salt.
- Where am I gonna get salt?
- Do you have a lunch?
- Lane!
- Sorry.
I don't see him anywhere.
What if he's hurt?
Rory, your test.
- What time is it?
- It's 7:40.
No!
I'm sorry.
Everyone back to your tests.
- You've to wait in the library.
- What about the test?
- You've missed the test.
- No.
We start class promptly at 8:05.
That's when I need people in their seats.
- Please.
- I'm sorry. It's the rules.
But you don't understand.
I was up all night studying...
and then I missed my bus.
So I had to drive.
- Let's discuss this outside.
- So, I'm driving, and I get hit by a deer.
- You hit a deer?
- No, I got hit by a deer.
You don't believe me?
I've got antler prints on the car.
Come on.
No! You have to let me take this test!
I'm ready for it.
- I know everything about Shakespeare.
- You've to calm down now.
- I know his birthday, his mother's name...
- Loser.
And just what is wrong with you?
You already have everything.
You have the grades and the status.
What's wrong with you...
that you have this need
to be the biggest jerk in the world?
Let's go.
What's up, quippy? Why so silent?
Outside, now.
And, for the last time, the name is Rory!
Make sure that carpet is replaced perfectly
before they go.
- Okay.
- Perfectly, nailed down and everything.
You mean that "perfectly."
I thought you meant the other "perfectly."
The one that could be misinterpreted
by the other Michel...
the one who couldn't understand
what you meant by "perfectly."
- What do you think about Pat Benatar?
- Great idea. Can she play the harp?
I knew it! I found it!
- You found what?
- I found his bill!
What are you talking about?
It wasn't the risotto, it was the wine.
He ordered the wrong wine!
Great.
In the review,
he mentioned a summer tomato salad...
which I only made once
in the last three weeks...
because Jackson decides to
get in a fistfight with his tomato grower...
- Okay, that's a different story.
- Yes. Save it for Christmastime.
Brian, the goateed waiter,
only worked one shift last week...
because his girlfriend kicked him out.
- Celia kicked him out?
- He didn't want kids.
- But she knew that.
- Women think they can change men.
Yeah.
So, I checked the dates,
and narrowed the day down...
and found a party that had ordered
practically everything including...
- The magic risotto.
- Yes, the risotto and a Riesling. A Riesling!
Why not drink battery acid?
Exactly. Changes the entire flavor
of the dish.
The fact that Brian served it...
makes me think
Celia is better off without him.
I'm so glad, hon.
Okay. Here are the zucchini.
Too small. Take them away.
- It's good to have her back, huh?
- Yeah.
You're still gonna have to pay
for the zucchini.
There's a man with a funny accent
on the phone, asking for you.
Really? Did you guys exchange
the secret handshake?
Lorelai here.
Rory, what happened?
- I got hit by a deer.
- You got what?
Then I was late,
and they wouldn't let me take the test.
- What?
- They wouldn't let me take the test...
- No, you're kidding me.
- Mom...
No, it's okay. Just sit right here.
I'll handle this.
Excuse me. Hello.
- Ms. Gilmore. Please come in.
- Thank you.
Have a seat.
I think there's been a terrible mistake.
Rory told me that
she wasn't allowed to take her test.
- She was late.
- Right, well...
see, there were circumstances
beyond her control.
Rory is never late.
She's almost annoyingly on time.
If you checked your records...
Past performance has nothing to do
with today's situation.
Okay. But see,
she was up all night studying.
I was there. She has a witness.
- She's not on trial here.
- Well, Your Honor...
Just a little trial humor.
That won't happen again.
She got up late.
She broke her neck to get here.
We don't live locally as you...
- "The dog ate my homework."
- Excuse me?
"My computer crashed,
and I lost my midterm."
I wasn't making excuses.
"My grandmother and first cousin died."
"My sister took my report to school
instead of hers."
"My religion prohibits studying
after sundown."
"I went blind last night, but I'm fine now."
That's not Rory.
Rules are rules.
When you're late,
you forfeit the right to take the test.
Where are you going? Where is he going?
Please, believe me,
if I could do anything, I would.
- You could let her take the test.
- I can"t.
That's not fair.
We're not here to be fair.
We're here to educate.
Yes, and I'm asking you
to please educate my kid.
We will when she's on time.
Have a nice day.
Are you holding that door open
for a reason?
- Our meeting is over.
- Like hell it is.
Do you have any idea
what we have gone through this week?
We have been up all night every night,
studying. We haven't slept.
We haven't talked about anything else...
except this school and this test
for seven days.
We have stretched ourselves
as thin as humanly possible...
without going completely postal.
My God! We're just one person!
Why don't we narrow
our field of conversation down to Rory?
Okay. Why don't we?
You sit here in your snotty little school...
in desperate need
of some extra heating vents...
and you nurture horrible kids
who treat each other like mortal enemies.
You set impossible standards...
that make normal people
feel less than everybody else.
You take a great kid like Rory
and tear her apart!
I don't think that's completely fair.
You say she's smart and she'll do fine.
And this rotting, stodgy rathole
could use somebody like her.
Then you completely shut her out of a test
that she's crammed for...
that she completely deserves to take!
- I didn't call this place a rathole.
- That's true. I added that.
Wouldn't want you to get
in trouble with II Duce here.
I thought this place
was gonna be so great.
And now, I guess this goes on
the "Boy, was I wrong" list...
right above gauchos
but just below the Flashdance phase.
My goodness,
you do like to throw fits in your family.
What are you talking about?
Your daughter threw a similar, if not
as manic, fit of her own this morning.
Please. Rory doesn't throw fits.
She's the most even-tempered person
I know.
Well, she did a lovely impression of you.
Everything you said in your rant
was absolutely true...
without the colorful embellishments
of course.
We do set impossible standards...
and such standards do foster
highly competitive children.
However, that is life, and that is Chilton.
Rules can change. You can change them.
I told your daughter when she came here,
this place was not for everyone...
and might not be for her.
I will now tell you the same thing.
She doesn't have to be here.
She doesn't have to go to Harvard.
Maybe she shouldn"t.
If she can't handle the pressure,
she should leave.
You need to take your daughter home now
and decide what it is you intend to do.
However, another outburst like this
from either of you...
will not be on the options list.
Thank you for coming in.
That will be all.
You got hit by a deer?
You did. You got hit by a deer.
It just came out of nowhere.
You couldn't just run into a wall
like other kids?
- Can we just go home, please?
- Yeah, sure. Jump in.
- May I help you?
- Yes.
Hello. My name is Sookie St. James.
I'm the chef at the Independence Inn.
- I know who you are.
- You do?
Well, I'm flattered.
You write about a lot of chefs...
- What are you doing here?
- Right.
I know that this
is a terrible intrusion, but...
- Are you cooking?
- I'm making chicken.
- You used too much salt.
- I did not.
It smells salty.
- I'm closing the door now.
- No, wait.
I found your address
from my network of culinary friends...
This is really inappropriate.
I gave you a good review.
I suggest you go home.
I don't care about the review. I just...
I want you to try this dish...
with this wine.
I'll wait.
- Quite a day, huh?
- I don't want to talk. Please.
Okay.
I just think we should talk about it.
- Stop the car.
- What?
Here. Stop here.
You're just feeling like
an impromptu nature walk?
I wanna see if it's all right.
- Lf what's all right?
- The deer.
- You're never gonna find the deer!
- I'm gonna try.
- I'm in heels.
- Stay in the car.
It's dangerous in the car
with the kamikaze deer running around.
I have to find it.
All right. Wait up!
So what does the deer look like?
Does he have any distinguishing marks...
besides the word "jeep"
imprinted on his forehead?
He's just a deer.
So I had a nice chat
with Headmaster Charleston today.
He said you went ballistic in class.
I was just tired.
You wouldn't have been tired
had you not been killing yourself all week.
I was studying. I didn't have a choice.
Maybe you shouldn't be studying
that hard.
- What are you talking about?
- You're 16.
You should get some sleep
and eat a real meal...
and come up for air once in a while.
They kicked me out.
No. Of course not.
They love you. This is coming from me.
Are you saying I should quit?
I'm saying, if you wanted to go back
to your other school with Lane...
that would be fine with me.
- You don't think I can do it.
- You know that's not true.
I think you can do anything.
But you don't lose it in class.
That's not part of
the Rory personality description.
If you're losing it in class...
because you're tired, stressed out,
or working too hard...
I'm worried about that. I have to be.
- I lost it once.
- Okay. Fine.
It's just I can't remember a time...
when we weren't talking about
you going to Harvard.
It was just a given.
That was what we were working for.
- Everything went in that direction.
- I know.
And I'm forgetting where that all started.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about...
did it start with me
or did it start with you?
Was it my dream
that you went to Harvard?
Mom.
Because I never got to do
the big, fancy college thing.
Maybe all this time I'm thinking
it's all for Rory...
when really it wasn"t.
- I'm not doing this because of you.
- Lf you are, you don't have to.
- I know that.
- I'll still love you...
even if you can't support me
in my old age...
in the fabulous manner
to which I plan on growing accustomed.
I'll remember that selfless gesture.
Thank you.
- I just want you to be happy.
- I am.
No, I want you to be...
dancing-through-the-woods-crazy happy.
If Harvard and Chilton
is not gonna do that for you...
then forget about them.
I was just behind.
I never caught up on all the reading.
That's why I got a "D."
I can catch up. I will catch up.
And when I do, everything will be fine.
No. Harvard is my dream.
- I want it more than anything. I swear.
- Yeah, but...
I appreciate all that you're saying. I do.
But I'm not ready to
give up on Chilton yet.
Fair enough.
I do, however,
reserve the right to change my mind.
That's your prerogative,
as long as you remain a woman.
- Thanks, though.
- For what?
For yelling at the headmaster
the way you did.
I didn't yell at him.
You called him II Duce.
Which means "kind sir" in Cantonese.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
How much longer are we gonna
look for this crazy deer?
Just a little further.
- I just hope he didn't hurt himself.
- I just hope he has insurance.
Go get that plaid skirt off
and grab your books.
We're going to Luke"s.
- Don't you have to get back to work?
- They can last a little longer without me.
Plus Michel gets so cute
when he feels he's overworked.
His ears puff out, his nostrils flare.
It's big fun.
- Go.
- I'm gone.
It's us. We're not here.
We have a life. Get over it.
Hi. This is a message for Rory.
It's Max Medina calling.
I just wanted to say
I talked to Headmaster Charleston...
or II Duce, as he's more affectionately
known in the Gilmore household...
and he's agreed to let you do
some extra credit work...
to help make up for the missed test today.
Now, I'm not sure
what the extra credit work is yet...
but it probably will be time-consuming
and extremely painful.
It will, however, get you back up to
where I think you rightly belong, Rory.
Don't lose heart. Make this work.
And if your mother's listening...
Lorelai, it was a pleasure
encountering you.
I hope it happens again.
Anyway, see you in class. Bye.