Previously on Gilmore Girls.
- My God, I'm going to Chilton?
- You did it, babe. You got in.
This guy asked about you today.
- I'm Dean.
- Hi.
- What did he want to know?
- Where you were.
- What did you say?
- You had to go to the genius school.
I've been watching you.
When?
Every day.
- I'm Max Medina.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm gonna miss the test!
- Go!
- I'm gone!
- What about the test?
- You've missed the test.
I'm ready for it.
I know everything about Shakespeare.
I think there's been a terrible mistake.
Rory told me that
she wasn't allowed to take her test.
She was late.
You say she's smart and she'll do fine.
And this rotting, stodgy rathole
could use somebody like her.
Then you shut her out of a test
that she's crammed for...
that she completely deserves to take!
No. Harvard is my dream.
I want it more than anything. I swear.
I'm not ready to give up on Chilton yet.
It's Max Medina calling.
Lorelai, it was a pleasure
encountering you.
I hope it happens again.
Bye.
Where did you say Dad was?
- Away on business.
- Location's top-secret?
Germany.
- Is Dad's firm insuring Nazis?
- Your father doesn't know any Nazis.
- I know, Mom. I was just...
- What?
Joking. She was joking.
- Hard to tell.
- Yeah.
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
Claudia died.
- Who?
- Claudia, your cousin.
I'm hearing the name, Mom.
I have no idea who that is.
Claudia's your cousin,
for all intents and purposes.
Now we're getting to it.
She was your father's grandmother's
sister's girl.
- So, to you, that would make her...
- Nothing?
Regardless. Funeral's on Thursday.
I thought we'd all go together.
Two problems: One, impossible
to get away from the Inn on Thursday.
Two, I've never met this woman.
- You certainly have.
- When?
- Several times.
- I'll take one.
We went to her house in Groton
to see the first moon landing.
She'd just gotten a new Philco.
I have no memory of this whatsoever.
Rory, correct me if I'm wrong,
but men have walked on the moon...
regardless of whether
your mother remembers.
That's the rumor.
I know men have walked on the moon.
I just don't know Claudia.
- So you're not going?
- Not this time.
I don't think Claudia's planning to die
a second time.
- Mom, I couldn't go if I wanted to.
- Fine.
Wait, Rudolph Gottfried.
Another cousin?
No, a Nazi that we knew. I'd forgotten.
We stayed with him once in Munich.
Nice old man. Interesting stories.
Mom, you socialized with a known Nazi?
That's despicable. That's heinous.
No, dear, that was a joke.
I have an idea for a new reality show.
How about everyone just looks out
their kitchen window for a change?
She's cranky this morning.
Let's just say the world's
got a formidable opponent.
- Wait. Shouldn't you be baking?
- I don't know. Shouldn't you be knitting?
- Mom, the Chilton bake sale is today.
- I know. I got it covered.
- They expect things to be homemade...
- I know.
...by someone other than Dolly Madison.
I said I have it covered.
All of the parents pitch in, so this
is really important. You know that, right?
I didn't know that.
In that case, I don't have it covered.
I have it covered.
- Get your stuff, hit the stereo. We're late.
- That's not me.
Where does your mom think you are?
On a park bench, contemplating
the reunification of the two Koreas.
Not here, skanking to Rancid?
- Wouldn't be included.
- School.
Bye.
Wow, Cinnamon, riding in style.
Yeah, Morey made it.
Cinnamon's not walking good these days,
but she still likes her passeggiatas.
- That's Italian for "a nice walk."
- Passeggiata.
- Oh, God, he makes it sound so sexy.
- Come on.
What's that?
That's Cinnamon's private area.
Sometimes she likes to be alone.
She's just like Morey in that sense.
Say "passeggiata" again.
I can't do it on command, Babs.
He's blushing.
God, I love a man that blushes.
- Okay, our town is just weird.
- Thank God.
Bye.
- I'll see you later at school.
- For what?
Mom, the bake sale.
- I got the vein in the forehead.
- Sadist.
- Morning.
- Good book?
I don't know yet.
I saw you standing in line,
so I thought I'd say hello.
- Hello?
- Hello.
Thanks for helping me
get the job at the store.
It's not a career or anything,
but it's got me solvent.
- Solvent is good.
- Yeah.
- Are you always this serious?
- No.
So, how long does it take you
to get to school?
Forty minutes if the bus driver's focused...
but longer if he's trying to win something
on the radio.
- This bus is going to Hartford.
- Yeah, I know.
But you go to school here.
You have to get off the bus.
- He has to get off the bus.
- Wait.
You're forgetting something.
Buses make stops.
Goodbye, Lorelai Gilmore.
Independence Inn, Michel speaking.
Yes, you are confirmed.
Goodbye.
No, sorry.
Sir, I'm a simple country boy from Texas.
I do not understand this Francais business
you're babbling about.
Pardon.
- He knows you are not from Texas.
- Smile when you say that.
Michel, I told you there would
be a French group here for some days...
and it's your job to keep them happy.
I don't know how many French people
you've met over the years...
- but most of them are insufferable.
- Really?
That is why I left France.
I thought it had something to do
with the torches and the villagers.
- Michel, talk to them.
- Never.
You are giving me that look, aren't you?
Your patented "do it or something
unspeakable shall befall you" look.
Fine. I shall be French,
but I shall not be happy.
Then you will be yourself. Good choice.
Kill me now.
Okay, we've got our French fantasies...
American treats,
and our Italian taste sensations.
- What do you think?
- Amazing.
Incredible.
It is good, isn't it? Well, final touch.
Can I do that?
Honey, this is a more delicate procedure
than you might think.
- Okay.
- It takes an expert hand.
Hi.
What is that, $1? Let me just give you...
Let me find you $1.
You know what? I'll take two.
I'll drink one.
Tasty and flame-retardant.
- Very Henry Vlll.
- We're not into subtle.
- Good to see you, Lorelai.
- Good to see you, Mr. Medina.
- Max.
- Mr. Medina.
Mr. Medina, meet Sookie,
the chef at the Inn.
- Sookie, Mr. Medina.
- What's the name again?
- Mr. Medina.
- I know, you've said it a zillion times.
Hello.
Lorelai, can I borrow you for a second?
Yeah, sure.
I'll be right back.
Trust me.
So?
You know, Lorelai,
I would love for the ice to thaw.
- There's no ice.
- You repeated my full name four times.
- That's ice.
- That's not ice. It's wintry.
I was doing my job
when I didn't let Rory take that test.
- I didn't like it, but I had to do it.
- I know.
- And I'd do it again.
- Okay.
I really do think Rory's a great kid...
and I'll do my damnedest to make sure
she gets through Chilton in one piece.
I appreciate that.
- And I'd like us to be friends.
- We are. Me, too.
- Yeah?
- Really, truly, I swear. There's no more ice.
We're walking in a pool of tepid water.
Good.
I'm going to propose something here.
I'm not sure how you're gonna take it.
Wow, intrigue.
I'd like to see you sometime.
Away from the ivy,
away from the gargoyles, away from here.
- Are you asking me out on a date?
- Yes.
Well, I don't want to
go out on a limb here...
but if the headmaster won't let
a kid be 30 seconds late for a test...
he'd probably frown on
a teacher dating a mom.
I do my job well,
I'm dedicated to my students...
and there's nothing in
the Chilton Book of Ethics that prohibits it.
But I'm guessing
it's sort of an unwritten rule.
- Do you want to go?
- Rory would probably freak at the thought.
Other parents would have a field day
with this thing.
- Do you want to go?
- Yes.
- Good.
- Wait.
- What?
- No.
- Why?
- I can't.
- It's wrong. It's weird.
- I'll pay.
- You're on.
- Really?
I'm kidding. I don't know.
You're Rory's teacher.
I know.
Could you quit?
Right, that's crazy. I'm sorry.
Okay.
How about coffee? You like coffee?
Only with my oxygen.
Can we drink some together?
A sort of pre-date.
Very casual, no strings, no obligations.
We'll see if it's worth going down the road
of including food in the deal.
Just coffee.
Decaf?
There's nothing safer than decaf.
I'm gonna be in town tomorrow
because I take a class at Hartford State...
and there's a coffee shop
across the street...
that I sometimes, almost all the time,
go to around 4:00...
and usually exactly 4:12.
I could not stop a person from entering
said establishment around that time...
nor would I avoid them...
if I knew them, if they did.
You know, the wordsmith thing,
that's something we have in common.
So, see you around, Max.
Indeed. You will.
Philadelphia.
Philadelphia? If you could live
in any city in the world...
you'd pick Philadelphia?
- M. Night Shyamalan lives there.
- Who?
The guy who directed The Sixth Sense.
But what would you do there?
Hang out with M. Night Shyamalan.
Okay, cross "Guidance Counselor"
off your list of potential career choices.
Lie still, baby doll. We're almost home.
- Hey, Babbette.
- Hey, kids.
Wow, that sounds bad.
Cinnamon's dyspeptic. So is Morey.
- Too many clams.
- Bad clams.
This doesn't reflect well
on Al's establishment.
- You had clams at Al's?
- Al's Pancake World?
Yeah, we had a coupon.
Wow, the store.
- Listen, I have to pick up some stuff, so...
- What do you have to pick up?
Just some stuff.
So, I'll talk to you later tonight.
- I'll go in with you.
- Why?
Because, otherwise, I'd have to go home.
- Home is good.
- My home?
Actually, I don't have to go in.
Okay, then I guess I will go home.
Great. Go. Bye.
Bye. Freak.
Rory! Hello.
- Try a plum. They're better than sex.
- No, thanks.
Fresh fruit always has
such a sensuality about it.
- Are you too young for this?
- Definitely.
- What are you here for, honey?
- Well, I just...
I see what you're here for.
That wouldn't fit in a basket. No.
Patty, it's not like that. He's just a person.
- A person?
- A boy-type person.
- My favorite kind.
- I really don't even know him.
- Right. You don't know him?
- I don't.
- You said.
- Please don't say anything.
I promise I won't tell a soul
that you don't know that young man.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Ma'am, what are you doing?
Please, honey, don't call me ma'am.
It makes me feel older than 25.
Here, have a pea pod.
I'm assuming you'll pay for the food
that you've consumed on the premises.
So brusque.
- And you are?
- I'm the new assistant manager here.
Listen here, my fine friend,
who, if he had a better hairstyle...
I might consider dating.
I do this all the time.
Not from now on. I'm sorry.
Wait a minute. I've been sampling food
at this establishment for years.
If you put something in that mouth
that doesn't belong there...
I'll remove it and then call the police.
Is this all you want?
A head of lettuce and a mousetrap?
- That should do it.
- That's a couple of must-need items there.
- $2.27.
- I only have $1.
- I can loan you the rest.
- No, I'll just take the lettuce.
Perfect. You could use half of it
for a salad...
then use the other half
to clobber the mouse with.
- Paper or plastic?
- I'm fine.
- Lorelai?
- Max. Hi.
- Small world?
- Absolutely.
- What are you drinking?
- Coffee.
Plain coffee?
I wanted some cream, but that prompted
a very elaborate foam conversation.
The disapproval I got when I said
I didn't want foam, just cream...
rivaled the one from my dad
when I told him I wanted to teach.
Wow, so it's been a tough outing for you.
It's getting better.
- What can I get you?
- Coffee, please.
So, here we are.
- Here we most certainly are.
- Running into each other.
- Away from school.
- And its unique strictures.
- These things do happen.
- Fate can be funny.
Should we cut the cute and just get to it?
- I think we should date.
- Why?
- Because I think we both want to.
- I want to be in The Bangles.
It doesn't mean I quit my job
and get a guitar and ruin my life...
to be a Bangle. Does it?
- The Bangles broke up.
- That's not the point.
It's got to be part of it,
if there's no band anymore.
I repeat my question.
Why should we date?
Because we're clearly attracted
to each other.
I'm attracted to pie.
It doesn't mean I feel the need to date pie.
Okay, then,
because we are... of similar heights.
Wow. Round 1 and already tapped.
Look, I know that you are concerned
about the appearance of us dating.
Yes, I am.
I can tell you I'm the soul of discretion...
when it comes to delicate relationships.
Dated a lot of Chilton moms?
No, I meant any relationship, work, family.
So you have things to hide
in all aspects of your life. Very interesting.
Do you have any hemlock back there?
Arsenic, something quick.
- Do you like rap music?
- Yeah.
Me, too.
- Italian food?
- Yeah.
Me, too.
- You telling me what I want to hear?
- Yeah.
I knew it.
Doesn't mean it doesn't coincide
with how I feel.
If you're telling what I wanna hear
then I'm not getting to know you.
If I know what you want to hear,
it shows my understanding of you...
far exceeds your understanding of me.
Who's the one lagging?
Wow. Round 1 and already tapped.
Rory is my life. She's my pal.
My everything.
And I would never ever do anything
that would hurt her.
- But Rory is not a baby anymore.
- Don't say that.
She's eight, and her favorite hobby
is making necklaces out of gum wrappers.
You could try stunting her growth,
keeping her in a box...
blowing cigarette smoke on her.
You are so taking this out of context.
When my uncle was a young man...
there was this girl who lived
across the street from him...
and he was completely in love with her.
But he never talked to her.
He knew in his gut that this was the girl
he wanted to spend his life with.
This is gonna be sad, isn't it?
- Let me finish.
- It's gonna be sad.
So, anyhow, my uncle watches this girl...
waiting for the right moment
to approach her.
- Next thing he knows, he gets drafted.
- I'm going for the Kleenex.
Now, he thinks,
"This is perfect. I'll come back..."
"I'll have a career, I'll have served
my country. I'll be worthy of her love."
When he gets back, she's gone.
Moved away. No one knew where.
And he never saw that girl again.
Now, my uncle, he didn't say much to me.
But the one thing that he did say...
was that if there's something in your gut...
that you know you feel is right...
you got to go after it, no matter what.
What do you say?
Maybe dinner...
wouldn't be such a bad idea.
Dinner? You mean we could sit together,
even drive together?
- Just take the card.
- I might frame the card.
- Just use the card.
- I definitely will.
What?
That story about your uncle, is that true?
Goodbye, Lorelai Gilmore.
Thank you.
Life is a funny thing, huh?
Yeah, I love that Jim Carrey.
- What?
- Jim Carrey.
- He's just funny.
- He is funny.
But then I don't mean funny-funny.
I'm being philosophical.
Very serious face. Jean Paul Sartre.
I can't talk to you with that face.
How do you guys get any work done?
So why is life such a funny thing?
- I met this amazing guy.
- Goody!
There's goody stuff about it,
but there's baddy stuff, too.
He teaches at Chilton. Max.
You met him at the bake sale.
- He looked good.
- Yeah. Right.
He's so sexy, smart, and funny,
and he likes coffee.
God, he sounds perfect for you.
- Did you get onions?
- No.
Luke, you forgot the onions.
I'm just so mixed up.
This is a real crossroads situation.
It's like: To perm or not to perm.
I'm really confused.
For heaven's sake!
Go ahead. I'm still listening.
You were about to perm your hair.
I just want to do the right thing.
- I don't see what the problem is.
- There are many problems.
First: I do not like to involve Rory
in my personal life.
I don't want her to deal with that.
I bring some guy home,
and he might not be the guy...
but then she gets all attached to him,
and then all of a sudden I decide...
that I don't like the way he eats,
or he hums incessantly...
Or the way he smacks his lips,
or how his hair isn't his own.
Then I break up with him,
and Rory is the one who gets hurt.
- I totally understand.
- This guy is her teacher.
I can't keep him out of her life.
She sees him every day.
- Are you the open-faced turkey?
- Yep.
I added a little fresh lemon
and a little cayenne pepper.
You're gonna plotz!
You do know
that Rory's not a baby anymore?
That's what he said.
Maybe I'm being too serious, right?
Maybe I should loosen the rules a bit.
- Plus, it would be great to get, you know.
- What?
- You know.
- No, I don't.
You know.
He knows.
- You know?
- Yeah, I know.
- Sookie!
- I was looking for your paprika.
- What have I said about the counter?
- I know.
How the counter is a sacred space,
my sacred space.
You don't do yoga
on the Dalai Lama's mat.
And you don't come
behind my counter. Period!
I was trying to help!
You bring her again,
I want her on a leash! I mean it.
He does make a damn fine burger though.
He does at that.
All right. I'm just gonna keep it simple.
I'll tell Rory.
If there's even an ounce of weirdness
about it, I'll cancel.
- You haven't told Rory yet?
- No.
- Oops.
- No, not oops.
The timing hasn't been right.
This is a very delicate, fragile situation.
It's like your souffles.
If you don't do it right, it's a disaster.
And you have to order it 45 minutes
in advance.
- My souffle.
- Right.
But I wasn't speaking directly
about your souffle.
I was speaking metaphorically.
- So you don't like my souffles?
- How do we work together?
Mom, you better come.
- Honey, what's wrong?
- It's Cinnamon.
- Babbette? Honey?
- Lorelai, come in.
She's gone.
- Cinnamon's gone.
- I'm so sorry.
Is there anything I can do for you, Morey?
This is life, Rory. It breaks your heart.
She looked like she was sleeping.
I thought she was asleep,
so I nudged her and she didn't wake.
I gave her a push
and she rolled off the couch...
and since I'd just waxed the floor,
she went shooting across the room.
And then she knocked over the lamp
and she still didn't move.
I knew it was over. Oh, God, my baby.
Tell me it wasn't the...
Morey, don't do this to yourself.
He thinks it was the clams.
She saw me eating them, and she gave me
that, "Hey, man, what's up?" look...
It wasn't the clams.
Morey, in human years,
this cat was 260 years old.
That's a good long life.
Listen, why don't you let me take her out
to the van?
- And then I'll get out of your way.
- No, stay.
All of you, please stay.
Cinnamon would want you here.
We'll stay as long as you want.
- I'll never eat clams again.
- Me either.
They said that they rolled her body
into a lamp?
Did you laugh?
Did you want to?
- But it's sad.
- Yeah, it's sad.
Hello?
Hello, where is Lorelai?
I'm dropping something off.
Yoo-hoo, heehaw man,
where's Lorelai Gilmore?
Thank you. I could not get back to the Inn.
What? You are having a party,
and I was not invited?
Sweetie, it's not a party. It's a wake.
- Really? Who died?
- Their cat.
- You are mourning a cat?
- Yes.
They lick their privates, these cats.
Not the comforting chit-chat
we're looking for.
Goodbye. I'll talk to you later. Thank you.
Babbette, Morey,
I came as soon as I heard.
- Darling, what do you need?
- A little air, honey.
- What you got in the bag?
- Bricks.
- Yeah, good one.
- Bless you both!
Everyone's starved. Come in.
Okay, how should we do this?
We'll create a flow through the room
to avoid bottlenecks.
People coming in the front door
will want a beverage.
Put them on the first table,
then the hors d'oeuvres next to that...
leaving one hand free to greet the people.
Then, back there,
set up plates and cutlery.
First the salads, then the meat,
then the desserts on the bench.
- How's that sound?
- Dig in!
- I wasn't expecting you.
- Or me you. I mean, you me.
I mean, come on in, you.
- Do you know him?
- No.
No?
He goes to my old school,
so I see him there sometimes...
- but I go to Chilton now.
- Thanks for the update.
You're welcome.
- Do you have a second?
- No, I have gum.
- No, thanks. Look...
- I have to get back.
Okay, sure.
I'll see you later.
Mom?
- Isn't that...
- No!
- That's Mr. Medina.
- Tonight's Thursday.
Am I in trouble?
- Did the school call or something?
- No, you're great.
Let me just come back in just one second.
- Wait, what's going on?
- I'll tell you in a minute.
- Tell me now.
- Max is here.
- Max?
- Max is here to pick me up.
Pick you up for...
I'm gonna talk to him real quick,
and I'm gonna be right back.
I was knocking, but no one answered.
I know. I was at the neighbors' house.
Max, I should have called you sooner, but...
- You're canceling.
- I know it's totally last-minute.
- I'm heartbroken.
- I completely forgot about our date.
- And forgettable.
- No, you're memorable.
I've been memorabling you all week.
It's just, we had a little emergency.
- Rory? Is Rory okay?
- Rory's fine. It's the neighbors' cat.
- The neighbors'...
- Cat, she died.
- She died.
- This was a very fat, very beloved cat.
I see.
I like you.
And I don't want to force
something on you that you don't want.
No. Wait.
Max, you're not forcing anything on me.
I am telling the truth about the cat.
Max, please don't read that much
into this.
Call me, and we'll reschedule.
I promise that's what I want.
Are you sure?
Cross my heart and hope that no other
neighborhood pets die on that day.
Okay, I'll call.
Good.
- I'm sorry about...
- Cinnamon.
Stupid cat!
Couldn't have held on one more day?
- Is that meatloaf?
- Yeah.
You use ketchup?
- You gonna make fun of my mother, too?
- Sorry.
My Roquefort puffs
would complement that dish quite well.
- It's fine on its own. Thank you.
- Right.
Okay, toss some on the plate.
Can I make a pretty design?
Maybe make some layers?
Right. Tossing them on. Got it.
Have you guys seen Rory anywhere?
- Yeah, I think she headed that way.
- Okay, thanks.
Excuse me, ma'am?
Well, if it isn't Kirk the Jerk.
I want to apologize for what happened
at the store yesterday.
I'm listening.
I wasn't aware you were the Miss Patty.
The owner tells me
you're one of our best customers...
and that you can put anything
in that mouth that you want.
Those were his words.
I could have paraphrased.
Stop sweating and close your pores, Kirky.
I always forgive.
- Thank you.
- Once.
- Babbette.
- Hello, sugar.
- Can I get you something?
- No, I'm fine. I'm looking for Rory.
- I think she might be in the bathroom.
- Thanks.
- Can I help you with something?
- No.
I thought I'd just get
some of this stuff packed away.
It's like a scene from the kitty version
of Valley of the Dolls.
Yeah, you never realize
how old they actually are...
till you look in the medicine cabinet.
These were for her heartworms.
For her thyroid, her kidneys...
for the rash she got from taking these...
and these were for the tics she developed
from taking the stuff for the rash.
And these are... These are mine.
Damn. I'm gonna miss that old broad.
I know.
You know, I don't know
what I'm gonna do with myself now.
You live to take care of your kids.
I know, sweetie,
but you gave her everything you had.
She was so tiny when I got her,
she could sleep in my shoe.
The other day,
I came across a hat that I made for Rory.
- It was like a doll hat.
- They grow up so fast.
And then they take your clothes.
I guess, eventually, you have to move on.
Figure out what your life is gonna be...
when you're not busy
taking care of somebody else.
Jeez, look at this place.
Not a clean glass in sight.
Let me help you with that.
Here, sugar, use this.
Morey sits on it when he helps me.
- How does Morey get around in here?
- Just fine.
He had a couple of concussions
his first year here.
But he never complains.
He's just the best thing.
Don't know what I'd do without him.
What do you mean without him?
I saw on Oprah a few weeks ago...
she had on couples who lost a child.
Most of the marriages went belly up
for the pain of it all.
Even though they loved each other.
Babbette, that is not gonna happen to you.
I never thought
a man would ever even want me.
I know the feeling.
Please, with that ass? Give me a break.
I mean, want me for more than my ass.
For me. The whole package.
- Annoying neuroses and all.
- You'll find him.
It might even be that stud
that drove out of here in that Mustang.
- Did you see him?
- Yes.
- What a jaw.
- Right. He's got a great jaw.
- How is he in the sack?
- I haven't gone out with him yet.
Will you tell me how he is when you do?
I'll call you during the cigarette.
That's Cinnamon's song.
- I can't find Rory anywhere.
- I'm sure she's around.
Max showed up for the date
I forgot about, and she saw him.
- You haven't told her.
- No.
- Oops.
- Stop with the oops.
Okay, calm down.
It's not that big of a deal.
Her teacher showed up on her porch
to take out her mother.
She'll understand.
You're crazy. She knows that.
- Enough of the comforting, Sookie.
- Sorry.
Jeez, you scared me.
Yeah, look,
I just wanted to say that I'm sorry.
- For what?
- I've been kind of bugging you lately.
I thought you maybe liked me,
but it's obvious that you're not interested.
So I just wanted to say that I get it.
And I'm not gonna bother you anymore.
Wait!
I am interested.
- You are?
- Yes.
I got to go.
Finally. I've been looking
everywhere for you.
- You found me.
- I have some explaining to do.
So sit down in that tiny chair.
I'm gonna do it right now.
That man on the porch was your teacher.
Mom, I'm a little behind in school...
but not so behind that I don't know
who the teacher is. So?
He and I were going to
sort of hang out together.
- On a date.
- No.
On something that could appear
like a date to the untrained eye.
- And to your daughter's eye?
- It was a date.
- How long have you been dating him?
- This was gonna be the first time.
When were you planning to tell me?
On your wedding?
No, by the rehearsal dinner at least.
- He's my teacher.
- I know.
He teaches me things every day...
in a small classroom
with a lot of other kids...
who won't be high-fiving me
when they find this out.
I know. I told him this was
one of the things I was concerned about.
- And?
- And he thought we could be discreet.
- Unbelievable!
- Are you mad?
- Yes.
- Right.
- Because I'm dating him?
- Because you lied to me.
- I kept information from you.
- Information that I should have had.
It would've come out eventually
like the Iran-Contra Scandal.
- So you're Oliver North.
- No, I'm Fawn Hall.
- Mom.
- She was much prettier.
I can't believe that you didn't tell me
about this. Why wouldn't you tell me?
'Cause I thought you were going to
take it bad. Thank God I was wrong.
Okay. Listen, I'm sorry.
I won't date him. I promise.
I'm not saying that you can't date him.
It's just... This is weird.
I mean, there are a million guys
in this world...
and you end up with Mr. Medina.
You think I don't get the weirdness factor?
Believe me, the last thing I intended to do
was date your teacher.
- I believe you.
- I really like him, Rory. I can't help it.
It's been a long time
since I've felt like this.
You can't always control
who you're attracted to.
The Angelina Jolie-Billy Bob Thornton
thing really proves that.
I know you don't understand this now,
but you will someday.
You'll meet some great guy,
and he'll make your head all foggy...
and you won't know
what to do with yourself.
Sweetie, I won't keep anything
from you again. Okay? I promise.
From now on, every aspect of my life
is an open book to you.
- It's okay.
- Really.
I'm not even gonna get dressed until
I tell you what I'm thinking of wearing.
- Fair enough.
- Okay.
Tomorrow, I'm thinking...
the purple tiger top, the black leather
skirt, the panda-bear underwear?
Good.
But of course
I'm totally open to suggestions.
Here's one: Get some help.
- Let us know if we can do anything.
- You've done too much already.
- Good night, Babbette.
- Good night, sugar.
- Good night, Morey.
- Stay cool, Rory.
It's getting late.
Let's stay outside awhile, baby.
- Look for the Big Dipper.
- Okay, I'd like that.
- Hello.
- I've been trying to get you all afternoon.
- Mom?
- Yes.
- You already said that.
- But someone hasn't.
Hello.
- There we go.
- You are impossible to reach.
There's no messages on the machine.
I don't leave messages.
If I wanted to talk to a machine,
I'd talk to my VCR. Where were you?
- At a wake.
- A what?
A wake. A funeral.
- A funeral? Whose?
- It was for the neighbors'...
cat.
Hold on. I'm looking up "aneurysm" in our
medical dictionary to see if I just had one.
I just wanted to be honest with you, Mom.
Silly me.
- A cat?
- Yeah, it was a cat's funeral.
You skipped your own cousin's funeral
for a cat funeral?
Not my cousin. My father's grandmother's
sister's girl who I never...
You said you can't be away from the Inn.
- I couldn't at the time, but I worked it out.
- For a cat.
It's late. I have a big day tomorrow, Mom.
What? You're going to
a raccoon's wedding?
- Good night, Mother.
- Good night.
She's working
for a sedative manufacturer.
Keeping that demand sky-high.
You shouldn't have told her.
I don't know what to tell and what to hide.
So, we never did quite settle
the whole dating-your-teacher issue.
I won't go out with him
if you don't want me to.
You can go out with whoever you want.
It's whoever we want.
I'm certainly not gonna go out with him
'cause that'd be really weird.
But I mean it.
I won't see him if you don't want me to.
If there's anything that makes you
feel uncomfortable, big or small...
- then he's out of there.
- Good to know.
Because, you know,
it's not like I'm desperate.
I mean, there are plenty
of other guys out there.
Sure are.
And it's not like
I have to ask your permission.
- I mean, this is a courtesy.
- Okay.
I'm gonna be up for a while
if you want to get back to me on this.
I know where you are.
Think you could keep him out late
on Thursday night?
I have this oral exam on Friday
that I'd really love him to sleep through.
I'll do my best.