Tomorrow our lawyer, Joseph Stanford,
is coming by.
- Crazy Sissy's dad.
- That's terrible. You were good friends.
She spoke to her stuffed animals,
and they answered.
- Let's start a new topic.
- You're impossible.
She said a new topic.
Everything's a joke.
Everyone's a punch line.
Okay, I'm sorry.
My daughter, Henny Youngman.
Sorry for that.
A little trouble in our China office.
Well, what did I miss?
I was being impossible.
Then I turned into a Jewish comedian.
- Continue.
- Thank you. Where was I?
Joseph Stanford is coming tomorrow.
Yes. So, Rory, your grandfather and I
thought it might be nice after dinner...
to go around the house and pick out
what you'd like us to leave you in our will.
Take a look at that desk in my office.
It's a really fine Georgian piece.
Why don't I ever bring a tape recorder
to these dinners?
Anything you want to leave me is fine.
Nonsense. You should have what you like.
Just look around.
When you see something you like,
stick a Post-it on it.
Okay, you two have officially hit
a new level of weird that even I marvel at.
- You can pick out things, too.
- Now it's way less creepy.
Did you hear that, Richard?
Apparently we're creepy.
Yes, well, you live and learn.
- Oh, cool.
- What's that?
- It's dessert.
- It's pudding.
If you knew what it was, why did you ask?
- You don't like pudding.
- Yes, but you like pudding.
I love pudding. I worship it.
I have a bowl up on the mantel...
with the Virgin Mary, a glass of wine,
and $1 next to it.
I've never had pudding
from a crystal bowl before.
You like the bowl?
Put a Post-it on it when you're done.
So, what do we think of this?
- Where would we put it?
- I don't know.
The Emily and Richard Gilmore
Psycho Museum?
This is the strangest evening
I've ever spent here.
So, how are we doing?
Great. Just getting ready for the big day.
- Very nice.
- It's getting late, Mom.
Unless you've got some funeral plots
for us to decorate, we should be going.
Any special requests
for dinner next week?
Mom, I want to talk to you for a minute.
And, Rory, why don't you
go say goodbye to Grandpa?
Very smooth.
Shall I sit down?
Yeah, but not there, okay?
We got a Post-it on that.
We'd like to keep it nice.
It must be very exhausting to be you.
- Mom, Rory's birthday is next Friday.
- I know that.
So, we were thinking maybe we could
push our dinner next week to Saturday.
- What're you going to do on Friday?
- I don't know...
Come here, and we'll have a little party.
- Can we do it another night?
- Why another night when her birthday is...
on the exact night that you come here.
- Saturday's a good night.
- Not as good as Friday.
- Pretty close.
- Not from where I'm standing.
Move then.
I'm sorry. Friday nights are my nights.
That's what we agreed on
when you borrowed money for her school.
I didn't intend for this loan to become
a constant source of blackmail, okay?
This is my kid's birthday,
and she will have her party...
at home on Friday, and that's it.
End of story.
So, how would you like two parties
this year?
- You couldn't get her to cave.
- No.
But she did agree to make
the string quartet learn Like a Virgin.
Well, you tried.
Sweetie, I promise, Saturday night
we'll do it up right at home.
A Stars Hollow extravaganza.
So, is this party Grandma's having
going to be a big deal?
Not really.
The government will close that day.
Flags will fly at half-mast.
Barbra Streisand
will give her final concert again.
The Pope has previous plans,
but he's trying to get out of them.
However, Elvis and Jim Morrison
are coming...
- and they're bringing chips.
- You ask a simple question...
Mini orange biscuits with
honey-mustard ham and cheddar cheese.
- Angel wings with dipping sauce.
- Good.
- Did you bring me the picture?
- Yes.
Too bad you couldn't get your mom
to relinquish Friday.
- She has her Vulcan death grip on that.
- Not that surprising though.
Emily Gilmore.
You could set your watch by her.
- You know what she did do last night?
- Wore jeans.
- Served pudding.
- I was close.
I'm sure it was some
expensive form of pudding...
but nonetheless, it was pudding!
- That is amazing.
- Right?
That would mean that she made
a mental note that we liked pudding.
Which means that she listened
to something other than...
the judgmental conga line in her head,
and got over the fact that...
to her, pudding is hospital food,
and only acceptable...
when you've just had
a vital organ ripped out.
That's some journey she had to take there.
- Open your mouth and close your eyes.
- Who are you talking to?
Right, sorry.
- Open your mouth and close your eyes.
- Okay.
Get ready for something truly amazing.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
- It's like a...
- A what?
- It's like a berry, but way more exotic.
- Yes. Good.
Have you been having reactions
to your fertilizer fumes again?
For some time now
I've been toying with cross-pollination.
Finally, I've got it.
I figured out a way
to cross a raspberry with a kumquat.
- Kumquat! That's what I taste!
- Are you serious?
How did you do this?
You didn't build a machine
like in The Fly, did you?
Will we find you wandering the streets
with a raspberry head crying, "Eat me!"
You!
You can make fun of me all you want to,
because today I am a god.
Today Mother Nature
has bowed down to me!
How nice for her.
- Michel, Jackson...
- No need to fill me in.
I'm quite happy being ignorant
of whatever it is...
that is making him raise his arms
over his head.
- Do you need me?
- The landscaper does.
Rory's birthday party is Saturday night.
So start thinking up reasons
why you can't come.
- I'm going to be out of town.
- You used that last year.
- I'll work on it and get back to you.
- 7:00. Presents mandatory.
Rasquat?
- Lucy, I'm home!
- Kitchen.
'And Justin is just so dreamy.
He can't marry Britney.
"I'll just cry, cry, and cry."
Okay, thanks.
- Pizza's on its way.
- You're such a good provider.
I'm gonna go start my homework.
Call me when the pizza guy gets here.
- Hello?
- Lorelai, what is your work schedule?
- Why?
- I want to go shopping.
- With me?
- I think that goes without saying.
- Only in your world.
- I want to get Rory a birthday present.
I'm sure whatever you get her, she'll love.
I want to get her something special.
Something that you would get her.
Okay, fine. You can get her the bong then.
This isn't funny. I hardly see the girl.
We only get to talk at dinner once a week.
And then it's all about school, and Jane.
Lane, Mom.
I thought you might let me into
your secret club just this one time...
and help me buy her something
for her birthday.
- You're serious?
- According to you, I'm always serious.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Well, good.
I'll meet you at Damion's,
tomorrow at 3:00.
Okay.
- And dress...
- Don't finish that sentence, Mom.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Attagirl.
- What, Tristan?
- I wanted to say, "Happy birthday."
- It's not my birthday.
- No, but it will be.
"On Friday at 4:03
in the morning, Lorelai..."
What is that?
Who else got these?
I don't know.
Everyone in our class, I think.
I have to go.
I'll see you Friday, birthday girl.
That's her.
My parents are making me go.
- Another obligation party.
- My life stinks.
- Isn't this lovely?
- Oh, yeah.
As soon as we have her crowned
Queen of England, we'll give it to her.
- You are so combative today.
- Hot weather does that to me.
Mom, look. This is good.
What is that?
It's a purse shaped like a guitar.
This is great.
- Great for what?
- For Rory.
- What would Rory do with this?
- Put stuff in it and carry it.
- In public?
- Yes.
- What would people think?
- That she's an ax murderer, of course.
What about pearls?
Pearls?
A double string of pearls
with a cashmere sweater set.
Mom, she's a young girl.
Think of something young.
A Montblanc pen?
- To put on her desk at the law firm?
- She needs to write.
Not with a $200 pen, she doesn't.
Oh, hey, look.
These day planners are adorable.
You could get her the funky eraser
with the mermaid on it. She'll love that.
Please be serious.
We're shopping for Rory.
I'm shopping for her. You're shopping for
an imaginary grandchild, Barbara Hutton.
I want to get her something nice.
You asked for my help,
but you're not listening.
You wanted me to get her a Filofax
and a mermaid eraser.
- It's one suggestion.
- Yes.
And the T-shirt
with the Farrah Fawcett face.
A hero to many
who aspire to the perfect feather flip.
I don't know how to do this. Let's just go.
No. Come on, Mom.
You do know how to do this.
Think pudding.
Pudding?
Come on, you asked for my help.
You're reaching out. A little, not a lot.
Don't get freaked.
- But, Mom, pudding.
- Why do you keep saying "pudding"?
Just look around and pick up something
you think she might like.
Here.
Now, that's really good.
- Really?
- Absolutely.
Looks like something
you could buy at a car wash?
Totally. That's half the charm.
- Oh, no, it's only $12.
- $6 more than a car wash.
$12 is not a present.
$12 is a perfect present, Mom.
She'll love that.
Can I at least get her the pashmina also?
- Fine, i'll get it.
- Good choice.
It lights up.
She's not here yet.
All right. You'll have to entertain me
until she arrives.
Okay, burger boy, dance.
- Will you marry me?
- What?
Just looking for something to shut you up.
Better be nice to me,
or I'm not inviting you...
to Rory Gilmore's birthday celebration
this Saturday night.
You don't have to ask me, you know.
I know. But I would like you to come.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay, i'll see.
- 7:00. Don't be late.
Wow, nice face you got on there.
- Coffee.
- Bad day?
I've now used the word "suck" so much
that it's lost all meaning to me.
Maybe this will cheer you up.
- What?
- You'll see.
- What is that?
- These are our party dresses.
So it's a Halloween party?
Listen, you. So I'm shopping today
with your grandmother...
and it's a whole three hours of,
"Who are you buying that for, Mom?"
"Have you met Rory?" And then finally
I talked and she listened.
She wound up getting you something
I think you're gonna like.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
And she insisted on
buying us these dresses.
But I think I can do something
to make them better.
I've never seen you so cheery
after spending time with Grandma.
It's been a long time since we got together
and didn't end up fighting.
It was refreshing. It wasn't exactly fun...
but I didn't get that shooting pain
in my eye like I usually do.
- That's great.
- Yeah.
So I hear you're having a party Saturday.
Yeah. Mom's famous for her blowouts.
- The best one was her eighth birthday.
- Yeah, that was good.
- The cops shut us down.
- Shut down an 8-year-old's birthday party?
And arrested the clown.
I don't want to hear any more of this.
So now tell me,
why Miss Lemonhead today?
Nothing. I'm fine.
I just got an A-minus on a French test
that I should have gotten an A on.
Honey, an A-minus is awesome.
Yeah, it's fine.
Let me see.
Maybe we should really embrace
the whole tulle thing.
Go totally modern Cinderella.
What do you think?
It's your birthday.
Yeah, lucky me.
Happy birthday, little girl.
I can't believe how fast you're growing up.
Really?
- Feels slow.
- Trust me, it's fast.
- What do you think of your life so far?
- I think it's pretty good.
Any complaints?
I'd like that whole humidity thing
to go away.
All right. I'll work on that.
So, do I look older?
Oh, yeah.
You walk into Denny's before 5:00,
you've got yourself a discount.
Good deal.
- So, you know what I think?
- What?
I think you're a great, cool kid,
and the best friend a girl could have.
Back at you.
And it's so hard to believe
that at exactly this time...
many moons ago,
I was lying in exactly the same position...
Oh, boy, here we go.
Only I had a huge, fat stomach,
and big, fat ankles.
And I was swearing like a sailor...
- On leave.
- On leave, right.
- And there I was...
- In labor.
And while some have called it the most
meaningful experience of your life...
to me it was
something more akin to doing the splits...
on a crate of dynamite.
I wonder if the Waltons ever did this.
And I was screaming and swearing...
and being surrounded as I was
by a hundred prominent doctors...
I just assumed there was an actual use...
- for the cup of ice chips they gave me.
- There wasn't.
But pelting the nurses sure was fun.
I love you, Mom.
We're getting to the part
where he sees your head.
So there I was, lying...
You shouldn't have to go to school today.
- I have to. Latin test.
- Jeez. Every day you have a test.
Do you have time to learn anything
to be tested on?
- Wrong table.
- Since when is there a right table?
Since the coffee cake I baked for you,
and the stupid balloons I blew up...
are at that table, over there.
- You blew up balloons for me?
- Yeah.
Luke, you old softy.
- I count to three, it's gone.
- Thank you.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I just...
I'm getting old, Lane.
- You seem a little quiet this morning.
- I'm just dreading this whole night.
It's bad enough that I have to see
these stupid kids from Chilton every day.
But tonight, on my birthday?
I've never even talked to most of them.
I've only been going to this school
for a couple of months.
God, they're gonna think
I am the biggest freak.
That I need my grandma
to get people to come to my party.
What did Lorelai say when you told her?
- I didn't.
- Why not?
- Because of the pudding.
- Right, I forgot about the pudding.
Grandma served us pudding
the other night.
Then she went shopping with my mom,
and they didn't fight.
I mean, they never get along.
And now, suddenly, they're getting along.
I knew that if I told Mom about the invite,
she'd wig out and call Grandma...
and that would be the end of the pudding.
You know, you can buy pudding.
- It's one night, right?
- Right.
I can stand it for one night.
Coffee to go, please.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- Why are you smiling?
- I'm just thinking about pudding.
No, not there. In the living room.
Why are you touching that?
- I was just...
- Well, don't!
I want those 6 inches apart. Get a ruler.
- Emily.
- Let me do that.
I hope the Larsons are coming tonight.
Richard, no business.
This is your granddaughter's party.
Five minutes of shoptalk
won't spoil the evening.
- Five minutes, please.
- Emily...
If I ever heard you keep your shoptalk
down to five minutes, I'd drop dead.
I could drop dead,
and you wouldn't stop talking business.
You'd just step over my body
to get to the speakerphone.
- What?
- You look very nice tonight.
Thank you.
Jeez, Mom, leave some servants
for the rest of the neighborhood.
- There she is, the birthday girl.
- Hi, Grandma.
Wow, you really went all out.
I wanted everything to be perfect.
What do you think?
Edith Wharton would have been proud,
and busy taking notes.
- Here, babe, go change.
- Okay.
Hurry.
- What is that?
- That's my dress.
- Where's the one I bought you?
- This is it.
I thought there was more of it.
- Mom, the place looks great.
- Did you turn Rory's into a hat?
Nice candles. 6 inches apart?
You're drinking white wine tonight?
No Scotch?
Excuse me. I'm going to sit over there
with my daughter.
Here.
- What is it?
- Shirley Temple.
- What are you drinking?
- A Shirley Temple Black.
I got your Good Ship Lollipop
right here, mister.
So, do you want something to eat?
Everything smells funny.
There you are. Come.
There's some people I want you to meet.
- Lorelai?
- Yeah.
Oh, my God! Oh, Mitzi,
wow, I haven't seen you since...
Your seventh month.
I was gonna say high school, but okay.
- Oh, no. Did I say something rude?
- No.
No, I did. I said something rude.
I've been trying to work on that.
Well, a noble goal.
Ever since my divorce,
I've been really trying to work on myself.
I just... I want to grow.
Lorelai Gilmore, the scandal girl.
Now, tell me,
what ever happened with Christopher?
- Christopher is in California.
- Do you hear from him?
I'm sorry,
is this painful for you to talk about?
When did he last call you?
You're making progress
with that rude thing.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
He calls, like, once a week.
And we see him at Christmas...
sometimes Easter. It's all very civil.
- So are you married now?
- No, it's just me and Rory.
- Your cat?
- My kid. She's right over there.
You can really see Christopher in her,
can't you?
- Yes, you can.
- Does that kill you?
You know what? I see someone else,
and it's been great.
- No, those aren't the terms we agreed on.
- They most certainly are.
You were at the same meeting as I was.
We spelled out a five-year extension,
not a three-year one.
I heard three.
- Hey, Grandpa.
- Rory.
Gentlemen, this is
my granddaughter, Rory.
Happy birthday, Rory.
I think we should get Dennis
on the phone right now.
Fine, I've got a phone in my office.
Rory, there's a group
of your school friends in the library.
Let's go say hello to them.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Just say hello first.
Come on, i'll hold those for you.
- Who's that?
- I think it's her party.
Paris?
- My parents made me come.
- Oh, God!
Otherwise I wouldn't be here.
You believe me, don't you?
Oh, coming to greet me?
Hello, Tristan.
- So where's my birthday kiss?
- It's my birthday.
- So i'll give you a birthday kiss.
- What is wrong with you?
Okay, I gotta tell you something.
- I'm madly in love with you.
- Well, good luck with that.
I can't eat, I can't sleep.
I wake up in the middle of the night
calling out your name. Rory.
Would you shut up please?
Rory, who's your friend?
- I don't know, but this is Tristan.
- Excuse me?
- Tristan Dugray, sir.
- Dugray?
- Are you any relation to Janlen Dugray?
- That's my grandfather, sir.
I've done business with Janlen for years.
- He's a fine man.
- That he is.
You have very good taste in friends.
I approve.
Richard, I've got Dennis on the phone
and he heard the same thing I heard.
Well, one wrong man
can always find a friend.
- He likes me.
- He's drunk.
Let's take a walk.
This is stupid. You don't even like me.
You have this weird need to prove
that i'll go out with you.
That's not liking someone.
Why are you fighting this?
You're gonna give in eventually.
I'm gonna go find my mother.
Wow, meeting your mom.
It's a bit sudden, but okay, I'm ready.
There you are.
I think it's time you said
a few words to your guests.
- What?
- Just a little speech to say thank you...
and tell everyone how it feels
to be a year older.
- I don't think...
- She's the hostess.
- This is her responsibility.
- I am not the hostess. You are.
Honey, hold on.
This is your party,
and these are your guests.
I don't have anything to say to them.
So you give the speech. Excuse me.
What was that all about?
Lorelai, your daughter
has no manners whatsoever.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
How did this become my fault?
- Can I come in?
- It's your room.
How are you doing?
I'm sorry I snapped at Grandma.
That was a pretty Freaky Friday moment
we had back there.
She just went ahead
and invited all those kids from Chilton.
You're kidding.
I thought she checked on that with you.
- She didn't ask me or tell me.
- Oh, man, I'm so sorry.
I don't know, but it really made me mad.
- Honey, why didn't you tell me?
- Because you were happy.
It's not often
that there's peace between you two.
I didn't want to screw everything up.
I appreciate you wanting
Mom and I to get along...
but you shouldn't keep such stuff from me.
I feel terrible.
I mean, I've never yelled at her before.
Listen, you'll apologize.
All will be forgotten.
You'll see.
It's like time has stood still in this room.
It must be weird
for you to be in this room now.
It was weird for me
to be in this room then.
You know,
they gave this to me with the glass on.
I now officially know what it feels like
to have grown up here.
It's not official until you're huddled
in a corner, eating your hair.
Do you remember your last birthday here?
We had just had a fight, and I was
lying on the bed just like you are now.
What did you fight about?
- I was pregnant.
- That.
And I said something at the table
about the pate smelling like Clorox...
and one thing led to another,
and I wound up here.
They hadn't told anybody yet
about me and you.
- That must have been really hard on them.
- Yeah.
I remember when I finally told them...
it was the only time
they ever looked small to me.
- I guess I'd better go find Grandma.
- Give her a minute...
- There you are.
...she'll find us.
You are both being very rude.
This isn't my birthday party, you know.
- Sorry, Mom.
- Honestly, the way the two of you act.
- Grandma, I just want to say...
- We'll talk about this later. Now go.
Thank you. Good to see you.
Lovely as always, Leeza.
My best to Darren.
Great party. One of your best.
I even liked
those brown mushroom things.
Grandma, can I talk to you for a sec?
Richard, the girls are leaving.
- Rory, I hope you had a good time.
- Yeah, I did.
I know your grandmother
has already bought you a gift...
and signed my name to it.
That was part of our agreement
when we got married.
However, I feel this occasion
calls for something a little extra.
Put that towards your trip to Fez.
- Oh, Grandpa.
- You're a good girl, Rory. Happy birthday.
- I don't deserve this.
- Fine. Hand it over.
You should get going.
You've got quite a drive ahead.
Grandma, we're having a party tomorrow
at our house.
It won't be anything like this...
but it will be fun.
Maybe you and Grandpa could come.
That's very sweet,
but I'm afraid we already have plans.
- Okay.
- Have a safe trip.
Lock the door behind you.
Why don't you go help that guy out there
put all the presents in the car?
All this can go in the dishwasher.
- Mom, come to the party tomorrow.
- I can't. I'm busy.
Throw those out. We won't eat them.
Your granddaughter invited you
to her birthday party. Please come.
I've already been to a party
for my granddaughter...
and she humiliated me
in front of all my friends.
I have no desire to relive that experience.
The cheeses must be
put in individual bags.
Mom, come on. Give her a break.
You invited all these Chilton kids
without asking her.
They're her schoolmates.
I assumed they were her friends.
You know what they say
when people assume things.
No, what do they say?
- That you shouldn't.
- Very clever.
Mom, she didn't want them here.
She doesn't like them.
I had to invite them.
That's good manners,
something your daughter is sorely lacking.
You're doing the same thing to her
that you always did to me.
You try to control her.
When that doesn't work you shut her out.
I'm too tired for your accusations
right now.
Can we do this tomorrow?
I'll find you a pen...
so you can write down your insults
so you won't forget them.
This is not funny.
I have a crushed kid out in the car.
What do you want me to say?
Everything's fine. It's forgotten.
There. I'll see you next week.
So I guess the whole pudding thing
was just a fluke, huh?
Trying to get to know us,
easing up on the rules...
smudging that bottom line of yours.
It was just some weird phase.
You were on cold medicine
last week or something?
Oh, so I'm a villain now, is that it?
I spent a fortune on this party.
I spent days planning it,
making sure every detail was perfect...
the food, the linen, the music.
I did all this for Rory.
That's not what she needed.
What she needs is
for you to accept her apology...
and come to her party.
That's what she needs.
- You don't care what she needs.
- How dare you?
You don't know what she needs
'cause you don't know her.
You've never tried to know her,
like you never knew me.
- I know you.
- You don't know anything about me.
You'd like to think that.
That you're some huge mystery?
"Why does Lorelai do that?"
"I don't know. She's a mystery to me."
- You're not so mysterious, Lorelai.
- No. What am I then?
Right now you're very loud and disruptive
to the cleaning process.
What do I have to do to get you to put
the damn cheese in individual bags?
Fine. I give up.
If I had a dollar
for every time you gave up...
Then you could pay for this party,
couldn't you?
I made coffee.
Hangover?
- Emily.
- Got it. Moving on.
- Good morning.
- Morning, popcorn.
- You want some pancakes?
- No, I've gotta get going.
- Where?
- The college fair is today.
So you're going to get
another Harvard brochure?
I just wanna see
if they've changed the pictures.
Weirdo.
I'll be back in plenty of time
to help you decorate.
This is your party. You do not work.
You mock those who are.
Have I taught you nothing?
- Sorry. I'll try to be better. Bye.
- Okay, bye-bye.
- New brochure?
- Yes.
- What are you doing here?
- There's a college fair going on.
- No. I mean what are you doing here?
- I'm getting a new brochure.
- Why?
- Because they're not selling pizza.
- Oh, no.
- You can't.
- You're applying to Harvard?
- Yes.
Ten generations of Gellers
have gone to Harvard.
I have to go to Harvard.
- I can't believe this.
- You can go somewhere else.
Go to Brandeis. Brandeis is nice.
I've only ever wanted to go to Harvard.
That's it. Nowhere else.
- It's a big school.
- I guess.
- We'll probably never see each other.
- You think?
- Lf we do, we duck.
- Okay.
- Are you dating Tristan?
- What? No way.
- Do you like him?
- Not even a little.
- Really?
- Really.
- Nice party.
- Thanks.
Hi, everybody. Happy birthday, Rory.
Oh, my God.
Open it.
- No!
- Do you like it?
- You can take it back.
- No, I love it.
- It's perfect.
- It's blue, and it has a handle.
- It's way too expensive.
- I know.
- That's what I told the guy at the store.
- On three, 'cause I'm gonna drop it.
One, two...
Make a wish.
All right, everybody, I need your attention.
Attention, please.
This is a very serious moment.
Two priests, a rabbi, and a duck...
- Mom.
- All right, I'm kidding.
I would like to propose a toast...
to the one thing in my life
that is always good...
always sweet...
and without whom I would have
no reason to get up in the morning.
My pal Rory. Cheers.
Here's to you, birthday girl.
And in honor of this very special girl...
I now invite you all
to help me eat her face.
And you may have the first cut.
There's something very strange
about hacking into my own head.
Jeez, who the hell's ringing the bell?
It's a party. Get your ass in here.
Or asses I guess.
Grandma, Grandpa...
I can't believe you're here.
I'm so glad you came.
- Hey, no tie?
- I thought I'd mix it up a little.
- Grandma, look.
- Why, it looks lovely.
I want you to meet everyone.
Everyone, these are my grandparents.
Lorelai, you look well.
I'm Patricia Lacosta.
We just love your daughter
and granddaughter.
Thank you.
My God, you're a tall specimen of a man.
Must be all that good air in Hartford.
Mom, Dad, can I get you a drink?
- No, thank you.
- You're gonna need one.
I have wine glasses that say
"Holiday Inn" on them.
- Stoli on the rocks with a twist.
- Right.
- My parents are here.
- No.
I've cursed in front of them twice,
Miss Patty tried to hit on my dad...
and I'm sure Mom's gonna call
Child Protective Services.
- When was the last time they were here?
- Never.
- Not once?
- Not since we moved here.
They'd come down and visit us
occasionally when Rory was a baby...
and we lived at the Inn,
but they have never been here.
That's big stuff. Is Rory thrilled?
- Through the roof.
- Oh, that's great.
Lorelai, I just tried
some of those hors d'oeuvres.
They're unbelievable.
- Who is your caterer?
- Sookie.
- What's a Sookie?
- That's a Sookie.
- Hi, Sookie St. James.
- Sookie's the chef at the Inn, Mom.
- My dear, you are very talented.
- Thank you.
You must cater my next party.
When my friends get wind of you...
you'll have so much business,
you won't know what to do.
But remember, I discovered you.
Mom, Sookie has a job.
She's the chef at the Inn.
The Inn where we work.
My Inn.
Six days a week, Mom.
She cooks there every day.
Just give her your number
or we'll never get out of here.
- So, how does it look?
- It doesn't look structurally sound.
Drink up, Dad.
Okay, don't panic.
- Good opening line. What's wrong?
- We're out of ice.
How can we be out of ice?
We had a ton.
It was like a penguin habitat in there.
I don't know how it happened.
I just know it happened.
Somehow we have to deal with it.
I will go and get some then.
Oh, my God. You're a vision!
- Sookie, we have ice.
- Hallelujah.
How did you know?
A good rule of thumb is
you can never have too much ice.
You're the best!
Hi, Mom. This is my friend Luke.
- How do you do?
- Fine, thank you.
I'd better get these in the freezer
before they melt.
Not very likely in here.
- Rory, what a lovely party.
- I brought you something to read.
It's not The Wall Street Journal.
But there's a quiz there that determines
if you're a summer or a fall.
I appreciate this. Thank you.
Morey, you remember the time
that Rory decided...
that our old tree stump was a fairy ring?
- I sure do.
- How old was she then, sugar?
I think she was about 10.
All I know is
that it matched the description.
Oh, God, she was cute.
She used to sit out there
with a peanut-butter sandwich...
just waiting for the fairy to get hungry.
Okay. New story.
I'm still crushed beyond belief
that she quit her ballet lessons.
Oh, not me.
Miss Perfect Work Ethic would
prance around this room 24 hours a day.
- And I still stunk.
- I can vouch for that.
- That's not true.
- She was pretty bad.
Don't you listen to them.
You had a true gift.
What?
She did. She was talented.
I made that.
- Really?
- From Rory's old baby clothes.
How nice. I hope you washed them first.
Oh, rats. I knew I forgot something.
That's quite an assortment of characters
you have down there.
They're great people.
- This Patricia.
- Miss Patty.
- She teaches dance?
- Among other things.
- This man with the ice...
- Luke.
How long have you been seeing him?
I'm not seeing Luke. He's just a friend.
Mom, I swear.
Luke keeps me in coffee. Nothing else.
He seems to like you.
- And you're judging this by what?
- By the way he looked at you.
Which was how?
Like you were about to
give him a lap dance.
- Mom, he did not look at me like that.
- You're pleased.
- What?
- You smiled.
You're glad that the ice man
looked at you like a porterhouse steak.
I'm smiling because you're crazy...
and that's what you do to crazy people
to keep them calm.
- What's this?
- That's me, Mom.
I know it's you. You're wearing a cast.
Yeah. That's when I broke my leg.
- You broke your leg?
- Yeah, three years ago during a yoga class.
The headstand portion
took a very ugly turn.
The good thing was that I brought the
smug, blonde, pretzel chick down with me.
I've since learned
that I'm a bit too competitive for yoga.
- I never knew you broke your leg.
- It was no big deal, Mom.
If I had been really sick
you would have known.
You could get a maid in here
once a week to at least tidy up.
- I like it cluttered.
- You can't even find the bed.
Yes, I can. It's the thing I crash into
on the way to the closet.
I should go check on your father.
It was nice that you came tonight, Mom.
It meant a lot to Rory. Really.
She is my granddaughter, after all.
- I should be here.
- I totally agree.
Leave it, Mom.
- It's time to go now.
- In a minute, please.
- Rory, we're going to get going now.
- Thank you for coming.
Thank you for asking me.
Lovely party.
I enjoyed the reading material immensely.
- So what's the verdict?
- I am an autumn.
- Interesting.
- Isn't it?
So are you guys leaving?
The mud wrestling starts in 10 minutes.
Good night, Lorelai. We had a lovely time.
And with a straight face you said that.
I'd have that chimney inspected
if I were you.
I'll get right on that, Dad.
- For Fez.
- But you already took care of Fez.
Fez is a very large city.
- Food fight?
- Absolutely.
She's right.
I don't know my daughter at all.
We should go. Traffic.
Next year we are going to a McDonald's
with one of those slides, and that's it.
The party was a hit.
And we'll be eating onion dip
for breakfast for a week.
You mix that dip with ground turkey
and garlic, and it is really not bad.
- I'm not looking for a recipe.
- Reflex. Sorry.
- I'm gonna go check the living room.
- Okay.
You didn't have to get me anything.
Sorry. That's the rules.
You get older, you get a gift.
I'm sorry about this sort of sneaky thing.
I just haven't told my mother yet
about you.
- Not that there's anything to tell.
- It's okay. This is better.
Oh, my God. It's beautiful.
I bought the medallion,
and then I just cut some leather straps...
and drilled a hole and, well...
Do you like it?
- It's amazing.
- Good.
- Thank you.
- Here.