Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet. World of Warcraft - Outland PVP (EU) - Torporr (name)
Hello...
Tackleberry.
We're all gonna miss you around here.
The Police Academy's getting itself
a real fine recruit.
May I...
go now?
Affirmative, sir.
Ten-four.
Yes, of course. Ten-four.
You guys.
Surprise.
Lot's full, mister.
Look, don't give me that crap.
- You've got a space.
- The lot's full, sir, really.
Find a spot, dickhead.
- Dickhead?
- That's right. Where's the manager?
Dickhead?
Park the car, butt breath.
- Butt breath?
- Yeah.
Wait a minute. Hold everything.
That's a wig, isn't it?
- Ahem. Park the car.
- Yeah, that's a wig.
Wig! Wig! Dong-dong-dong!
- Wig alert! Wig alert! Dong-dong-dong!
- Park the car, asshole. Shut up.
Girls. It's a rug.
What the hell's going on here? Hi, Lou.
- Lou?
- This rude little punk won't park my car.
Mahoney, park this car.
If you can find a spot...
Do it now or you're fired.
You understand? Fired.
Fired? That's not fair,
the guy has a bad attitude.
Do it, okay?
I want you to apologize to this man,
then park his car.
Yes, sir.
- I'm sorry.
- Get out of here.
And clean the ashtray while you're at it.
Yeah, I'm sorry, Lou. You just can't get
good help these days.
- Respect for anything.
- They don't respect customers.
They don't respect property.
They don't respect respect.
Holy shit. Jesus.
It fits. Damn thing fits.
I thought there were no more spaces.
Am I an idiot or what?
Hi, fellas.
Hey, guys, just...
Hey, hey!
Guys, I don't think I'm supposed
to get the photos wet.
You're going to pay for this.
Mark my words.
And you want to know why?
I'll let you know why. It's no secret.
Everybody knows.
I'm joining the police force. Ha, ha!
What do you think of that?
Now who's in charge?
Hey, sarge, it's him again.
I'll call Captain Reed.
Sit over there, Mahoney.
All right, let's go.
Sit. And stay there.
- What are you in for?
- I'll show you.
Goddamn it! Stop that!
Oh, no, sir. No, not you.
That's terrific. Really.
- What's your name?
- Jones. Larvell Jones.
Monsignor Larvell Jones.
M.D.
- Let's go, Mahoney.
- See you around, monsignor.
Doctor monsignor.
Why can't you stay out of trouble?
I mean...
What's wrong with you?
Last week: Disturbing the peace.
Week before that:
Destroying private property.
And I'm getting tired of saving your butt.
I only do it because of your father.
- He was a good friend.
- Yeah, I know.
Now, Mahoney, I've made a decision.
I ain't gonna help you this time.
You're going to the county lockup.
- Lockup?
- Mm-hm.
Why? I didn't do anything really major.
- Then I'll make a deal with you.
- Anything.
I want you to go to the Police Academy.
The Police Academy?
Even if you never graduate,
the training will be good for you.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Reed?
Listen, you've seen the commercials
on TV.
The Academy's taking
all kinds these days.
Anybody can get in.
Even you.
No deal. That's nuts.
Well, it's either that or the lockup.
- Police Academy or jail.
- Will I get my own squad car?
You'll get 14 weeks of Academy training
and discipline...
- Starting Monday morning.
- Fourteen weeks.
Oh, they can throw you out.
But you can't quit.
You quit, and you're back in jail.
That's the deal.
- Can I bring a friend?
- Who?
Monsignor Larvell Jones,
my personal physician.
You decide.
Honey, please don't go. I love you.
I don't want to see you hurt.
I worry about you.
You're so accident-prone.
And the Police Academy
is such a dangerous place.
Honey, don't worry. I'll be okay.
Everything'll be okay.
You start that car
and you're a dead man, buster.
Honey, I'm late.
You pull out of that driveway
and I'll have your head on a pole.
Come back here, you turkey!
You move this car an inch
and you're finished, mister. You hear me?
Of all the things that you could be
in this world, why a policeman?
A policewoman, mother.
But why?
Because it's exciting, it's different.
It'll give me a chance to meet
interesting and unusual people.
Right now! If you don't pull over...
People who aren't like you and me.
- Hey, look, it's the chief.
- Really?
Hey, mention my name.
Cadet Kyle Blankes
reporting for duty, sir.
Get away from me, you asshole.
Yes, sir.
- Where are we, man?
- Ecuador.
Okay! Oh, here we are.
I got to go now. Bye.
- Bye, sweet-pea. Bye, cutie-pie.
- We'll miss you.
- Okay.
- Bye!
Okay, girls. Remember, I love yous.
- Introduce yourself around, man.
Bye! Bye, babies. Goodbye.
Hey, excuse me.
- Do you know all those women?
- Sure.
- They're my girlfriends.
- All of them?
- Yeah.
- Carey Mahoney.
I'm George Martin, Carey.
We should be pals.
You're an interesting guy.
You a cadet?
I am until I can get myself
thrown out of here.
I'll be gone by 10:00.
You, like, joined the Academy
to get thrown out?
That's right.
Hey, you're a pretty interesting guy
yourself.
Look at that.
Just look at that.
Look at that scum.
When I went through this academy...
every cadet was the right weight,
the right height, color...
and they all had Johnsons, Lassard.
Every single one of them.
Johnsons?
You know...
Oh, yes.
Back in the old days, there were Johnsons
as far as the eye could see.
And what a lovely sight it was.
Have you seen these applications?
Have you seen what our new lady mayor
has brought us?
Do you know she is attempting
to dismantle...
one of this country's great institutions
of law and order?
What do you say to that, Lassard?
The bitch.
- Commandant?
- Yes, chief.
The mayor says we've got
to take this flotsam.
But that doesn't mean
we have to put them on the force.
You get my drift?
Weed the undesirables out.
- Get rid of them.
- No problem, chief.
We'll start washing them out
this morning.
We don't throw them out.
They must be encouraged to quit
on their own.
- Do you understand?
- I think I understand, sir.
Thank you, Lieutenant Harris,
I'm sure you do.
- Lassard?
- What?
Do you understand?
- It's clear as glass, chief.
- Good.
Then we all know what to do.
That's it...
There sure are a lot
of spades around here.
Which I think is good.
Very good for the Academy.
What the hell are you doing here?
I want to be a police officer.
What? I can't hear you.
- Don't unpack.
- Well...
time to get thrown out.
Princess. Princess! Prin...!
- What's your name, Cadet?
- Thompson, sir.
- You live around here?
- No, sir.
What's your telephone number,
Thompson?
Come on, eyes front. Telephone number.
5-5-52-4-6-7, sir.
Okay, let's see the thighs.
Come on, come on. I haven't got all day.
The thighs.
- What in the hell are you doing?
- Meeting women, sir.
What's your name, dirtbag?
- Dirtbag?
- Your name?
Mahoney, sir.
Back in line, Mahoney.
Sir, can I have a second with you?
Listen.
I don't really belong here.
I'm not right for this.
Get back in line.
Now!
Mom, it's all right. Don't worry.
Come here, Princess.
My name is Commandant Lassard.
Welcome to the new police force.
Your training time here will last...
Fourteen.
Fourteen weeks.
You will be schooled in firearms,
police procedures, local laws...
and many, many other things.
After those 12 weeks,
some of you will be police officers...
and some of you will not.
Some of you will be...
Here at the Academy...
you will learn...
You will learn...
Princess. Princess. Come here.
Princess?
Looks more like a prince to me.
- Give me that dog.
- Ahem. But he's mine, sir.
He's a queer.
Cadets, proceed to the supply room
and draw your uniforms.
Fall out. Let's go. Move it.
Move it, move it, move it.
- Next.
- What about guns? When do we get guns?
Next.
- I'm a size 9, sometimes a size 10.
- Next.
Hey! You three dirtbags report
to the Academy barber...
before you do anything else.
Where's that?
Find it, rat face.
Rat face?
- He probably meant the other guy.
- Oh. Oh, okay.
- What's that?
- That's where the commandant...
- And his wife live.
- Nice.
Oh. Excuse me.
Do you know where we get our clothes?
Yeah. You gotta go right over there.
- Here? Okay, thanks.
- Mm-hm.
- Go in and tell them Mahoney sent you.
- Got it.
- Be out of here by 3:00.
- Move it, dirtbag. I'm first.
And I'm next.
For important guys like you, I'll wait.
Okay, let's go. Take it all off.
You got it.
Hello?
- Just a little off the side, please.
- You bet.
- You can do that?
- Sure. This ain't the Army, you know.
Let's go, let's go! We've got to find
you little babies a place to sleep.
Better listen up, you fart-blossoms.
- You sure you said Mahoney?
- Yeah, I even spelled it to her.
- Copeland and Blankes, in here.
- Sir.
This man is my personal physician.
I can't live without him, sir.
Right down here,
I want Fackler and Martin.
I've known him since childhood...
- Right here, Mahoney and Tackleberry.
- Yes, sir! Thank you, sir!
Thank you.
I've always wanted to live with a nut.
My pleasure.
- Mahoney, is it?
- Yes, sir. I'd like to say one more...
The rest of you wimps come with me.
Move it, move it, move it.
Wimps?
- You're married?
- Yeah.
That's beautiful, man.
To me, marriage is a sacred institution.
So tell me.
You and the wife do it doggie-style
or what?
Room ready for inspection, sir.
Good haircuts, men.
- Thank you, sir.
Damn good haircuts.
Men...
I've got a little problem.
It seems I've got a squad
full of scumbuckets.
A whole big bunch of losers.
And I was kind of hoping
that you two fine, young cadets...
might help me to just get rid of
a few of them.
What do you say?
Will you help me out?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
- I'm Copeland, sir. Chad Copeland.
Good for you.
Hi, I'm Douglas Fackler.
I always wanted to be a cop.
Lieutenant Hoffman, Lieutenant Hoffman...
report immediately to the infirmary.
Hey, Thompson. Well?
- How do I look?
- That wasn't very funny this morning.
Wasn't funny.
I'd give anything to see your thighs.
Don't suppose you'd
describe them for me.
Well, they're tan, of course.
Very supple, well-rounded...
and luxuriant to the touch.
Mm.
Absolute silence!
My name is Lt. Harris...
in case you missed it.
This is Sgt. Callahan...
We are the meanest instructors here.
We've got you because
you are the worst people here.
You people are D-Squad.
D for dirtbags.
When I say, "Hey, dirtbags,"
that means you.
You people are going to hate my guts
for the rest of your lives.
I am going to make you sorry
that you ever came here.
Now, it is traditional here at the Academy
for each squad...
to have two student squad-leaders.
I have chosen Cadets Blankes
and Dopeland. Step out, men.
If these two cadets give you an order...
obey it.
Now, I thought it would be nice...
if we were to close out
our first afternoon together...
with a nice little stroll
around the campus.
Move out, maggots!
- Holy, shit.
- This is definitely not Ecuador.
Get up, Barbara. Get up. Get up.
Move it, move it, move it.
I could show a movie on your butt, fatso.
Nineteen. Twenty!
More! I want more!
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
Eighteen. Let's go. Let's go.
Nine. Ten.
Attention. Lights out in 10 minutes.
Lights out in 10 minutes.
Game over.
Asshole.
Police work...
is what...
you are...
here for.
Arrest...
procedures...
traffic violations...
high-speed...
driving...
self-defense.
And you will have many examinations...
which you must pass.
Plus...
you will endure an extremely rigorous
physical training program.
Do you know what that means, Hooks?
I'm not sure, sir.
What?
Voice commands.
We will learn to use our voices
with authority.
Won't we, Hooks?
Now, have any of you
had any military training?
Mm-hm?
I served with the U.S. Army
Airborne 209th Special Forces Unit.
Anybody else?
What?
You have had prior
military training, Mahoney?
- Well, yes, but not in this life, sir.
- What?
In a previous life, I served
with Her Majesty's Forces in India.
- Interesting sideline...
- If you're trying to get thrown out...
I'm afraid that's quite impossible.
Impossible?
What the hell's going on here?
I'll have to see
the commandant about this.
You will also learn the Municipal Code.
And you will learn them by heart.
Cadet Mahoney. Cadet Mahoney.
Report immediately to the commandant's
office. Cadet Mahoney.
Okay, Mahoney, get going. On the double.
Move it. Move it. Move it.
Now...
Lieutenant Harris, Lieutenant Harris...
report immediately to the firing range.
Lieutenant Harris.
Excuse me.
Callahan, take over.
Howdy.
- No one's allowed in here.
- Listen.
- I got a problem, chief.
- It's commandant.
Commandant, I'm sorry.
Is that your fish?
- No, it belongs to a friend.
- Very pretty.
- What do you want?
- I want out of here. Right now.
- Out of this office?
- No, out of the Academy.
- That's no problem. You can just quit.
- I can't quit.
Of course you can.
Many, many wonderful people...
- Have quit many, many...
- Commandant?
Do you know Capt. Reed?
Oh, yes. Capt. Reed. You're Mahoney.
Mahoney. Mahoney. Mahoney.
- You're a special case. You can't quit.
- I know that.
- On the other hand, I can't throw you out.
- Why not?
I promised Capt. Reed. I promised
I'd keep you here the full 24 weeks.
You what? You what? You told...?
He told me that I could...
- I'm trapped here?
- Well, yes. We all are.
Pick it up, pick it up.
Keep moving up that hill.
Put some muscle in it.
Get those knees up.
Get those knees up, come on!
Hustle, hustle, hustle!
This is definitely not for me.
Keep going!
Come on, Hooks, get over the wall.
Move it, move it, move it.
Come on, Hooks, get up.
Skip it. Go around. You'll never make it.
Why don't you quit now?
Quit, quit, quit. You'll never make it.
Sir, I'm terribly sorry,
but I seem to have ripped my pants.
Don't try me, punk.
Now, wise guy...
you run, don't trot...
to the supply room,
and you get a new pair.
Yes, sir. I'll be back later in the day.
Be back in five minutes!
Yes, sir. Shit, I'm deaf.
Hey, you got any brown shoe-polish?
I've got cordovan. Who's it for?
Lieutenant Harris.
Sir! Look, sir, new pants.
What are you doing...? Give me that.
All right, you scumbags, you have
30 minutes to shower and get to class.
Let's go. Move it. Move it. Move it.
Pick it up. Pick it up.
Pick it up, assholes.
So far, nobody's quit.
But they will.
Well, well, well.
I told you not to try me, boy.
Stand up.
Now, I want you two squad leaders...
to take Mr. Mahoney here
and run him until he throws up.
- Yes, sir.
And then, just after he throws up...
run him some more.
- Yes, sir.
You are going to learn, Mahoney...
that nobody...
nobody...
screws...
with me.
- Pick it up, pick it up! Come on!
- Hey, this is great.
- Two assholes, no waiting.
- Move it!
Chad, would you please just let me
yell at him without interrupting?
- Sure.
- Come on, Mahoney! Move it, move it!
Bang!
Son, where did you get this gun?
My mom gave it to me.
Can I borrow it for a little while?
Sure.
Left, left right left.
Left, left, left right left.
You will learn to defend yourselves
without stick or firearm.
I need a volunteer.
- Barbara, get out here.
- I just ate.
Right where I'm standing.
Right here. Right now.
All right, come at me
with an imaginary knife.
Do I have to?
Yes, you do. I'm not joking.
Come on. Come on.
Now!
Ouch! Ouch!
Okay. That's how it's done. Who's next?
- Pick me!
- I'd love it. I'd love to go.
I'd love to go. We'll both go.
You have 20 minutes
to complete the test.
Try to answer as many questions
as possible.
All right, start.
All right, here we go.
The count's at two. Here's the pitch.
Swung on and missed!
Struck out.
Well, it was Saturday night
And I was feeling all right
Looking for my buttercup
They were dancing next door
On the thirteenth floor
You know, Mahoney...
I'd like to spend the next month
breaking you into little pieces.
But I won't...
because you're bad.
You're bad for morale, Mahoney.
You look like the sweet little boy
from next door.
Ha. But you don't fool me. Oh, no.
No, you're the devil,
and you're rotten to the core.
And you're ruining my chances...
of training some men
who might make pretty good cops.
I agree. I've been saying that.
- You make me sick.
- Thank you, sir. I make everybody sick.
We're going to pick up this telephone
and call your buddy Capt. Reed.
And you. You are going to help me
talk him out of this terrible mistake.
Terrific. I'll do my part.
You're damn right you will.
Ha.
This is the Academy.
I'd like to speak to a Capt. Reed.
Reed!
Captain Reed? Yes, sir.
How are you, sir?
This is Lt. Harris, Lt. Thaddeus Harris
out at the Police Academy.
I'm so sorry to disturb you, sir...
but your friend Cadet Mahoney
would like to speak with you.
Just one moment, please. Mahoney.
- Mahoney!
- Oh, yeah.
Hi, Captain Reed? Can I get out of here?
No? Okay.
I tried.
Captain Reed, thank you so much.
Yes. Goodbye. Yes.
I don't know
what you're trying to do.
I don't know why you're here.
But you'll never be a cop
as long as I live.
- Don't want to be.
- Get your butt off my desk.
And get out of here!
Mahoney!
I've already told you once.
Nobody screws with me.
Well, maybe you'll meet the right girl
and all that'll change.
Get out of here now!
Come on, Mahoney.
Harris said you had to do a hundred.
Hey, Mahoney.
Here's a pair of my old sweat socks.
I wore them all day.
That should help you to get up.
You did it.
You son of a bitch.
This is a hell of a way
to spend my evenings.
I can't feel my arms anymore.
Hey, Barbara, come here.
- Me?
- Yeah, come here.
- What?
- Come on, right here.
- I want you to give me your best shot.
- What?
I want you to hit me. Best shot.
- Hit you?
- Yeah, come on.
- Ha, ha. No, really, I...
- Hit me.
- Really, when I...
- Do it now. Come on.
- I can't. Because when I...
- Do it. Give me your...
How was that? Was that okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's good.
This weekend is your first leave
from the Academy.
When you go, wherever it is
you filthbags go...
do take note of how nice things are
on the outside.
Do give serious consideration
to not coming back.
Four of you have already quit.
And that's just the beginning.
Ten-hut!
Dismissed.
Heard him, dismissed! Let's go.
They'll get together for a party.
They always do.
You go with them.
Whenever they get out of line,
give me a ring.
Hi, Leslie.
Studying hard?
Yup.
Where's the party going to be
this weekend?
Party?
Party? I don't know anything
about a party.
I'm going home for the weekend
and visit my mom and dad.
Now, if you don't mind,
I do have to study.
You know, Chad?
I don't think we've got his full attention.
So why don't you take his books
and throw them out the window?
My pleasure, Kyle.
Find out where the party is.
- How?
- Ask Mahoney.
- Mahoney.
Thousand eleven, 1012, 1013...
Mahoney.
Could I speak to you outside
for just a second?
Yeah.
What's up?
Mahoney.
Is there a party this weekend?
Yeah, of course there is.
Do you want to come?
No. No, I can't.
I just need to know where it is.
Sorry to be asking.
Then why are you asking?
Some people want to know.
Okay, yeah. It's no big secret.
It's at the Blue Oyster bar.
It's on Howell.
Hey, big boy
Why don't you come up
And see me sometime?
Hey, big boy
So, what about you, Hightower?
What are you doing at the Academy?
I got bored with my chosen profession.
- What was that?
- I was a florist.
A florist?
You know, flowers and shit.
Oh, yeah.
- Hi.
- I didn't think you'd show up.
- I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Do you want to go for a walk?
- Walk.
- Oh, yeah.
Are you kidding? Of course.
- Can you tell me something?
- Yeah?
Why do you want to be a cop?
I like to dress like a man.
Me too.
Tonight you're mine completely
You give your love so sweetly
Tonight the light of love is in your eyes
But will you love me tomorrow?
Is this a lasting treasure
Or just a moment's pleasure?
Okay, let's go. Move it. Move it. Let's go.
Two lines, right here.
The first one on the step,
the second one off.
I said two lines, dummy!
Now step it up, step it up, let's go.
Hey.
Why didn't you call me this weekend?
Well nothing really happened, sir.
There was a party, wasn't there?
Yes, sir.
Well, what went on?
Dancing, sir.
Mostly dancing.
Dancing?
Hightower, you're first. Let's go.
Come with me.
Ready now, sir.
Thank you.
I got him.
Tackleberry. You're next.
Come with me.
- Hey!
- Tackleberry!
Holy shit.
Get back here.
- Yes, sir.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Don't worry, I can explain everything.
- Shut up.
- Yes, sir.
- Yes, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am.
You've been sneaking in here
every night for weeks.
What? No.
What do you think
I ought to do about this?
Well, let's see.
My God.
Sir.
Ma'am.
A police officer must generate
respect and confidence.
His or her voice, Hooks...
has a great deal to do with that.
Hooks, get up. Stand right over here.
Today, Hooks.
Now, here is the house.
Here is the window.
And I am a burglar.
I am coming out of the window...
with a stolen stereo in my hand.
I'm coming out of the window,
over the hedge...
and you are the arresting officer.
What do you say, Hooks?
Don't move! This is a stickup.
Stickup?
I mean, police... Police officer. Stop.
Sit down, Hooks.
Sit, sit, sit.
Tackleberry, you try it. Same situation.
All right. Here is the house.
Here is the window.
I'm the burglar. I'm coming out
of the house, over the hedge...
I've got the stolen stereo in my hands.
Drop that stereo before I blow
your goddamn nuts off, asshole!
Tackleberry, we really need to talk.
Mahoney, let me ask you a question.
Have you ever had a woman just...
throw you down
and screw your goddamn brains out?
No.
It happened to me last night.
Really? How was it?
I think...
I'm in love.
- How many girls were there?
- Just one.
Just one?
You made love to just one girl?
That's disgusting.
Yeah, I know.
- Hey, George, can I ask you something?
- Sure.
Every now and then...
you seem to lose your Spanish accent.
What's up?
Yeah. Every now and then.
Can you keep a secret?
Oh, yeah.
I'm not really George Martin.
I'm just plain old George Martin,
fourth-generation American. Ha, ha.
- Really?
- I just use the accent to get the girls.
Does it work?
- Barbara!
- He's in the gym.
You're gonna pay for sending us
to the wrong party.
- I'll tell him.
- Not just pushups, either, Leslie.
We're gonna get your fat ass
thrown out of here. That's a promise!
- How?
You'll find out.
Mahoney isn't the only one here
who can play tricks.
Hey, hey. Take it easy.
These ain't track shoes.
Yeah, I know. Just hurry up.
I'm as anxious as you.
I'm not comfortable in these surroundings.
- Yeah, well, come on up.
- Up here?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Hey, listen, when do I get my money?
When the job's over,
for crying out loud.
That's good, Hightower.
Why don't you just sit down over there?
All right, you scumballs,
30 minutes to room inspection.
Move it. Move it. Move it.
- Hi, honey.
- Hi.
Got a light?
I don't smoke. Ha, ha.
I have a friend who smokes. I'll go get him.
Mahoney, major problem.
Well, my goodness.
Would you please just calm down
and take it easy?
I just like to do it in strange places,
that's all. Okay?
Why the hell didn't you say so?
You'll find this academy one of the most
comprehensive in the country.
I could point out many,
many, many features to you.
- Squeeze in here. Yeah.
- In here?
- You want to do it in a podium?
- All my life.
- Right. Where you going?
- I'll be back.
I'm not the customer. The real customer
will be here any second now, okay?
Oh, okay.
Gentlemen, please follow me.
We have a very, very fine...
slide presentation for you.
Please take your seats.
I think you'll find
there's plenty of room for everybody.
Thank you.
First of all, I'd like to say
how sorry I am...
that everybody could not make it today.
For those here, I think you'll find
the presentation interesting...
as well as very, very stimulating.
Could we have the lights turned down?
Now, this first slide...
shows a very...
very interesting thing:
Our main building.
In slide two...
we see...
another view...
of it.
Oh, my God. You wouldn't believe it.
Let us look at this slide for a moment,
without comment.
I think it speaks for itself.
Could we have the lights, please?
Well.
I hope this was as much fun for you
as it was for me.
Let's have lunch, shall we?
And maybe, smoke a cigarette.
Good speech.
What do you intend to do
about Mahoney?
- What's he done?
I'll tell you what he's done. He...
Yes, sir?
He did a very, very bad thing.
To whom, sir?
To whom?
Yes, sir.
Well, I don't know.
Are you all right, sir?
No, not really. May I go?
- Of course, sir.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Left, right, left. Left. Left.
Left, right, left. Left.
Left, right, left.
Left. Left. Left, right, left.
From now on, part of your training
will be to ride, from time to time...
in actual squad cars
with actual police officers...
in actual situations.
And you'd better actually
keep your mouths shut.
And your eyes and your ears open.
Say, Mahoney,
why don't you ride with me?
Well, move it, cretins!
Move it, move it, move it!
Lieutenant Harris, I've changed
my mind. I want to be a cop.
- Never, punk.
- Why not? All I have to do is behave...
Get out of this car, Mahoney.
You hear me?
You get. Get, Mahoney.
You get out there and you follow me.
You stay right behind me, punk.
Oh, how I love a ride in the country.
Officer. Officer.
Can you get my kitty-cat out of the tree?
No problem, ma'am.
Oh, no. No, wait.
What the hell is this?
I'll be right back. I'm sorry.
What the hell is going on down there?
Move it!
Assholes.
Hey! Hey, you, give me that bike.
Come on, move it. This is official
police business. Move it out. Let's go.
- It's new.
- Don't worry, I'm not gonna hurt it.
My God.
Someone call a veterinarian.
Your new hat, sir.
You told no one?
Not a soul.
Hightower? Hightower?
I need to talk.
That's terrific, Hightower, but it's...
It's 2:30 in the morning.
- The driving course is tomorrow.
- So?
I haven't driven a car since I was 12.
Really? You're kidding.
If I don't pass this driving course,
they're gonna kick me out. Harris said so.
All right. Let's go.
Sleeping is for fags.
First thing we gotta do is steal a car.
Copeland's should do.
Okay, your turn.
Now, you've got to remember
to drive defensively...
or offensively, depending
on your needs. Let's go.
Comfy?
- No.
- All right.
Let's just move the seat back a little.
On second thought, let's rip
the front seats out and sit in the back.
I was kidding about the front seat.
But this is good.
It's different. Comfort's important.
Put it into first. Right. Little more.
Okay, you can go a little faster now.
Yeah. Yeah, you're doing beautifully.
You feel it? You feel what's going on?
You can even
turn off the windshield wipers.
Yeah, that's it.
Okay, now there's another car.
Hightower?
Hightow...? What...?
You didn't hit the brakes.
You didn't tell me to.
You idiot!
You bastard! You dumb shit!
- Pull over and let me drive for a while.
- No, not now.
This is fun.
- Pull over.
- No, I'm getting out of here.
Holy shit!
Attaboy, Hightower.
Taught him everything he knows.
Not bad.
Miss Hooks, you're next.
Hurry up!
Thanks, Mahoney. You saved my life.
- Maybe someday you'll save mine.
- Any time.
You're next. Yellow line. Yellow line.
You better not cry
You better not pout
I'm telling you why
Wee!
Oh, this is fun.
What is it? What is it?
She ran over my feet.
I'm sorry. I really am.
Sorry? You dumb, fat jigaboo!
Oh, shit.
- At ease, Hightower. At ease.
- It's okay, Hightower.
- He didn't mean it. He was joking.
- Take it easy, now. Hightower!
Hightower, don't do that.
If you don't stop, you are out of here.
I am warning you, Hightower!
You messed up big, mister.
Now you get your stuff
and get out of here, right now.
Get!
Attention,
applications for motorcycle service...
should be turned in
at the Administration building by Friday.
Applications for motorcycle service
should be turned in...
One down, several to go.
Copeland, get out of that car.
Mahoney.
It's got to be Mahoney.
I know, I know. Come on.
Out of all the people I thought would
make it, Hightower was the one.
I mean, if all the cops looked like him,
there'd be no crime at all.
I'm getting sick of this place.
How're you doing, "Ma-homo"?
Don't fool with me.
Not in the mood.
You wrecked my car.
No, Hightower did. Why don't you
go see him? That'd be a matchup.
Because we want you.
Okay, how about 12:00 midnight?
Nine o'clock on the coast.
No, no. I'm talking right now, Mahoney.
Let's go. You throw the first punch.
Cadet could get thrown out...
- For hitting another cadet.
- Oh, really?
I thought you wanted to get thrown out.
Here's your chance.
No.
Now, Mahoney, I'm going to rub this
right in your face.
On your mark...
get set...
- Wait, you guys! Wait!
- What the hell...?
Who threw the first punch?
- That's all I want to know.
- Barbara did.
- Barbara?
- That's right, sir.
Then he's out of here.
Him and his queer dog.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Barbara didn't throw the first punch.
- He did so.
- I threw the punch.
Mahoney, you're out
of your mind. Lieutenant...
- Blankes, who'd you rather have out?
- Is that true, Blankes?
Did Mahoney start it?
Yes, sir. Mahoney started it.
Then, Mahoney, my little piss-ant...
you are out of the Academy...
forever.
Get your stuff.
And get out.
Too bad, so sad, bye-bye.
Does the radio bother you?
I could turn it down.
Here, I brought you an apple.
Thanks.
Hey, man, what...?
My God. Here, take this.
Hey, free TV's.
Hey, everybody! There's a riot going on.
My livelihood! You're ruining me!
What do you got there?
What are you doing with that TV?
- Hi. Want a ride?
- No, thanks.
Hey, did you two hear the news...
- On the radio?
- No.
- A riot's broken out downtown.
- How come?
Who knows how these things
get started?
Attention! All cadets report immediately...
to the parking lot in full riot gear.
Repeat, all cadets report immediately
This is not a drill.
- Jones! Was that you?
- No, man.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Get out there fast!
Move it, move it, move it!
Let's go, let's go.
This is it. This is the big one.
It's time this cop...
met the public.
All right, listen up.
Here's the situation. There is a state...
of general disorder
in the Oakfield section of town.
Real police are handling the problem.
We are being sent
to a peripheral safe area.
Our job will be merely to divert traffic
away from the trouble zone...
and to protect public property.
You will have live ammunition...
but there will be no call to use it.
Tackleberry, do you understand,
numb nuts?
Yes, sir.
Come on!
We are now entering
the expressway at Belmont.
Very good. Your bus is to deploy
on Sixteenth Street...
between 4th and 8th Avenues.
Sixteenth Street? Are you sure, sir?
Of course I'm sure.
I never forget a number.
Yes, sir.
There's nobody around.
I guess they're hiding.
All right, let's go, dirtbags, unload it.
Let's move it.
I want two lines right here.
Come on, dummies.
Let's go, let's go.
You, one block over, one block up.
You, one block down.
You, one block up. You, one block over.
You, one block over. Let's go. Let's go.
If you have to make an arrest...
do it as quietly as possible.
Boy, it sure is quiet around here?
Hey, Fackler. How's it going?
Oh, just fine, thanks.
- What the hell are you doing here?
- We're from the Academy.
You're supposed to be blocks away.
The damn riot's right down this street.
We're pulling out.
I love sushi. I'm into back-rubs,
all kinds of Japanese stuff.
My car stereo, it's a Sony.
I got a good friend, his father was killed
at Pearl Harbor.
Hey, maybe your family had
something to do with it?
You know sake? The wine?
I know a place where they heat it up
before they serve it.
Holy shit.
I got to go now.
Run!
Hello, men. I thought I'd come by
for a personal inspection.
- Okay if we get in, sir?
- I guess so.
Sure, why not?
Well, men, how's it going?
I want you to give me a fix
on the entire situation.
Not that good, sir.
Oh, so this is very, very, very bad.
The main thing is not to panic.
Attention! Attention, everybody.
Attention. This is Commandant
Eric Lassard of the Police Academy.
If you do not disperse immediately,
my men will have to arrest you.
You have five seconds to move away.
Five. Four. Three. Two. One.
Give me the thing.
You should park cars for a living, sir.
Anybody want any of this?
You want this? You'd die for this.
- You're not so tough now.
- Come and take it.
- How about you? You want this?
- What's the matter?
- I'm talking to you, twerp.
- Just too dumb to talk?
Damn it. Look, in here.
Try this one.
Help. Help.
This is Cadet Leslie Barbara. Help.
Barbara, this is Lt. Harris.
Just calm down.
I'm being chased by 30 rioters.
Barbara, just tell me where you are.
I'm passing you now, sir.
Holy shit.
Hi.
Get the cops!
Okay. Hold it right there, guys.
Why, if it isn't Leslie Barbara...
- The police officer.
- Yeah.
Come on, Les,
you're not going to shoot us.
You wouldn't shoot old friends,
would you?
No.
Les.
Get lost. We're busy.
Now, get the furniture back up there
and get out of the area.
But it's our furniture.
Sorry.
Callahan calling Harris. Come in, please.
Harris, come in.
Where the hell is Harris?
- I don't know.
- What?
- She doesn't know.
- I heard her.
Run!
Why don't you shoot back?
- Are those gunshots?
- Fucking A.
Shoot back. Come on.
Look up there. See? See?
That looks like Harris up there.
Should we shoot back?
I don't think so.
Come on!
Stay there.
Mahoney!
Oh, shit. Oh, shit, oh, shit, oh, shit.
I'll bet there's a back door to this place.
Hooks. Hooks!
Hooks, get the hell back here.
That's an order.
Freeze!
Oh, shit.
Don't move, you bastard.
Run, Thompson! Run!
Put the gun down.
Let's say you put your gun down.
Lieutenant Harris, any last-minute
tips or suggestions?
Nothing really comes to mind.
What's it gonna be?
Throw your gun over the ledge.
I got two piglet-wigglets.
Hey!
What do you want?
I want to watch you off these pigs.
Sure. Ha, ha. Sure.
Which one do we do first?
I believe I'd shoot this one.
Yeah, the old one.
- Looks like cadet revolvers to me.
- I know those guys.
Don't move, dirtbag!
Hey. Aw. Hey, hey.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- What's wrong with this man?
There was gunplay, sir, and he missed it.
- Lieutenant Harris? Captain Reed.
- Nice to meet you, sir.
Thank you. I also want to thank you
for looking out for Mahoney.
It was an honor and a pleasure, sir.
Thank you, sir. Ha, ha.
- Could you just...?
- This woman bothering you?
What? No. This is my mother.
Ten-four. Carry on.
- Oh, my precious...
- Mom, would...?
- Then at 8:00 you'll meet my mother.
- Right.
- You'd better have some flowers.
- Flowers, check.
You men, stop that.
Oh, well, ha, ha.
That's more like it, Mahoney.
Good man. Keep up the good work.
Thank you, sir.
Ladies and gentlemen, the commandant
of the Academy, Eric Lassard.
So many unusual events have happened
to this graduating class...
and to me, also.
I could tell you many, many stories,
but instead...
I have a presentation to make.
No Academy cadet has ever received
the highest award...
this police department has to make.
Today, there are two:
Officers Moses Hightower...
and Carey Mahoney.
Gentlemen, please step forward.
You are both expected
to make a few short remarks.
Officer Hightower.
Thanks.
That was very, very, very good.
Officer Mahoney.
Thank you, Commandant Lassard,
Chief Hurnst...
Madam Mayor, Mr. President...
His Holiness the Pope,
the King of Norway...
and our other honored guests.