JASON BOURNE: I remember.
I remember everything.
DR. HIRSCH: Captain Webb. Good morning.
Has everything been explained to you?
Yes, sir.
When we are finished with you,
you will no longer be David Webb.
I'll be whoever you need me to be, sir.
[ECHOING] You knew exactly what
it meant for you if you chose to stay.
You can't outrun what you did, Jason.
You made yourself into who you are.
Eventually you're gonna have
to face the fact.
You volunteered.
- [GUNSHOT FIRES]
- [GRUNTS]
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
[CHOKING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[INDISTINCT]
[SPEAKING GREEK]
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
[SHOUTING IN GREEK]
- [WHISTLE BLOWS]
- [CROWD CHEERS]
[GRUNTS]
[CROWD EXCLAIMS]
[PANTING]
Christian  made a reservation.
[SPEAKS IN DUTCH]
[MEN CHATTERING IN OTHER LANGUAGE]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[MEN LAUGHING]
[SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Heather Lee.
CONTROL DECK OFFICER:
Ma'am, we have a device
issued to a stay-behind team
in Novosibirsk, Russia, in 1993.
Marked on our inventory as destroyed.
It's knocking on our front door.
What's the status?
Whoever it is, is just sitting there idle.
MAN There's no outbound traffic, nothing.
Move.
- [BEEPING]
- They've found a back door.
We need the reverse shell.
I'm gonna locate the source.
I'm working on it.
Okay, people, we have a major breach
of our classified mainframe.
Drop everything you're doing,
get on it right now!
Ma'am, I'm sending you the shell.
Got it.
- WOMAN Need it right now?
- MAN Yeah.
- WOMAN Getting IP.
- MAN Where's that traceroute?
WOMAN Unknown user. Monitoring.
Reykjavik.
SecOps hacking camp.
Kill the power to the building.
CONTROL DECK OFFICER:
Get into that power grid now.
CYBER TECHNICIAN: Yes, sir.
[BEEPING]
- I've got the power to the building.
- LEE: Stand by.
- MAN1 Ten seconds.
- MAN2 Let's get on top of this.
- Shut it down.
- TECHNICIAN: Copy that. Shutting it down.
[PEOPLE EXCLAIMING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[MAN SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE]
[GRUNTS]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Dewey.
We've just been hacked.
How badly?
Could be worse than Snowden.
Is there any attribution?
We're working on it.
Lee says it must be someone
with a deep knowledge of our systems.
This could affect Deep Dream, and Iron Hand.
I want a briefing
in my conference room in one hour.
Yes.
- Did you get confirmation?
- Yeah, there was a hack.
So are we exposed?
We don't know yet. We're checking.
I want you to call Dewey.
Set up a meet in DC.
Aaron, we got a lot at stake here,
- maybe we shouldn't rock the boat.
- Just do it.
Hey, George. We ready for the launch?
Heather, you know
the Director of National Intelligence?
Heather Lee, Cyber Ops, sir.
Have you got a name for us?
The hacker was a former Agency operative.
Believed to be working
with Christian ,
and previously linked to Jason Bourne.
Bourne?
- Jesus Christ.
- What did they get?
LEE: Black-ops files.
From Treadstone all the way to Iron Hand.
Iron Hand?
But that's not even operational yet,
for Christ's sakes.
Where is Nicky Parsons right now?
On the move.
She left Reykjavik,
traveling through Bucharest to Athens.
Feels like a meet to me.
Well, how are you going to handle it?
We cut the head off this thing.
Sir, I'd like to be point on this operation.
You're not indoctrinated for this material.
LEE: I'm already into it.
I embedded malware into Parsons' download.
When those files are opened,
I can trace them.
Let me in.
I'll deliver Parsons, the files,
and, if he's out there,
I'll give you Bourne, too.
Excuse me.
I appreciate your enthusiasm,
but do not push your personal agenda
to the DNI again.
Understood.
All right. I think you can help me.
I'm going to give you
full operational control on this,
and I will make sure you have access
to any relevant teams and resources.
And I want to know every move you make.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much, sir.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yeah?
I need your help, now.
I'm not finished here.
Jason Bourne is in play.
- Where?
- Athens.
Close your account in Rome.
Understood.
[COCKS GUN]
[WHIMPERING]
[SILENCED GUN FIRES]
[WATER FLOWING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[GRUNTING]
[SHOUTS IN GREEK]
[CROWD SHOUTING IN GREEK]
[GRUNTING]
[BODY THUDS]
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
[CROWD CHANTING IN GREEK]
[MAN SPEAKING ON SPEAKER IN GREEK]
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
[POLICE SIRENS WAILING]
Lee got a hit from a CCTV feed.
Parsons boarded a bus a half-hour ago,
headed west across Athens.
I got two local teams en route.
- Any sign of Bourne?
- Not so far.
He's involved in this somehow. I can feel it.
Upload all Athens data and feeds,
and activate real-time processing.
MAN1 Copy that.
Where are we?
Parsons' bus has just arrived
at Syntagma Square.
There's a demonstration
in front of the Greek parliament building.
I think she'll use it as cover.
Deploy Alpha and Bravo to the square.
Recon for Parsons
in the crowd outside parliament,
and any possible rendezvous points.
Copy that, sir.
Sir, the Asset has landed.
[CAR ENGINE STARTING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
Alpha Team arriving now.
Copy that.
[HORN HONKING]
- [WHISTLE BLOWING]
- [INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
- I have the Alpha Team feeds.
- Pull them up.
[SHOUTING CONTINUES]
Athens police are reporting tactical teams
moving on the demonstrators.
Isolate all social-media posts
from the square.
Yes, ma'am.
Rewind Alpha One's feed.
Yes, ma'am. Twenty seconds.
MAN2 All right, Bravo Two, Four, moving in.
What's wrong?
I hacked the Agency.
For Christian .
I got all the black-ops files.
We're putting them online.
We need to move.
Stop.
Two seconds forward.
Blonde hair.
Enhance.
Find her.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
MALE OPERATOR: Nicky Parsons sighted in
Syntagma Square. Redirect south on Stadiou.
I told you, Christian
is going to get you killed.
We don't have a choice, Jason.
It's started again. A new program.
Iron Hand. It's even worse than before.
What's that got to do with me?
Because it matters. It matters.
Not to me, it doesn't.
All that matters is staying alive.
You get off the grid, survive.
I don't believe that and neither do you.
Look at yourself.
Look at what you're doing.
You can't live like this for much longer.
Jason, I came here
because I found something.
I found your father's name
in the Treadstone files.
He was an analyst.
He wasn't in Operations.
He wasn't near any of that stuff.
I'm telling you what I saw.
It looked like he was involved directly.
And there's more.
More about you.
What do you mean?
Before you joined the program,
they were watching you.
Watching me?
You've tortured yourself
for a long time now, Jason.
You torture yourself for what you've done.
But you don't know the truth
about what they did to you.
You need to read those files.
[POLICE SIRENS BLARE]
BOURNE: Move. They tracked you.
Alpha One has eyes on two targets.
One female, one male.
Identify the male.
Copy that, sir.
Alpha One, we need an ID on the male target.
We've got to get out of here before
the police cut off this part of the city.
[SHOUTING CONTINUES]
Head north.
Meet me at the statue of Athena.
I'll take them with me.
That's him.
Now.
Stay with Bourne.
Clear to engage the target.
MAN 3: Copy.
Alpha Team, stay with the male.
You are clear to engage.
Come on.
[GRUNTING]
[SPEAKING IN GREEK]
Sir, Alpha Team comms are down.
We've lost him, sir. He's taken them out.
Find Parsons. He'll come back to get her.
Sir, rioting is spreading.
The Greek government
is declaring a state of emergency.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
FEMALE OPERATOR:
Bravo Team, we are retargeting Parsons.
[SHOUTING CONTINUES]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[GRUNTS]
We got her.
Split the team, put her in a box.
[MAN SHOUTING ON SPEAKER IN GREEK]
[POLICE SIRENS WAILING]
[MOTORCYCLE REVVING]
[OFFICER SPEAKING IN GREEK]
[SIRENS WAILING]
A suspect matching Bourne's description
has stolen a police motorcycle.
He's coming for Parsons.
Where the hell is the Asset?
Two minutes out, sir.
Parsons is at the statue of Athena.
Copy that.
- [GRUNTS]
- [HORN HONKING]
[GRUNTS]
MAN 3: Bravo Team is down.
MAN4 Sir, the Asset is arriving on scene.
- LEE: Pull up the dash cam.
- MAN3 Copy.
Give me the feed
and direct comms to the Asset.
[ENGINE STALLING]
[HORN BLARING]
ASSET: Engaging targets.
LEE:
I'm accessing Athens police tactical data.
I need eyes overhead.
Bring up the satellite suite.
Sir, I'm showing a Misty
and a KH-12 satellite available.
- Light up the 12.
- Yes, sir.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Satellite video feed is online.
LEE:
Police have blocked the road to the north.
The target will be forced to turn left.
LEE: Another barricade in 200 meters.
Target turning left again.
Bourne's heading for the alley.
Left at the top of the hill.
Stairway.
Up the hill. Heading east.
Give me a strike point.
LEE: He's found a way out.
Two hundred meters to your left.
19 Solomou. Get to the roof.
Target should pass within your line of sight.
19 Solomou. Copy.
Focus the satellites on these coordinates.
And give me a lock
on the motorcycle when it gets there.
Copy that.
[PANTING]
I've got the targets.
They're approaching Omonia from Fidiou.
Look west.
The long boulevard.
Coming at you in 55 seconds.
Copy that.
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNT]
MAN4 The Asset is online.
Target's with you in 15 seconds.
Five seconds.
Contact.
Stay low!
Find a shot.
Hold on!
WOMAN Targets are down.
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
Where's Bourne?
Ma'am, a police helicopter spotted
three bodies on the roof near the Asset.
A tactical team's on its way.
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE STALLING]
[GROANS]
Nicky?
[GASPING]
BOURNE: Don't move!
[GROANING]
Athens police have entered the building.
Asset, you need to get out of there.
Negative.
We don't even know if Bourne's alive.
You want to lose this guy?
This is Director Dewey.
You have 20 seconds.
Hold on, Nicky.
I'm going to get you to cover.
[WEAKLY] No.
No.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
No, don't.
I'm coming.
[POLICE SPEAKING IN GREEK]
- Get a location on Christian .
- Yes, sir.
DIRECTOR DEWEY: If he was working with
Nicky Parsons, he will lead us to Jason Bourne.
And let me know if you get
a hit on that malware.
Sir, can I clarify one thing?
Yeah.
Does the Asset know Bourne?
Why would you ask me that?
His behavior on the rooftop.
It suggested a connection.
The last time Bourne came back,
he exposed the Blackbriar program.
It compromised active operations.
The Asset was in Syria undercover.
He was captured, tortured,
and it took two damn years to get him out.
So you think that's why
Bourne wants the files?
To go public again?
I have no idea why he came back.
But whatever he's doing,
he wants to destroy us.
We can't let that happen.
So, you give me a call
soon as you hear anything.
Yes, sir.
[WATER RUNNING]
[EXHALES]
[MAN SCREAMING]
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
WOMAN [ON SPEAKER] And now,
the founder and chairman of Deep Dream,
Aaron Kalloor.
[PEOPLE APPLAUDING]
Hi.
Uh...
You all know why we're here.
We're gonna be unveiling a new platform.
We think it is a bold new step
to allow us to serve our community better.
We're a community right now
that is transcending national boundaries.
And I think we're 1.5 billion users.
[AUDIENCE CLAPPING]
In a nutshell, as you know,
we have an ecosystem
of hundreds of thousands
of apps at this point.
And what this new platform will do
will be to integrate users' data
and preferences,
and use that information
to enrich and tailor-make
each unique user experience
in a way that is, frankly, unprecedented.
Um, now, I can see some
journalists' pens twitching,
- ready to ask about privacy.
- MAN Yeah.
This is a concern to many people,
and so it should be.
I mean, this is something that matters to us.
And let me just say, uh,
I understand nobody wants to
feel like they're being watched.
So let me just tell you, when you come
to Deep Dream, when you use our service,
no one will be watching you.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
- MAITRE D': Mr. Kalloor.
- WAITRESS: Right this way, sir.
WAITRESS: Enjoy your meal.
AARON: Thank you.
DIRECTOR DEWEY: Congratulations.
I hear your stockholders
were very happy with that new platform.
And I heard you got hacked.
We're dealing with it.
This changes everything.
There's too much risk.
I'm out.
Aaron,
you are an extraordinarily gifted
and perceptive young man.
When you agreed to help us,
it was because you understood
the very grave threats that...
[MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Do you have any idea of the shit-storm
I'll have on my hands
if this arrangement becomes public?
I already took a hit with Snowden,
and you want more?
Our enemies have become
much more sophisticated.
Gathering metadata is no longer adequate.
We need a back door into your new
platform, and a way past the encryptions.
And when that's not enough,
you'll want something new.
You don't get it, do you?
Privacy is freedom.
Maybe that's something
you should think about defending.
You little prick, you didn't believe
in privacy or freedom
when we funded your startup,
turned you into a billionaire.
I paid you back many, many, many times over.
And I was never comfortable with any of this.
I'm out.
I'm done selling out our customers.
But you would sell out your country.
The truth is, we wouldn't be
having this conversation
if you didn't feel personally at risk.
You talk about a free Internet,
you tell yourself you're saving the world,
but all you're doing is making it
a much more dangerous place.
And you're sure as hell making
this country much more difficult to defend.
And you're sure as hell
accountable for that, Aaron.
Accountable.
[SNIFFLES]
Bourne?
Everything on the table.
[SIGHS]
Open it.
Sure.
[BEEPING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
LEE: [ON PHONE]
Bourne has surfaced. In Berlin.
Get the Berlin team up.
Where is she?
She's dead.
She knew the risks.
I warned her.
She made a choice.
You exploited her.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Berlin team is mobile.
What do we have on the location?
It's an address linked to Christian .
Anything on Bourne?
Nothing yet. I'm accessing CCTV now.
Sir, I've been thinking,
maybe we've got this wrong.
What if he's not coming for us?
What if it's something else?
You don't have any idea
who you're dealing with.
We should work together, Bourne.
You exposed the Blackbriar program.
We're both after the same thing, right?
We both want to take down the corrupt
institutions that control society.
I'm not on your side.
CCTV feed is online.
He's on a computer.
We have to stop this.
If he puts those files online,
operations will be compromised
and people will die.
Yes, sir.
At least when you're done,
leave me the files.
These programs have to be exposed.
People have a right to know.
We need that computer.
There's a phone in the room.
I can use it to delete the files.
- Got the phone.
- Where's that team?
JEFFERS Five minutes out, sir.
MAN We're running out of time. Get there.
RICHARD Listen to me, David.
I've done something.
Something...
...that came at a cost.
One day you'll understand why.
I gotta get back to Washington.
I love you, son.
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
They're fighting, sir.
One more firewall.
Files deleted, sir.
DIRECTOR DEWEY: Call in.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[CELL PHONE CONTINUES RINGING]
LEE: Bourne, my name is Heather Lee.
I'm not in charge here.
I wasn't here when you went missing.
I can see you're going through
the old Treadstone files.
Retracing your history.
I know you're looking for something.
Let me help you find it.
Give me that phone.
Yes, sir.
Jason, this is Robert Dewey.
Do you remember me?
Jason, your dad was a patriot.
He could see the threats
that America was facing,
and, like you, he chose to serve his country
out of a profound sense of duty.
He would not want to
see you harm the Agency.
You have to stop this.
And you have to stop it now.
Sir, our ETA is...
[CELL PHONE VIBRATES]
WOMAN He's on the move. Be ready.
MAN1 Take point!
On me!
MAN2 The elevator.
We lost him, sir.
Malcolm Smith, contract only,
based out of London.
Ran all of Treadstone's surveillance
in the late '90s,
when Bourne was recruited.
RUSSELL Is he still active?
JEFFERS He's private security now.
DEWEY: Contact the Asset and tell him I want
him on the ground in London in six hours.
I think that could be a mistake, sir.
A mistake? Why?
There is an argument for catching Bourne
instead of killing him.
All right, let's hear it.
Bourne's been off the grid for a long time.
He's been hiding in the shadows,
he's seen things.
He knows things that could help us.
Bringing him back in is the smart move.
And how are we going to do that?
Albert Hirsch wrote a psych evaluation
when Bourne left the program.
He concluded Bourne
is still a patriot at heart,
and that leaving the program
could come back to haunt him.
And what are you suggesting?
I watched Bourne with those files.
Desperately looking into his past.
And I think he's at a tipping point.
If I could get face-to-face with him,
I think I can bring him back in.
One attempt.
And if it fails,
you do what you have to.
Well, it makes sense to me.
What do you think, Bob?
Let's give it a shot.
All right, do it.
Bring Bourne in, or tie it off.
But this ends now.
LEE: Thank you, sir.
Sir, I'm sorry...
No, don't worry about that.
Better get some sleep, kid. [CHUCKLES]
You got a long 24 hours ahead of you.
Yes, sir.
AARON: It's taking too long. It shouldn't
still be buggy this close to launch.
Well, I don't think it's buggy.
I think we've changed some things
that's going to change the parameters.
We're going to have to go and...
Okay, we need to change them back.
Amanda, can we get that note over to Kyle?
- Absolutely.
- Look, I think you're right,
- I just don't think we want to...
- I'm tired of waiting.
Mr. Kalloor.
What the hell is this?
Mr. Kalloor, my name is John Burroughs.
I'm from the Department of Justice.
I'm hereby serving you
with the enclosed complaint...
- Really? We have to do this in public?
- Issued by the US government
against Deep Dream Corporation
for violation of the Sherman Act.
This complaint requires you to preserve all
personal and corporate financial records
pending antitrust motions
to be filed in federal court.
Good day.
[CAR ENGINE TURNS ON]
- This is Dewey.
- Aaron, it's a message.
And maybe we should think about
what we're doing before it gets any worse.
So, you think if we give him
what he wants, it'll end there?
You know, I'm just saying
that maybe we should listen.
I want you to pull up all the records
of all the meetings I've ever had with Dewey.
All the records?
Even the off-the-books discussions?
Especially those.
We're going to Vegas.
I need an insurance policy.
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
[MAN SCREAMING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yeah.
DIRECTOR DEWEY: Are you in London?
ASSET: Yes.
Why are you sending her?
She serves a purpose.
I work alone.
Not this time.
Don't make this personal.
Bourne betrayed us.
It's always been personal.
You know who you're dealing with.
You better make sure you're ready.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yeah.
BAUMAN There's something
you should know about Deep Dream.
But I need an assurance
that I have your support.
You got it. What do you have?
Kalloor is planning something for Vegas.
[RINGING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Yes?
This is Jason Bourne.
I need to talk.
What about?
I don't work for the Agency anymore.
Paddington Plaza, 15 minutes.
[SIGHS]
Bourne just called Smith.
They're meeting at Paddington Plaza.
15 minutes.
We'll tail Smith the whole way.
As soon as we get eyes on Bourne,
I'll approach him.
Whatever you do, stay contained.
I don't want the Brits crawling all over us,
asking questions.
Understood.
Tracking device.
You'll hold on the south side of the bridge.
I'll contact you if I need you.
Sure.
You're the boss, right?
- [ELEVATOR DINGS]
- [EXHALES]
Subject is on the move.
Heading toward the canal.
Alpha Team, take a parallel track.
Bravo Team, follow the subject from behind.
And keep your eyes open for Bourne.
Bravo Team tailing subject.
Let's go.
In 200 meters, make a right.
AGENT: Copy that.
Comms check. Second channel. Do you copy?
I have you. Where are you now?
Heading towards Smith.
No sign of Bourne.
Subject has turned east, into an alley.
Alpha Team, that alley leads to
a footbridge, which will bring him to you.
Copy that.
[SILENCED GUN FIRING]
Bravo Team is down.
Sending you updated route now.
You copy that, Smith?
Yes.
Bravo Team, why aren't you moving?
What's going on?
Bravo Team, do you copy?
What's happening, Heather? Where's Bravo?
We're comms down on Bravo.
Alpha Team, do you have
eyes on the subject?
We have eyes on.
- [SILENCED GUN FIRING]
- [GRUNTS]
Alpha Team, sit-rep.
Alpha Team, report.
What's happening, Heather?
Alpha Team isn't responding.
Bravo?
Still nothing.
You lost both teams?
Get a grip on this operation, Heather.
That's Bourne.
Green-light the Asset.
Sir, I need more time.
We have no time.
Are you going to give that order or not?
Sir, please.
You are too naive to see the truth.
There's no bringing in Bourne.
He has to be put down, and you obviously
cannot do what has to be done.
I am taking operational control.
Asset, you have a green light.
Repeat, you have a green light on Bourne.
Copy that.
I'm on my way.
Asset, are you on the move?
Asset, your tracking device
says you're stationary.
Are you moving?
Heather, stay off this channel.
Let him do his job.
Left here.
- Get to Paddington Plaza, fast.
- AGENT: Copy that.
In position.
Locked in.
[RINGING]
[ALARM BLARING]
- [RINGING]
- [CRACKLING]
[ALARM BLARING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
What's going on?
What's that noise?
Multiple fire alarms.
That's Bourne.
What do I do?
You stay there. You do not move.
MAN [OVER SPEAKER] Leave the building
by the nearest available exit.
I can't stay here.
You can't protect me.
I need you to stay where you are, Smith.
You still have line of sight?
I'm on him.
You're gonna shoot him in a crowd
when he's right next to me?
Stay where you are, Smith.
You know why he's here.
He wants answers.
You've lost this thing.
I gotta get out of here.
Shit!
What the hell is going on?
Bourne's got Smith.
Go after them.
I'll come around and cut them off.
Smith, we know you're with Bourne.
You have to find a way
to let us know where you are.
Why are you taking me in here?
They've got to be near the Plaza.
[POLICE SIRENS WAILING]
SMITH: Jesus, Bourne!
[GRUNTS] God damn it!
What are you doing? Take it easy.
Richard Webb.
Station Chief, Beirut.
He was my father. He started Treadstone.
He hired you to put me
under surveillance. Why?
- Jesus!
- Why did he hire you?
Don't say anything, Smith.
No. No.
- [GUNSHOT FIRES]
- [GRUNTS]
There's no sign of them.
What do you want us to do?
Work your way down the canal.
I'll circle around and meet you there.
[GRUNTS]
You followed me to Beirut.
The last time I saw my father!
Why would he have you follow me?
It doesn't make any sense. Why?
Don't give him a goddamn thing.
Why?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS]
Jesus Christ, Bourne! I'm falling!
Bourne, please!
I can hear them!
Beirut.
I went there to tell him
that Treadstone had approached me.
But if it was his program,
why didn't he say anything to me?
I've done something.
Something...
...that came at a cost.
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
That was the day he was killed.
They said he was killed by terrorists.
He wasn't killed by terrorists, was he?
Think about your family's safety, Smith.
You keep your mouth shut.
The next bullet's in your head!
Why was he killed?
Why?
He was killed because of you.
Your father, he wasn't in Operations.
He didn't know we'd chosen you.
When he found out, he...
He threatened to expose the program.
He didn't want you turned into a killer.
Who killed him?
[MAN SCREAMING]
Don't do it.
Where is he?
He's almost there.
We're gonna stop this now.
No, please.
- [SILENCED GUN FIRES]
- [GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS]
[PEOPLE EXCLAIM]
MAN Somebody help! Call an ambulance!
WOMAN Someone help!
ASSET: He went off the roof. Five floors.
He recognized me.
I'm going to make sure it's finished.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
MAN Help's coming now.
No, don't get up, mate.
Step aside, please. Step aside.
POLICEWOMAN Everybody step back.
- POLICEMAN:: Let us do our job.
- POLICEWOMAN Please step back.
Did anybody see what happened?
He's gone.
- Oh, shit.
- I'm going after him.
I'll work my way down the canal.
No. You're done in London.
What are you talking about?
There's another play to be made.
Now that he knows what we did,
he'll come for both of us,
and that could be the opportunity
for something else.
This isn't about revenge.
ASSET: Yes, it is.
And it won't be done until one of us is dead.
DIRECTOR DEWEY: Get to the airport.
We have a problem with Iron Hand.
Copy that.
Give me a sit-rep.
AGENT: We've got nothing.
Keep looking.
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- [GRUNTS]
Drive.
It wasn't supposed to go like this.
I wanted to talk.
Where's Dewey going?
He's going to Vegas to speak
with Aaron Kalloor at a cyber convention.
The Agency recruits there every year.
What's Iron Hand?
Dewey's new black-ops program.
Full-spectrum surveillance.
Watching everyone all the time.
Dewey needs Kalloor's cooperation
to bring it online.
Let me out.
I can help you get there.
Why would you do that?
You and I have different reasons,
but we both want Dewey gone.
Here, take this.
I'll see you in Vegas.
Sir.
JEFFERS We're pinning Kalloor's hit
on a fictional jihadi shooter.
A 20-year-old Iraqi national.
We created bank accounts,
travel documents, e-mails, phone records.
He'll look like a lone wolf.
Any physical evidence?
The Asset leaves the gun.
It'll have the Iraqi's prints on it.
Russell doesn't need to know about this.
I understand, sir.
Any news on Bourne?
Nothing.
He was always gonna come for me.
Well, if it happens, we'll deal with it.
[BEEPS]
What was the purpose of your visit
to London, Mr. Michaels?
Business.
OFFICER: Welcome home, sir.
Thank you.
MAN Parking lot clear. You're good to go.
Sir, we have a secure room for you,
right upstairs.
- Enjoy your stay.
- Thank you.
Hi, welcome to the Aria.
- Heather Lee, checking in.
- Okay.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
We have you in a lovely Sky Suite.
Number 2016.
Enjoy your stay.
Thank you.
[PEOPLE CHEERING]
MAN1: Aaron!
MAN2: All right, Aaron!
MAN3: Deep Dream!
[SIGHS]
Find Lee.
Tell her I want to see her
before we go on stage.
Yes, sir.
I want agents posted backstage
as well as the auditorium.
Yes, sir.
GUARD1: Coming through, make a hole.
Make a hole, make a hole.
AARON: Gonna make a quick stop here.
Hey, guys. Hi. How's it going? Aaron.
Good to meet you.
Can I get one?
Thanks very much for your hard work.
Thank you.
BAUMAN You're doing a great job.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
Yeah.
You all set?
Checking the departure route now.
You won't have much time.
They won't know where it came from.
I'll have enough time.
After you take care of Kalloor,
I'll be standing, left hand at my side.
You put a bullet in it.
It's better if I'm a target, too.
Copy that.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
Lee.
The Director wants a word
before you go on stage.
Of course.
ID?
Thanks.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
[SIGHS]
Ah.
Heather.
My protge. Strongest supporter.
You know, after what happened in London,
I did not know what to do with you.
I suppose we'll just, um,
write it off to your learning curve.
I'd appreciate that.
DIRECTOR DEWEY: At least you can
now see that you never had a chance.
When Bourne turns up again,
I'll deal with him.
Do you understand?
Of course.
I agree completely.
When we get on stage,
I'll handle all the policy questions,
throw everything technical to you.
I'll be ready, sir.
Okay, let's do this.
GUARD: Badges?
Aaron.
Robert.
DIRECTOR DEWEY: You know Heather Lee.
Yeah, we went to Stanford together.
Wow. How are you enjoying
life at the Agency?
Challenging. But fulfilling.
It's tough to stay true
to your principles over there?
My principles are just fine, thanks.
ORGANIZER: Gentlemen, we're ready for you.
Follow me, please.
I'm going to enjoy this.
So am I.
Thank you, sir.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
Oh! Hi! How's everybody doing tonight?
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
BRADLEY: Welcome.
Welcome.
Welcome to tonight's EXOCON Symposium.
We are so lucky to have
four fantastic guests this evening.
The CIA Director, Robert Dewey, is here.
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
And a dear friend of mine,
and an old friend of EXOCON,
the CEO of social-media giant Deep Dream,
Aaron Kalloor is here.
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
[GRUNTS]
Tonight, "Policing a free Internet,
"personal rights versus public safety."
This is the great question of our time.
And the choices we make about this
will determine our future.
So let's just dive right in, okay?
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
Come on out here, guys.
Sir, you've got an incoming message.
High priority.
All right, guys, I'm gonna have to take this.
I'll catch up with you later.
Go ahead.
[CROWD CONTINUES APPLAUDING]
Thanks for having me. Hey.
BRADLEY: It appears Director Dewey
is held up momentarily,
and I am being told
that it shouldn't be too much longer.
But we have a ton of stuff
to get into tonight,
- so we can start anyway...
- Brad? Brad, could I say a few words?
- Excuse me?
- Can I get the ball rolling?
Oh, sure, man, by all means.
Ladies and gentlemen, Aaron Kalloor.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
Thank you. Thanks a lot.
Thanks a lot to Brad
and all the folks at EXOCON
for having us back,
and to you guys for turning out.
Before the Director comes out to join us,
I just wanted to share
a few words with you guys.
A long time ago, I had this idea.
- Copy that.
- A beautiful idea, to create a place, online...
Facial recognition got a hit.
Bourne was on a BA flight
from Heathrow to Vegas.
It landed two hours ago.
How the hell did he get through immigration?
Someone issued him an Agency
security clearance on his passport.
[SIGHS]
AARON: Well, it turned out
to be a pretty popular idea.
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
- AARON: Um...
People from around the world
started using our service.
[VIBRATING]
AARON: Well, first off, this has all made me
a lot more rich than is probably healthy.
When I come on stage,
take care of Kalloor and the girl.
Copy.
AARON:
But, what I mean to say is that, you know,
all this success has come at a cost.
There is a cancer at the heart of Deep Dream.
- A guilty secret, and, um...
- [AUDIENCE MUTTERING]
I have to share it with all of you guys.
Son of a bitch is about to take us down.
Take out Kalloor and the girl right now.
[COCKS GUN]
MAN Whoa, whoa...
- Stay there.
- Okay.
AARON: When I was starting out, I, uh...
I took money to start my company.
Made a bargain with a guy in a dark suit...
...and now he's come back to take my soul.
[GRUNTS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOTS FIRING]
AGENT VASQUEZ: I see the shooter!
We've got eyes on Jason Bourne.
BAUMAN
He's still breathing. Call an ambulance!
AGENT1: Go, go!
- AGENT2: Let's go!
- Sir, we gotta go.
[SCREAMING]
AGENT3: Head for the exit!
This is Vasquez. We're on Bourne.
Get the cars ready!
Get the cars ready right now!
No, take me to the suite.
Sir, we've got to get you out of here.
Bourne is on the loose.
You heard me. Take me to the suite.
Yes, sir.
Take him to the suite. Take him upstairs.
Get him upstairs.
Right now. Right now.
Up to the suite.
- Let's go, right now. Go, go, go!
- Yes, sir.
AGENT3: Come this way.
This way. Don't worry. Come on.
Out of the way! Federal agent!
[GRUNTING]
Vasquez, sit-rep.
Vasquez, come in!
Hey!
[CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
Okay, we've got him. Sir, this is Collier.
- We've ID'd the sniper.
- Shit.
We're circulating his photo now.
What about Bourne?
Hang on.
Okay, Bourne is just leaving the west
service corridor, heading for the lobby.
Copy that. Stay on Bourne.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
What?
JEFFERS We're still looking for Bourne.
And they've ID'd the Asset.
Go back to the first floor
and wait for further instructions.
- Yes, sir. Copy that.
- Copy that.
[MACHINE BEEPING]
- Everybody down! Right now!
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Down, move, move, move!
Out of the way! Federal agents! Move!
[GROANS]
[ELEVATOR DINGING]
Take a team to the northeast elevators.
I'll meet you up there.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Bourne's on his way up to you.
[PANTING]
[GUNSHOT FIRES]
You took a long time to get here, Jason.
I know about Beirut.
I know what you did.
It all ends tonight.
Be a lot easier to do it right away.
[CHUCKLES]
You didn't come here for revenge.
You came here because
you know it's time to come in.
Your father created the program.
Didn't have what it takes to make it work.
And you did.
You always did.
That's why you volunteered.
I volunteered because
I thought our enemies killed him.
I volunteered because of a lie.
No, you volunteered because of who you are.
You volunteered because
you are Jason Bourne,
and not David Webb.
Thirty-two kills, Jason.
Every one of them made a difference.
People all across this country
are safer because of what you did.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I'm trying to find another way.
[CHUCKLES]
And how's that working out for you?
[PANTING]
You're never going to find any peace.
Not until you admit to yourself
who you really are.
It's time to come in, Jason.
It's time to come in.
I can't.
Not for you.
[COCKS GUN]
[DOOR OPENS]
[BOTH GRUNT]
- [GUN FIRES]
- [GRUNTS]
You were never here.
You don't have to go after him.
This can stop now.
You have a choice.
[ALARM RINGING]
- OFFICER1: Let's go!
- OFFICER2: Have your IDs ready.
Have your IDs ready, ladies and gentlemen.
OFFICER3: Have your IDs ready!
Come on, guys, let's go, let's go!
Stand in a line.
Las Vegas Police, ladies and gentlemen!
[SIRENS WAILING]
[ENGINE TURNS ON]
FEMALE DISPATCHER: BearCat SWAT truck
and unmarked black Dodge Charger
stolen from the front of the Aria.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Pursuit in progress. Air support requested.
MAN What was that ID?
[SIRENS WAILING]
[CARS HONKING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[SIREN WAILING]
[ENGINE REVS]
[STRAINS]
[METAL CLATTERS]
[INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
[INDISTINCT TALKING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
POLICEMAN:: Stop him! Block that road!
Oh, my God!
Fire!
[GUNSHOTS]
Move out!
[PEOPLE CLAMORING AND SCREAMING]
[PANICKED SCREAMING AND CLAMORING]
Move!
OFFICER: [OVER RADIO]
Next two units involved, identify.
OFFICER: [ON HELICOPTER RADIO]
This is Air 1. Be advised, suspect vehicles
have crashed into
the southeast entrance of the Riviera.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
[STRUGGLING]
DISPATCH: We have an armed suspect
heading into the storm drain south of Riviera.
[PANTING]
[CAN CLATTERS]
[GRUNTS]
[STRAINING]
[BOTH STRAINING]
Aah!
[STRAINING]
[CHOKING]
You're a traitor.
You've always been a traitor.
It's in your blood.
[CHOKING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[COUGHS]
[SIRENS WAILING IN THE DISTANCE]
[SIRENS WAILING]
REPORTER1: Mr. Kalloor!
[REPORTERS CLAMORING]
REPORTER2: Aaron! What were you
going to tell everyone at the convention?
REPORTER1: What are you hiding, Aaron?
Easy.
REPORTER3:
Why did somebody try to assassinate you?
REPORTER2: What's the cancer
at the heart of Deep Dream?
I think it would be inappropriate
to pass any comment at this stage,
but I look forward to
working with the authorities
to find out who was responsible.
And to getting back to Deep Dream,
where we can continue
our important work. Thank you.
REPORTER1:
Have you been lying to your users?
Sir.
[EXHALES]
I wanted to say I'm sorry, sir.
About Vegas.
Director Dewey's tactics were unwise.
Unwise?
We're still trying to come up with
a narrative to explain what happened.
That son of a bitch put
a spotlight on Iron Hand.
On all of us.
Kalloor hasn't gone public yet.
I know Aaron.
There are still moves we can make with him.
Tell me.
Dewey's problem was
that he belonged in the past.
People like Kalloor are shaping the future.
These are my people.
I know how to deal with him.
And what do you want?
When you appoint a new Agency Director,
you're going to need someone
working for your interests.
Someone
empowered by you.
What about Bourne?
You still think you can bring him in?
I have his trust.
After what we went through.
I'll bring him in.
I'm certain of it.
And if you can't?
Then he'll have to be put down.
It's an interesting proposal.
You can pull over here.
Of course, if you decide that you
don't need me, then that's not a problem.
There are many other agencies
who would want what I know.
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- [ENGINE REVS]
LEE: I brought you something.
It's a cast from your father's star,
on the Memorial Wall at Langley.
I'm sorry for what happened to you.
How you were treated.
But the people that did that are gone,
and things are changing at the Agency.
What is it you want?
I know you've always been a patriot.
That what happens to this country
matters to you.
We need you to help protect us.
Come back in.
And we'll work together.
Let me think about it.
How will I find you?
RUSSELL
You still think you can bring him in?
LEE: I have his trust.
After what we went through.
I'll bring him in.
I'm certain of it.
RUSSELL And if you can't?
[CAR HORN HONKS]
LEE: Then he'll have to be put down.