Oh, boy. Lots to catch up on.
We'll start with the basics.
Jane was accidentally
artificially inseminated
with Rafael's sample.
Oh, and the doctor who inseminated her?
Well, that was his sister, Luisa.
They'd fall in love.
But happily ever after?
Not by a long shot.
For one, Jane's ex-fiancé Michael
is a detective, and he's
made a shocking discovery.
Rafael told us the bellboy's last words
were "Sin Rostro"
he wasn't naming his killer,
he was identifying her.
Rafael's stepmother, Rose, is Sin Rostro,
the big, bad criminal he's been after.
Oh...
And she killed his father.
But Rafael doesn't know that... yet.
Meanwhile, Luisa was sleeping with Rose.
We still have to tell my father
- what happened between us.
- What?
My shaman thinks it's really important
for me to just come clean.
So Rose had her committed.
You're having some sort of episode.
- Fantasizing...
- Stop lying!
Oh, and even more scandalous,
remember Roman Zazo, who was impaled?
Did everything go okay?
Yeah.
So let's see what the
hell is going on, shall we?
Great.
There's an old Woody Allen quote:
"If you want to make God laugh,
tell him about your plans."
And though I have complicated feelings
about Woody Allen, post Soon-Yi,
it's still a very wise quote.
Okay, I made a decision.
- _
- Ready?
- Lista.
- We're ready.
I'm going to go to the
University of Miami.
Wow.
I thought you were leaning towards Iowa.
- _
- Yeah, well, I weighed everything
and Miami makes the most sense.
I can write on the side while
I'm getting my teaching degree,
plus if I live at home,
then I'll save money,
which will put me a little
ahead on my five-year plan.
- _
- You don't even have a plan.
- Well, that's not true, dad.
I plan to go to Bora Bora next week.
Bora Bora? When are you going
to get your life together?
Look at your sister.
Even she is on the right path.
No, thank you.
I'm newly sober and they say alcoholics
either end up in rehab, in jail or dead.
I chose rehab.
There is no need to give them
every single detail, Luisa.
In any case, you need a job.
No, I really don't.
Oh, yeah, I'm definitely
working while I'm in college.
I mean, it may take a little longer,
but I don't want to graduate with debt.
- Then I'm going to cut you off.
- That's ridiculous.
You're lazy. You're unmotivated.
By 30, I see myself tenured at a school,
my first novel about to be published...
_
Definitely married but no kids yet.
I want my life set up first.
You've done nothing with your life.
You've accomplished nothing.
Can I just say
how proud I am of you, honey?
You are such a disappointment.
- Thanks, dad.
- Thanks, mom.
- It means a lot.
- _
- Wow.
Babies need a lot of gear.
No, they don't. It's
all marketing, all right?
They act like you need all this
stuff, when really, you just...
Oh, my God, do you see?
That little snowsuit
with the little ears.
We live in Miami.
I'm not gonna register for it.
I was just saying that it was cute.
Hey, tell me about the shower.
Do I get to come in and
make, like, a grand entrance
and play cutesy games or whatever?
I don't do games. You know
what, I don't even know
what half of these things are.
And the other half, I'm
not registering for them
- until I read a review.
- You read reviews?
I read multiple reviews.
And I review.
Of course you do.
Okay, come on.
Let's look at something we know we need.
- Cribs.
- Cribs, okay. Cribs are cute.
- Yes. Just definitely not that one.
- Oh, I love that one.
Really?
What's wrong with this one?
J... it... the bars...
It's just so prison-like.
But they all have bars.
Well, then, I want the Orange
is the New Black version.
A friendly prison,
where one has a chance
to explore their identity.
Although, we could just get 'em both.
One for your place, one for mine.
And just like that,
a terrifying thought
- occurred to them both.
- _
Well, maybe not
terrifying, but expensive.
I got it.
Ah, yes, Michael.
Hi.
You'll recall that, up until recently,
Michael had plans of his own.
What's going on?
Did you find my father?
No.
But I do need to talk to you.
About... Sin Rostro.
_
Should I leave, or...
Depends how much you want her to hear.
Everything.
Anything.
Stay.
Sin Rostro is your stepmother, Rose.
- _
- Wow.
Um...
Let's... let's sit down.
So how do you know that it's Rose?
Are you sure?
I don't want to interrupt,
but I do think it's important
that you know what Jane's thinking.
- _
- All the evidence leads to her.
She's been running an underground
- plastic surgery ring.
- _
She's been surgically changing
the faces of criminals.
_
We have reason to believe she may have
- altered her own face.
- _
- If Rose altered her own face,
she could look entirely different.
She could be... Anyone.
At least you know my
father's not involved.
I don't know that at all.
Sin Rostro had a network of associates,
and your father could
have been one of them.
What are you implying?
I'm implying exactly what
you know I'm implying.
Rose didn't kill Roman Zazo
and your father is still at large.
So if he contacts you, you let us know.
You, too, Jane.
- Jane?
- Huh?
Sorry.
Can you repeat the question?
- Synced and corrected by ChrisKe -
- www.addic7ed.com -
I'm gonna need to talk
to your sister, too.
How can I reach her?
She's at Haven View Psychiatric Hospital.
What's she doing there?
Um... she had a breakdown.
Claimed she was having
an affair with Rose.
You mean Sin Rostro.
Oh, my God, Rafael...
I-I gotta get her out of there.
All right, Betty...
I'm breaking out of here.
Poor Luisa.
Always one crucial step behind.
I am. I've had it.
No phone privileges, are you kidding me?
Just because of one little incident?
This is an emergency.
I need you to go to the Marbella hotel.
I think my father might
be a criminal mastermind
and I'm worried that my stepmother
is in imminent danger.
Yes, I am calling
from the Haven View Psychiatric Hospital.
This is the key to my escape.
Don't tell anyone, Betty.
- _
- I have to get out of here.
As long as Rose is
with my father, she's...
She's in danger.
Look, I know what you're going to say.
Why am I trying to help
Rose, after what she did?
Putting me in here...
I should hate her for that.
I do hate her for that.
Yeah, I know.
I don't believe me either.
Wait, so his stepmother's
like a real-life criminal mastermind?
- Yes.
- Wow.
That's like straight
out of La Reina del Sur.
- Right?
- Like when Teresa Mendoza turns into
this huge drug queen and
she ends up killing Teo...
Exactly, that's exactly
what I was thinking!
But I couldn't tell Rafael that.
So what did you say?
Oh, something about
I'm sure his father will turn up.
So you think he knows
where his father is?
- What? No...
- It's not out of the question.
You'd hide me if I were a criminal.
- No, I wouldn't.
- I'd hide you if you were a criminal.
That's because I wouldn't
do something that bad.
And you think I would?
Example "A," you have a temper.
Oh, hello.
Please, don't let my mood
interrupt your good times.
Hey, Rogelio.
Dad.
You're locked into "dad" now.
Dad. Got it.
I wanted to talk to you both
about my job offer in Mexico.
I am being pressured by
my publicist to take it.
So... you're leaving for Mexico?
I don't know.
I-I also got a job offer...
here.
To play the second lead
in Esteban's Telenovela.
_
Their ratings need a boost.
Normally, I would never
consider it, but...
Well, we've just connected.
And I don't want to lose that.
We won't.
Look, I selfishly want you to stay.
But... if you want to
go for your career...
I get it.
Anyway, I'm tired, so
I'm gonna go to bed.
I'll leave you guys to talk.
- Night, hon.
- Mm-hmm.
- Good night.
- Night.
So, what are you going to do?
I'm not sure.
What do you think I should do?
Here's what he hoped she would say:
Stay here. With me.
And... here's what she said:
You should do whatever makes you happy.
What would make you happy?
Here's what she hoped he would say:
You, Xiomara.
And... here's what he said:
Neither option is perfect.
Take everything up to
the presidential suite.
I'll be staying there for a while.
Mrs. Solano...
Mrs. Solano, wait.
The thing is...
- Mr. Solano, well...
- _
He's banned you from the hotel, ma'am.
Hmm. Did he?
And what is your name?
Gabriel.
Excellent.
Gabriel, can you tell
me exactly what he said?
Great, as long as he got the money,
I want out of this whole mess.
And clearly, use discretion
when wiring the last of it
so nothing can be traced.
So you think he knows
where his father is?
Just let me know if anything changes.
Yeah. So we're all good.
All right. Bye-bye.
Hey.
Hey...
What was that all about?
Uh, Luisa.
I have to get her out of the hospital,
but I need the power of attorney.
This was absolutely true.
_
- _
- I have to make another call
about it, actually.
Yeah. I have to get to work.
Yeah, uh, we have a meeting, so...
- Okay.
- I'll see you.
- Mm-hmm.
Hello, Jane.
Oh, hi.
I thought you left.
Oh, I did.
But I'm back.
What are you doing here, Petra?
I banned you from this hotel.
Hmm, yes, I know.
The manager, uh...
Gabriel was his name, right?
Yeah, anyway, he told me.
Then I fired him.
Consider it my first act
as co-owner of the Marbella.
What?
Oh, didn't you know?
Yes, well...
The company that bought into
the hotel, Stanwyk Investments...
It's a family company.
My old boyfriend's family.
And, well, he bought it for me.
So we need to talk
about some changes, hmm?
The hotel's reputation has taken a hit.
And I believe that the first step
towards changing public perception is
to distance ourselves
from the Solano name.
Meaning, stripping you from
your day-to-day responsibilities.
What are you talking about, Petra?
I believe the term is "silent partner."
Shh...
This man, Emilio Solano,
is potentially armed and dangerous.
If anyone sees or hears anything...
So listen, we need to have a
meeting asap about your shower.
Okay, don't make a big thing about it.
I'm gonna make a big thing about it.
That's it.
Just keep your eyes open.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about that.
Jane, I meant it before.
Emilio might try to reach out to his son,
and if he does, we need to know.
Great, as long as he got the money,
I want out of this mess.
What is it?
- Nothing.
- Jane.
This isn't about Rafael
or you or me, okay?
It's about this.
Ugh.
Roman Zazo was murdered.
And his killer is still out there.
So be careful, okay?
It should be noted that Jane's
first thought was Rafael.
She really needed to talk to him.
- _
- But then this happened.
No one knows you're here, okay?
- _
- Get some rest.
Okay, that absolutely did
not mean he was hiding Emilio.
And it's certainly not
like Jane should get
the master key and break in.
That would be ridiculous.
And dangerous.
She should definitely leave.
Right now.
But there's no harm in knocking, right?
Did you forget something?
Jane.
Michael, hi.
A-are you okay? What's wrong?
Nothing.
You always look away
when you're not telling the truth.
I just was... I was looking for Rafael.
And you look scared.
Is this about his father, about the case?
Jane.
Roman Zazo's murderer is on the loose.
But I just saw him.
Hi, Michael.
Hi, Jane.
Hi.
What the hell is going on?
I'm Aaron Zazo.
- Aaron?
- Yeah.
I'm Roman's twin brother.
I'm so sorry I scared you.
I figured you were someone
who knew my brother,
but I didn't know who you were.
Oh, yeah, no big deal.
I used to have sisters that are twins.
One of them has a bigger
dimple, I think, maybe.
Look, start at the beginning.
What is going on?
After Zaz died, I knew I
had to find his brother.
But they hadn't spoken in years,
and I didn't know where to start.
So I hired a private investigator,
and eventually I tracked
Aaron down to an orphanage
in Mexico where he volunteered.
But he had just been
kidnapped by a cartel.
It happens down there.
- They grab you, demand cash.
- I negotiated
- with the cartel.
- I owe this man my life.
He's one of the good guys, Jane.
Why didn't you tell me any of this?
Because the kidnappers demanded secrecy.
They said they were gonna kill him.
I need to talk to you about your brother.
Absolutely. Satya.
It means, "all in pursuit of truth."
It's a part of my religion.
I'm a Jain.
_
I just want to know what
happened to my brother.
I'm sorry.
L-look, I...
I was looking for you.
But I ran into Michael instead.
I tried not to say anything,
- but he just, he knows me so well.
- God.
And I was scared.
I thought that I just saw a dead man.
And what were you doing even knocking
on the door in the first place, huh?
I saw you come out,
and you put a "do not disturb" sign on,
and you had that weird call earlier,
and I just...
I thought that maybe
your father was in there.
- What?
- But I didn't really think that.
I just...
I couldn't rule it out a hundred percent.
Because you don't trust me.
No, I do.
Really?
'Cause it doesn't feel like it.
Can we just talk about this later?
I have to get my sister out
of the mental institution.
All right, this is
how I'm gonna bust out.
You know Dan, the hot delivery guy?
Yeah, I know, I don't see
why everyone thinks he's so hot.
- He's so basic.
- Anyway,
every other Friday,
Dan delivers supplies to our floor.
And Nurse Chelsea...
- _
- I know, she's so tragic,
she just reeks of desperation.
Anyway, she's always flirting with Dan.
So all I have to do is sneak by them
while Chelsea's distracted.
And then I can use Rose's brooch
to pick the lock by the back door
and voilà... I'm free.
Luisa?
Hey,
you.
What are you doing here?
I finally got power of attorney.
I'm here to sign you out.
Great.
Let's go back in this way.
It's a shortcut.
Ah...
We're all responsible
for our own baggage.
At least that's what I
learned in the mental hospital.
- Luisa?
- What?
Look, I don't know what
made you change your mind
and decide to sign me out,
- but I cannot believe that...
- Rose is Sin Rostro.
Come again?
Rose, our stepmother...
Is Sin Rostro.
Sin Rostro,
like, that crazy big drug-dealer person?
Yeah, except she got out of drugs
and now runs a plastic surgery ring
that apparently changes criminals' faces.
You don't say.
Wow.
Sin Rostro, like, killed people, right?
Only those who really deserved it.
Lu, I am so sorry.
And I believe you now.
That's good, that's great.
Okay.
I ran everything by your grandmother,
and we both agreed that this
will be a dry baby shower.
Apparently, we feel
very strongly about this.
It's really sweet what
you're doing for me, Lina.
Are you kidding?
Your best friend throws
you your baby shower,
- that's the rule.
- I know,
but, you know, it's been
kind of weird with us.
Since the whole Frankie thing.
Yeah, I know.
And I missed you.
So...
I missed you, too.
Okay, we'll hug it out later,
but we have things to accomplish here.
Okay, did you finish
your target registry?
- No.
- Jane.
It's complicated.
I mean, where are we gonna even live?
Do we get two of everything
or one of everything?
Hmm, I didn't think about that.
Okay, we'll just say "cash."
next up... Party game.
- Oh, God, I hate party games.
- I know you don't like party games.
You'll just fill this
out about each other.
Where did you meet?
That'll be funny.
Um, what's your favorite song?
Oh, and, um, this is a good one...
Which one of you will
be the disciplinarian?
Luisa, there is so much I
want to say to you but can't.
So let me say this.
I'm sorry that you were
hurt during all of this.
And I know you have so many questions,
so I want to answer one.
Unfortunately, your father is
where the lightning first struck,
where there were fireworks.
Sounds like gibberish to me,
but clearly it meant something to Luisa.
Look, you were right.
I shouldn't have knocked on that door,
and I should have
trusted you enough to wait
and ask you what was going on.
But, I mean, can you blame me, really?
I mean, with everything
that's going on...
I mean, the murders and twins
and mastermind criminals,
this is not normal stuff.
It's pretty friggin' crazy.
Yeah, you're right.
But even with all that, I
thought that you trusted me.
And I do.
For the most part.
Ah, yeah, see, "for the most part"...
Doesn't feel great.
Yeah, but how can it be
anything more than that?
I mea... I mean, I don't even
know what your favorite song is.
What?
Nothing, oh, it's just
this silly question
on a baby shower game.
The-the point is, is that
I didn't know any of the answers.
And that's because we just
met. And I know it doesn't
feel that way because of everything
we've been dealing
with, but it's the truth.
We did just meet. And trust takes time.
And you could have told me about Aaron,
but you didn't. No, and I know now...
That that was a matter of his safety,
but I wasn't gonna say anything.
That's fair.
We'll get there.
Yeah, we will.
"Livin' on a Prayer"
that's your favorite song?
Really?
Bon Jovi?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, no, no.
Hold on.
Hello.
Luisa?
Are you okay?
Hmm, not great.
Luisa, what are you doing out here?
Rose...
Sin Rostro, I found this letter from her.
Read the last sentence.
I don't know when she left it.
It might've been when she came to visit.
"Your father is where the
lightning first struck.
There were fireworks."
What does that mean?
We made love for the
first time in a pool.
Rafael,
I'm pretty sure right now I'm...
I'm sitting on dad.
You know that feeling when
you've been up all night
waiting to find out if
your boyfriend's father
was dug out of a reflecting pool?
Sure you don't want to eat anything?
No, no, no, I'm fine.
Well, that's how Jane's feeling.
Hello.
This is he.
Okay, thank you.
So, they found him.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, I, um, I need to
make funeral arrangements
and, uh, call a board meeting.
'Cause Petra's gonna try
to use this to take control.
- So...
- You can do that later.
No, I really can't.
I know her; She's gonna pounce.
I got to be prepared.
Speaking of prepared,
Luisa was ready to share everything.
Okay, I'm gonna need
you to tell me everything
that happened between you and Rose.
No detail is too small.
Finally, a chance to tell the truth
about the greatest love story ever told.
It all started about five years ago.
I was sitting alone at a girl bar,
and then I saw her.
She was wearing this tight red dress
that highlighted every curve of her body,
her breasts, her hips, her...
Got it. Good.
And then she sat down next to me.
Hi.
We could both feel it,
that instant attraction.
Can I buy you a drink?
34 days sober.
Gotcha.
I am just getting out
of the drug world myself.
Of course, when she was
talking about the drug world,
she was referring to her former
half-billion-dollar-a-year business.
Yeah.
I didn't pick up on that.
I mentioned the red dress, right?
Yes.
And what happened then?
And then we left.
We just wanted time to be alone.
So how long are you in town?
The weekend.
I'm trying to close this
deal, but my heart's not in it.
She was trying to
close a deal, all right.
She was dating a man
so she could use his hotel
for her illegal plastic surgery ring,
and her heart wasn't in it because,
well, Rose was a lesbian.
I really did not expect this.
I guess you never know when
lightning is gonna strike.
And then she kissed me.
And then there were fireworks.
It was also the fourth of July.
And then we made love.
Raw, passionate, desperate love.
Okay, then what?
We made love again.
- Okay, after that?
- And yet again.
Okay, well,
let's assume you guys
had sex a bunch of times.
Can we skip ahead?
I thought I'd never see her again.
And then I went to a
family dinner that night.
It was a horrible night.
My dad was all over my brother.
You are such a disappointment.
Thanks, dad.
It means a lot.
Oh, my God.
Oh, good, you made it.
I am so sorry I'm late.
Traffic was terrible.
Ah, yes,
the deal Rose was trying to close,
it was Emilio.
You're dating my father?
Please lower your voice.
What about last night?
It was a mistake.
I really, I do have feelings for him.
I...
It's getting serious.
Look, I just, I...
I think I needed to be with a woman
one last time, you know?
Just...
Get it out of my system.
Yeah, I get it.
I mean, I have a girlfriend anyway.
Her name's Allison,
and she loves to have sex in bathrooms.
Good.
I'm glad.
You have some...
Mashed potatoes on your shirt.
Can I get a glass of water, please?
Is that allowed?
Again, you're not under arrest.
You can have anything you want.
So if you can bring
my black dress in the morning?
Sure, no problem.
Thanks. I just don't want
to leave him alone tonight.
Yeah, I get it.
How's he holding up?
He seems...
Okay right now.
You know, he's just making arrangements
for the funeral and talking
to his lawyer about business.
Well, people cope in different ways.
Yeah, I know. I...
I just don't know what he needs
or how to help him.
Well, just be there for him, I think.
That's all you can do.
I just...
I did something really stupid today,
and I-I'm just worried
that he's not gonna trust me enough
to open up, you know?
For some of us, it's hard,
talking about feelings and stuff.
Hello?
Luisa?
It's me.
How are you?
How am I?
You put me in a mental institution.
You killed my father!
I know, and I'm sorry.
Why are we only seeing her back?
But this plan, it's been
in the works for years.
Oh, maybe she's changed her face.
Before we met.
Why are you calling me?
Because how I feel
about you, what we have,
that was the only thing in my life
this past five years that was real.
And you once said that you
wanted to run away with me.
Do you still?
You okay?
Yeah.
Petra called a board
meeting an hour from now.
It's a power play.
She's got no shame.
I'm so sorry.
It really was a beautiful service.
I, um, I need to go talk to my sister.
- Do you mind?
- No, of course not.
- _
- Mm-hmm.
You okay?
Yeah, I just...
I can't believe he's gone.
I know.
I'm so sorry, Lu.
For not believing you.
For everything.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
And listen, I know this is
the worst time in the world,
and trust me, I don't want
to be thinking about this.
- What?
- Business.
I don't want anything to do with it.
I know, I know,
but now that dad is gone,
we each own a third of the Marbella.
And Petra, she owns the other third.
So, if you assign your shares to me,
I can overpower her.
Is that why you apologized to me?
Because you want my shares?
No, I was just...
Petra's calling a board
meeting in an hour.
I have to think practically, that's it.
No, you have to think about
the fact that you and dad
locked me up in a mental institution.
I know.
And when you were sick with cancer,
I was there for you.
Look, things got messed up.
Yeah, they did.
Want to know why?
Because of money.
I meant what I said when
I got back from the ashram.
Money is the root of all of our problems,
and I want out.
So, yeah.
You can have my shares.
And if you don't mind,
I-I want to be alone now.
Thanks for coming today.
It really meant a lot.
Of course.
In such sad days, it helps people
to see a celebrity.
And like you said,
we are a part of each other's lives now.
No matter what happens.
So does that mean you made
a decision about Mexico?
No.
Not yet,
but your mother thinks I should go.
- Come on.
- That's what she said.
That I should do what makes me happy.
Would it have made a difference
if she said something else?
Perhaps.
Okay, you two,
we were just at a funeral,
and if that doesn't say
that life is too short,
I don't know what does.
So you two are gonna tell each other
how you feel honestly right now.
Go.
Okay, mom, you go first.
Rogelio is...
Dad?
Right.
Dad is considering going to Mexico.
How does that make you feel?
You know.
No, we don't.
Tell us.
I guess...
I'd be... bummed.
"Bummed."
Okay, good.
We can work with "bummed."
Why?
His turn.
Okay.
Mom said she would feel bummed.
How would you feel if you
were far away from her?
I would feel like... Santos felt
when he was separated from Blanca.
Okay, now real world version.
- I'd be devastated.
- Why?
Because I have very strong
feelings for your mother.
And I would like to see where things go.
Really?
Of course. Go on, mom.
Tell him how you feel.
I have really strong feelings
for you, too, and I
don't want you to leave.
Then I won't go. I will stay
and work on Esteban's show.
But you hate him.
And what if you hate it?
A-and if you do it for me
and-and you don't like it, I don't know,
you might blame me.
Never. And I will shine
on Esteban's show the way I always shine!
Even brighter because
you will be by my side.
There has been an awakening.
Have you felt it?
Bueno.
_
Seriously, was it that difficult
for them to tell each
other how they feel?
_
Yeah.
I don't think Rafael feels safe with me.
We got into a fight earlier
and I didn't trust him.
Which... hurt.
And I get that.
Bueno...
_
- Hmm?
- Yeah.
Exactly.
So, how do I fix it?
Thank you all so much for meeting.
Look, I know it's short
notice, but I thought
it would be a good time
to talk about our game plan
- moving forward.
- That's great.
Luisa's here to formally
assign her shares over to me.
Which means I am still in charge.
Actually, Rafael,
I've changed my mind about the shares.
Uh...
I thought you didn't want to have
anything to do with this hotel.
I don't. I'm assigning
my shares to Petra.
What? Are you crazy?!
No, actually, I'm not crazy.
Okay, I should probably explain.
Remember when this happened?
I meant what I said when
I got back from the ashram.
Money is the root of all of our problems.
And I want out.
So, yeah.
You can have my shares.
Luisa?
I... I saw you here.
And I-I...
Well, I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
Your father was always good to me.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
I want to apologize to you.
We never got along.
And that's my fault.
But a day like today...
It makes you reflect.
That's what my shaman says, anyway.
You have a shaman?
Yes. Uh...
I went to an ashram a few weeks ago.
I know, I know, I know it sounds silly.
No. It doesn't.
Really?
I wish Rafael would consider an ashram.
He's so...
Misguided, you know?
Money is destroying your life.
You're not relating to
people as people anymore.
We're all just financial
liabilities to you.
Luisa, look.
I get that you are mad, okay?
But, please, do not
give Petra your shares.
I'm not giving them to her.
I'm assigning her my voting rights
while I go to my ashram to think.
That is crazy.
There you go with that word again.
Uh... Look...
Uh, I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna take off.
Take care of yourself.
Well, I guess that's settled.
So, let's talk about some changes.
Shall we?
From now on...
I'm the face of the Marbella.
To say that Petra was on
top of the world right now,
well, that would be a
gross understatement.
Hi. How are you?
Petra had just made the world
her bitch.
Uh, what floor?
And then
she saw her dead ex-lover.
Roman?
No.
I-I'm his brother Aaron.
Yes. Oh.
Yes, of course you are.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
You just... you look so much like him.
What is your name?
Oh, uh, Petra.
Petra.
Solano?
It is so nice to finally meet you.
My brother's told me so much about you.
I look forward to getting to know you.
I talked to my agent.
I told her that I'm staying here,
working on Esteban's show.
What did she say?
That I'm stupid.
But, hey, you pay agents
to give their opinion,
then you threaten to fire them,
then you hang up on them,
and then you do whatever you want.
You are what I want.
Well, you know what I want?
But what about your vow of chastity?
You said you wanted to wait to have sex.
Yeah, but that was until
there was a commitment.
And you just decided
to stay in town for me.
That's a pretty good commitment
from where I'm standing.
- It is not the same as marriage.
- Why are you arguing, man?
Why am I arguing?
Michael.
You've got to see this.
Where's Luisa?
How am I supposed to know?
She took off after the meeting.
Why?
Okay.
After Rose sent Luisa a letter,
we started monitoring your sister's phone
just in case she tried
to reach out to her.
Well, last night, she did.
Rose asked Luisa to run away with her.
Your sister said no.
About an hour ago, she sent
a text to an encoded number.
Yes?
Yup. She's gone.
I got takeout Chinese.
I don't know what you like
to eat when you're upset.
But egg rolls are my go-to.
Egg rolls sound great.
Good.
And, look, you don't have to tell me
the way you're feeling right now.
I-I just want you to know that you can.
That you can trust me with whatever
you're feeling or thinking.
Because I love you.
I do.
I love you.
I love you. I love you.
And in that moment, it felt
like a telenovela again.
But for all the best reasons.
And I am so, so sorry
that your father is gone.
I can't imagine what you're
going through right now.
It's, uh...
Just hard.
'Cause I was a huge disappointment.
No...
No, I was 'cause he told me.
And I'm fighting so hard to change that.
Mm.
Good morning.
Have you been up long?
Mm, little bit.
Oh, I filled this out.
It's our baby shower questionnaire.
So we can ace that test.
Aw, that's sweet.
"Livin' on a Prayer"?
Really? You don't want
to rethink that one?
That's a great song.
But I do want to rethink something else.
Caddyshack?
Filling this out
made me think about our
whole registry thing.
Jane, what are we doing, huh?
I love you.
You love me.
We're having a baby.
This is true.
So let's move in together.
- Synced and corrected by ChrisKe -
- www.addic7ed.com -