Previously, on
AMC's "The Walking Dead."
We live.
We kill them all.
You wanna just come back with us?
Take a couple days before
you and Tara go out again?
I just wanna get outta here.
Heath and I are still
going on that two-weeker.
When we leave from there...
It's gross. Just throw it back.
It'll dry out.
It smells terrible.
We can empty it out,
stuff it full of Miss Iris' sage,
and some of the lavender, too.
Then what?
Then you have an awesome bear
that survived the stormy sea, Rachel.
I had one just like this
when I was your age, and...
Oh, shit! Look!
Don't run!
One hit.
I didn't have to twice.
Not bad, huh?
Yeah.
Look! Another one!
Come on. Don't run!
Wait!
She's not a bobber.
She's alive.
We still gotta do it.
No.
We don't have to do it.
Yes, we do.
No, we don't, not if
people don't find out.
We're supposed to.
I want to.
I don't.
So we won't.
Are you gonna tell?
Just tell me if you're gonna tell,
if you're a snitch.
I'm not a snitch.
But I'm not going to help.
Sync and corrections by rickSG
www.addic7ed.com
Eight rusty cans of okra
and a bottle of aspirin.
That's what we got to show
for our time out here...
other than the fact that
we're still standin'.
Rule number one of scavenging...
There's nothing left in
this world that isn't hidden.
We just have to find it.
Good.
For a second there,
I was worried.
Listen, we went farther
than we were supposed to.
There's nothing left out here.
We don't even have
enough gas to keep looking
even if we wanted to, okay?
We said we'd be gone for two weeks.
It's been two weeks.
As long as the Hilltop keeps
their side of the bargain,
we have food at home.
We need ammo.
We need medicine.
We can't go back like this.
There's people counting on us.
Why you acting like you don't know that?
I'm not sure that means
much to me anymore.
What we did at the satellite station...
all of those people that we killed...
You didn't see it, okay?
You just saw what was left.
No.
I had to do it, too.
Yeah, we all had to...
for some milk and some corn.
That wasn't the only reason.
And yeah, we did.
You know we did.
See, that's... That's the thing.
You saw how we were living back
home before you guys got there.
We didn't know shit.
We thought...
What?
- What?
- It doesn't matter.
I get it now.
If it's you or someone
else, you choose you.
You take what you can, you
take out who you have to,
and you get to keep going.
Nobody's in this together, okay?
Not anymore.
Hey.
It only hurts because you know what
you just said is total bullshit.
That's not you, Heath.
Tara...
that's me...
that's you...
and that's everybody
who wants to stay alive.
That's the truth.
We can push towards the
shore, but after today...
we go back.
Even if we just have those rusty cans.
No, I got it. Thanks.
Did they find
anything out there yesterday?
Ev said she reached the mouth.
Are you serious?
- What'd she see?
- Nothing.
All the way down there.
Not a damn thing.
Go ahead.
Doesn't matter.
We're supposed to.
Rachel... no.
Hi.
I just... I didn't mean to.
Look, I'm cool.
I'm not here to hurt anyone.
Rachel...
everyone, just lower your guns.
Cyndie, get away from her!
She hasn't done anything wrong.
That has nothing to do with it.
Get away!
I'm sorry.
I just walked in... Crawled.
I didn't even know I was in.
I'm sorry.
I can just go.
Okay.
This is cool, too.
We just keep doing this.
What do we think?
Lotta blind spots down there.
Let's check behind the tarps first.
Looks like they had plans for something.
Looks like they didn't get to finish.
It's heavy.
Could be something good in there.
Tara.
Hold on. Hold on!
That way! Go!
- Heath!
- Tara!
Heath!
We just need to
hear what she has to say.
No. The longer we wait,
the more our community's at risk.
We agreed to discuss this together
as a group if someone ever got in.
We made that decision a long time ago.
Do you, need to use the
bathroom before we get started?
No.
Thank you.
But maybe...
I'm Natania.
This is Kathy and Beatrice,
whom you've already met.
Am I the only one hearing bells?
They're ours. We have six of them...
Some nearby, some a
couple of miles away.
What about the air horn?
We could only find so many bells.
They are to redirect any of the dead
that might have been drawn by it.
Not bad.
It helps sometimes.
But a branch in the
wind, leaves rustling...
We're lucky this is a
relatively clear area.
The evacuations, the barges...
If they were even real.
So...
where are you from?
Atlanta...
a long time ago.
I just stayed on the move.
My friend and I... We've
been traveling around
on our own for a couple years now.
We used to work on a fishing boat.
There's someone with you?
There was.
We got separated.
What kind of fishing
boat did you work on...
Trawler, seiner, larder?
Oh, last one. You got it.
What were you doing here?
You must understand, we get nervous
when people just find
their way into our home.
Yeah, I-I saw that.
My friend and I... We found this
settlement built on a bridge,
or what was left of it.
We were scavenging, and we got
attacked by walkers... the dead.
We were trying to get away from them,
and I got knocked off a bridge.
I fought the current,
wound up in the inlet.
The estuary?
The bay?
Look, I'm not good with geography.
I just thought I was dead out there.
And I got to the shore,
and I just passed out.
It's the bridge on Windsor.
You... you know how to get there?
We do.
She didn't answer the question.
I didn't?
What was the question?
What were you doing here?
When that girl, Cyndie, brought me food,
I just pretended like I was
out and I followed her back.
It seemed like she had a camp,
and I wanted to see if
I could get any help.
Then why were you sneaking around?
I wanted to see if it was safe.
Still not sure.
Look, I'm sorry that I freaked you out.
Really.
But if you just point me in
the right direction, I'm gone.
I need to get back to the
bridge and look for my friend.
If we let you go, you
have us at a disadvantage.
You know a great deal about us now.
If you let me go?
Yes.
You see, normally, we
would've killed you already.
We shoot strangers on sight
if they come into our camp.
But Beatrice said you spared your life,
and my granddaughter almost
lost hers trying to save you...
"that girl," Cyndie.
So it leaves us with the question still
of what to do with you instead.
Yeah.
That's a pickle, all right.
Why don't you rest up?
We'll talk more later.
Maybe one of us will have a brainstorm.
Cool.
Hope you like fish.
The dried kind?
She brought you salted perch.
Did you like it?
Sure.
No, you didn't.
Not so much.
We're having stew.
Oh, that's right...
You two haven't formally met, have you?
Tara, this is Cyndie.
Hey.
Thank you for the beach and...
everything out there.
I mean, you saved my life.
You did.
I mean, I don't know if your
grandma totally approves, but...
My mom would've.
She showed me the way.
A way.
I was trying to show Rachel.
The little girl?
Yeah.
She hasn't had to do it yet.
Have you?
I'm a really good shot.
Yes, you are.
Okay, let's eat.
Let's talk.
Tara.
When was the last time you ate?
Do soy-sauce packets count as food?
We have an endless
supply of fish here...
One of the perks of living
so close to the ocean.
You... you think, Tara,
it's something you could get used to?
I'm hoping to convince you to stay.
Wait. What?
Why not?
It would be the perfect
solution to our problem.
We keep our village a secret,
and you'd get to put down roots.
You're a skilled fighter,
Tara, and a good person.
I can tell that.
You wouldn't be leaving anything behind.
And if you want, we can
help you find your friend.
And if he wants to stay,
we'll offer him a home, too.
He could stay here?
Is there a reason why not?
I mean...
well, I never thought
I'd be asking this,
but where are all the men?
All of them?
We got into a
skirmish with another group.
None of them made it.
And we lost others, too.
Cyndie had an 11-year-old
brother, my grandson,
and their mother, too, my daughter.
After that, we decided to
protect ourselves, no matter what.
No matter who we crossed,
we would kill on sight.
We left our old home with
just the clothes on our backs.
And then we found this place.
We would stay hidden.
And we would stay alive.
Tara, you could have
hurt us, and you didn't.
I-I know we must sound
like monsters to you,
but I had to be honest so maybe
you could understand why we do it.
Maybe you could...
consider staying.
And maybe you could be honest with us
about where you're from.
I was telling you the truth.
Really?
You said you worked on
a fishing boat, a larder.
That's right.
Tara, a larder is a room
used for storing meat.
Yeah. I was lying.
I come from a community.
And that's really what it is.
We live with each other.
We help each other.
We have walls, houses.
I have a girlfriend
I want to get back to.
And we've done things...
just like you.
There were these people.
They were threatening us.
We found out they were using an old
satellite station to operate out of.
We went out there in the
middle of the night, and we...
took them out, every one of them.
These people got what they deserved.
They chose to kill and
to terrorize people,
but that's not why we killed them.
We didn't do it to make
the world a better place.
We did it because we wanted
to stay alive, just like you.
And I know that you
think that me staying
is the only solution.
Well, how's this for brainstorming...
Maybe our groups can
start working together.
We just told you that we don't want
anyone to know about this place.
You can't live like that forever.
I think we can.
Look, I ... I
get why you're doing it,
but if you keep seeing
everyone as an enemy,
then enemies are all you're gonna find.
Sooner or later, you're
gonna need a friend.
We can protect each other.
We'd be safer than we are...
All right.
We could send a guide out with her.
Help her look for her friend,
and then continue on to their community,
just... just to see what it's like.
Yeah, I'll do it.
I want to go with her.
Absolutely not.
You left without leaving a routing plan,
without signing with the gate.
Cyndie, I thought we were
through with all this.
We are.
You will be staying behind the fence
until you learn some responsibility.
If this works out, there will
be plenty of other chances.
And if it doesn't...
I don't want you there.
There will be other chances.
Are you sure there isn't a
fishing boat called a larder?
'Cause I'm, like, pretty sure that...
- There isn't.
- Yeah. Fair enough.
This is gonna get better...
People getting together.
That's how the world is
gonna be the world again.
I hope you're right.
Be safe.
Where's Cyndie?
She's in the cabin, sulking.
We wouldn't be doing this if
it wasn't for her breaking all the rules.
Good luck, Tara.
Yeah.
You know, we'll...
We'll work on that, Natania.
Thank you.
See you soon.
See you later, Rachel.
Hey, Beatrice.
I'm sorry about the hit.
Well, you got lucky.
Yeah, I did.
How far are we to the bridge?
About halfway there.
Stick close. It's pretty
thick through here.
I got it.
Please.
I could have killed
you back in the village.
Let me go.
You don't have anything left.
Your people are dead.
The Saviors.
That satellite post you took out...
You have no idea what you started.
We didn't start anything.
We ended it. They're dead.
You didn't stop them.
You can't stop them.
That was just an outpost.
There are more... More Saviors...
more outposts.
If they know about your friends...
it's already too late for them.
The Saviors...
they did this to you?
They're the ones that
killed all your men?
Every man...
every boy over 10.
They lined 'em up, shot 'em in the head.
You see, we tried to fight...
just like you.
They won.
And we were supposed to
keep working for them.
Then one night, we just left.
We got away, okay?
We are not gonna let
you lead them back to us.
They get what they want.
I'm sorry you didn't get...
Go! Run!
Wait!
You're not gonna shoot me.
Because I saved you?
Three times now.
You're not gonna shoot me.
You have to swear...
that you'll never come back
and you'll never tell anyone about us,
not even your own people.
Why... would I come back?
Why would I tell
anyone about this place?
Because maybe you could
get something out of it...
Anything.
Why did we kill those two
people who just came near us?
Why did you kill all those people
at that satellite station?
Because you all thought you had to.
But none of you had to.
You just did.
Nobody's evil.
They just decide to forget who they are.
You have to swear.
Some people are evil, Cyndie.
I've seen it.
That's why I have to get back now.
You have to swear.
I swear.
Here.
Food and water.
C'mon.
I'll take you to the bridge.
Try not to fall off this time.
There's more, right?
Yeah, a lot.
I'll use the cars as cover
until I can't anymore.
Then what?
I'll run.
I love to run.
It's my favorite thing.
You'll never make it.
Yeah, I will.
Let me help you.
You already did. You got me here.
Just go back. Tell them
that I attacked you.
They know you, Tara.
No, tell them you killed me.
They know me.
You know I'm not going anywhere
until you get to the other side... safe.
I've got my rifle. I've got ammo.
I didn't get you here
just to watch you die.
So let's just get this over with, okay?
Kathy and Beatrice... They
know we were coming here.
They're coming.
Okay.
Why aren't you like the rest of them,
after everything that's happened?
Why aren't you?
Okay.
Okay, up on that side.
Go!
Heath!
Heath, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
No! Go! Go!
We're in this together!
I know.
Maybe that was you.
I hope that was you.
I'm sorry, Tara.
I'm sorry, too.
We don't have to just sit here.
Guns, ammunition...
you don't have any leads?
Anything, anywhere.
I don't care how dangerous it looked.
Tell me a place.
I'll go.
There's gotta be somewhere.
We can square this.
We can make this right.
We have to.
We can't.
I didn't see anything
like that out there.