See that aspiring model there?
C'est moi... Deb...
Jusqu'au jour de ma mort.
Je pensais aller droit au paradis,
mais il y a une erreur,
and I woke up in someone else's body.
So now I'm Jane,
a super-busy lawyer
with my very own assistant.
I got a new life, a new wardrobe,
and the only people who really
know what's going on with me
are my girlfriend Stacy
and my guardian angel, Paul.
I used to think everything
happened for a reason.
- Whoo!
- Now, I sure hope I was right.
Drop Dead Diva 5x08 - 50 Shades of Grayson
Original air date August 11, 2013
Sync and corrections by atrn97g
for www.addic7ed.com
Oh, no, no, seriously, I'm good.
I'm good.
- Stacy!
- Oh! Oh!
Oh, wow!
You must do like
a thousand push-ups every day.
Oh!
It's too close. It's too close!
- Oh, God! Oh, God!
- Emma!
Hi!
You should totally do a shot
on that blond's six pack.
- I will call him over.
- Oh, I'm fine. I'm fine.
But thanks, Stacy.
Can you believe
I'm getting married in two days?
No.
I shouldn't even be looking at them.
I know, but let's kind of look again.
Oh, this is Robert's best man
calling from the bachelor party.
Okay.
No, Stacy! Stace!
That's like your third shooter
in 10 minutes.
I'm about to be
artificially inseminated.
And this bachelorette party
is... it's like my last hurrah.
- Okay.
- Emma!
Who wants to strip naked
and jump into the neighbor's hot tub?!
Wow, are you okay?
Robert was arrested in San Diego.
I need to get down there, Jane.
He needs a lawyer.
I am furious. I'm devastated.
I am pissed to high hell!
Just slow down.
Start from the beginning.
When my husband lost his job,
we were in bad shape.
So I decided to publish a book online.
And at first, I was earning
almost $2,000 a month,
but now almost nothing.
And it's all because a best seller
ripped off my story line,
my characters... everything!
Look. Here's my book.
An Erotic Thriller."
I know what you're thinking.
But it paid the bills.
Last we spoke,
I thought you were writing
a serious novel.
Yeah, I couldn't find a publisher.
But they all complimented
on the one sex scene...
missionary in a yoga studio.
And that's when you decided
to write e-rom?
Erotic romance.
There's a huge market
for female-focused historical erotica.
"The Randy Baron" saved my family.
But then it got ripped off
by "The Naughty Earl."
Look.
With the marketing behind that book,
my book has become invisible.
They're really that similar?
Down to the mead-driven orgy
in the hedge maze.
Mmm! I've always
wanted to do it in a maze.
You're not alone. Women really
responded to my book.
Well, that's probably why
Elyse Hoffman copied you.
Cindy, we'll start working
on your case immediately.
Robert was having a blast.
We got drunk at the hotel
and decided to cross the border
into Tijuana.
- Always a smart decision.
- We were marinated in Tequila.
We weren't thinking straight.
What exactly happened to my fiancé?
When we were coming back to the U.S.,
we got separated
at the border-crossing station.
As his best man, I went to look for him
and found out he was arrested
for disorderly conduct.
Okay, I need to speak with Robert.
The marshal said he'll come get us
when he's in his holding cell.
- Holding cell?!
- No, no, no.
It's all fine.
Listen, you and Robert are going
to be married tomorrow night.
I promise.
Okay?
Anyone need caffeine?
- No, thank you.
- Okay, I'll be right back.
Ah, this court never has cream.
Which is why
I keep a stash in the fridge.
You never know when they'll
arrest a client at the border.
Thank you!
- I'm Luis.
- Jane.
You an immigration attorney?
Well, my office is in Long Beach,
but I practically live
in this courthouse.
- Ah!
- I am digging that outfit.
Especially the, uh, glitter in the hair.
Oh. Yeah.
I left a bachelorette party
to rescue a drunk bachelor
who got arrested at the border.
Happens every night.
You'll argue before judge Coleman,
and if your client
doesn't have a record,
he'll just be released with a fine.
Great. Thank you.
Excuse me. Jane? Robert's ready for us.
Okay. Thanks, again. Luis?
Yeah. No problem. I'll see you later.
I have an appearance
before the same judge, so...
Great.
Emma, I am so sorry.
You swore that the party
wouldn't get out of control.
What happened?
Honestly, I don't know.
Okay, Robert, what do you remember?
I was at the Hard Rock pounding shots,
and then I woke up in jail
with vomit on my shoes.
Everything in between is a blank.
Emma, please forgive me.
I can't wait to get married.
But right now I want to kill you.
You had an impressive second quarter.
Things are certainly up
since you've arrived.
I'm just part of a team, Mr. Tuttle.
- Ah. Meet my colleague.
- Ah, Ms. Kaswell.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I was just with a client.
Not a problem. Clients should
always come first.
Spoken like a true
malpractice insurance adjustor.
Yes, and, uh, I'm sure you're both busy,
so I'll get down to it.
Mr. Parker has hired me
to make sure that the firm
is adequately protected.
I'll need access to all of
your employees and your records.
I'm sorry. W... will you excuse me
for a second?
Certainly.
I'll use the time
to speak with Ms. Kaswell.
Great.
So, Ms. Kaswell,
how long do you plan on
being out of commission?
Excuse me?
Maternity leave.
It's relevant to my assessment.
Oh.
Um, yeah, I plan to keep
my leave as short as possible.
Uh-huh.
I mean, I'm... I'm working on
my childcare plans right now.
I... I believe it, uh, takes a village.
A village?
Hmm. Got it.
Stacy, what's wrong?
Oh, nothing's wrong.
I brought gifts
in honor of your sperm donation.
- Boxers?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, Jane happened to mention
that you wear tighty whities,
- but...
- Huh.
...to maximize sperm motility,
you got to keep those fellas
free and cool.
Uh-huh.
Fertil-aid...
the selenium and zinc
increase sperm count.
Let me guess... super sperm water.
No, just regular water.
Don't take the pills without drinking.
I don't want you to choke.
Okay. Stacy, when exactly
will you be ovulating?
Any day now.
As soon as my ovulation stick
turns pink,
I will pick you up,
drive you to the clinic
at Roosevelt Hospital,
and you can make a fresh deposit.
Okay. I'll be ready.
- Okay!
- All right.
Excuse me.
I did some digging
on the "Randy Baron" case.
Now, according to Cindy's sales records,
her e-book was downloaded
by an executive at the publishing house.
Well, that's great.
It proves the publishing house
had access.
- Nice work.
- Thanks.
Nicole's stepping up.
I'm glad you've noticed.
You know, we only date where we work
when we're too busy
to seek it out elsewhere.
Says the woman who's expecting
the senior partner's baby any minute.
Says the woman who was dumped
by the senior partner
and speaks from experience.
Hey, Grayson, other than me,
does anyone else know
about the two of you?
No, we're being discreet.
Well, for what it's worth, be careful.
Don't hurt her.
What about me? I could get hurt.
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
Was my client sloppy-drunk? Yes.
I mean, we all know how guys
can be at bachelor parties.
But the disorderly-conduct
charge should be dropped.
My client has no prior record.
What does the United States
have to say on this?
Your Honor, the United States
is amending its complaint.
We are now charging Robert Medina
with false representation of citizenship
in violation
of 8 U.S. code section 12-27.
Excuse me. What?
Your client is not a U.S. citizen.
It's true. I... I moved to
the U.S. when I was an infant,
and I have a green card.
I don't even speak Spanish.
Okay, my client is a legal
resident. He has a green card.
The defendant was born in Mexico.
Your Honor, last night,
while trying to cross
back into the United States,
he went into the American-citizen line.
I call the court's attention
to the surveillance footage.
Okay, what is the problem?
His California driver's license
is valid.
So, Your Honor, as I mentioned earlier,
my client was really drunk.
Getting in the wrong line...
it was just...
it was just an innocent mistake.
The law prohibits the impersonation
of an American citizen
at a border crossing.
It...
I agree. I'm gonna
set this down for trial.
Uh, whoa!
Your Honor, my client is due
to be married in 36 hours.
I request an expedited hearing.
Fine, we'll reconvene after lunch.
- Ms. Bingum?
- Yeah?
I know you're in a rush,
but, uh...
If your client is found guilty,
the penalty is exclusion from the U.S.
for a minimum of five years.
Robert will be stuck in Mexico?
Yeah, that's right,
and, uh, I'm sorry to say,
but the odds are against you.
Oh, man. I love bachelor parties.
Getting so drunk
you can't remember anything?
What's the point?
If you have to ask,
you can't understand it.
Whose phone is this, anyway?
The best man's, whom I blame
for taking my client out of
the country in the first place.
Thank you for driving down, by the way.
I needed this change of clothes
in the worst way.
I listened to Beyoncé.
I flashed a few truckers.
Two hours flew by.
Now that I'm here, I thought
I might go to the beach.
Uh, no. Not so fast.
I need you to go through
the discovery
the A.U.S.A. just dumped on me.
Hey, I thought you angelinos
might be hungry.
- Gracias, señor.
- Thank you!
So the false-representation charge...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...It's based on
this federal statute
rarely enforced before 9/11,
but now the U.S. attorney's
office is using it
as this anti-immigration weapon.
Robert is a legal immigrant
with no record!
Yes, and having a clean record is key.
Be sure to tell the court
that Robert never meant
to misrepresent himself.
- Okay.
- Oh, and it wouldn't hurt
to compliment judge Coleman's watch.
Why his watch?
His brother makes these
handcrafted watch bands.
He could talk about it for hours.
Thank you for helping my wife.
Her book... it... it really saved us.
Don't worry, Howard.
We're gonna make this right.
All rise.
Be seated.
- Ms. Kaswell.
- Yes.
Your Honor, we'd like to introduce
as plaintiff's exhibit "A,"
a sales report from my client's company.
On may 5th, a credit card
owned by Jamie Levit
was used to purchase my client's book.
Ms. Levit is an editor
with the Hudson Lake Press,
which proves
they had access to her book.
Just because
an employee purchased the book
doesn't prove Elyse Hoffman copied it.
Correct, which is why we
need to hear from Ms. Hoffman.
Elyse Hoffman is actually here.
I'm I'm sorry. What?
Hudson Lake Press is Elyse Hoffman.
You want to explain that?
My client uses a team of writers
to compose their erotic fiction,
but even if we admit to access,
the standard for a plagiarism
claim is substantial similarity.
We are not stipulating to that.
She's right, Ms. Kaswell.
And the burden of proof is on you.
Well, thank you for noticing,
Ms. Bingum.
These bands also come in women's styles,
and they're available
in a shop across the street.
Well, I will have to buy me a few
before heading back to L.A.,
which I'm hoping will be today,
as there's no reason
to further detain my client,
a respected businessman
who never intended
to misrepresent himself.
Very well. Does the government
wish to add anything?
Yes, Your Honor.
Based on recent information,
we are proceeding
with additional criminal charges
against the defendant.
- What?!
- Solicitation of a prostitute
at the San Diego Hard Rock Hotel
yesterday, prior to visiting Mexico.
The San Diego P.D. just sent my office
a credit-card receipt
for a "happy massage."
- Even if that's true...
- It's not true.
Even if the allegations are true,
it's only a misdemeanor.
It's also a crime of moral turpitude,
and any person
convicted of such a crime,
if found guilty of false representation,
faces a 10-year exclusion
from the United States.
I'm sorry, Ms. Bingum,
but these proceedings are stayed
pending the outcome
of this solicitation charge,
which I will hear this afternoon.
So you have no memory of using
your credit card at 11:03 P.M.
To pay for a Tina Lassider's
massage service?
I... I don't remember anything.
But I would never cheat on Emma.
How can you not remember?
No matter how much I drank,
I would never cheat on you.
Can I come in?
Yeah.
Robert's innocent.
He didn't hire the prostitute.
I did.
I... I used your credit card
while you were passed out.
Son of a bitch!
I was really wasted, which is no excuse.
I'm so sorry, dude.
Let's talk about Jane Bingum.
What about Jane?
From what I've heard,
she's a trial phenom.
She is an asset to the firm.
Mr. French, why did you join
Harrison & Parker?
I mean, you could have made more
at a larger place.
Cut to the chase, Tuttle.
I think you came here for Jane.
How is that relevant?
Now that you're no longer together,
I'd like to know
if you plan on sticking around.
We were over before I joined the firm.
Perhaps you're hoping to win her back.
No. No, that's not the case.
You're a tremendous litigator.
Why don't you try to convince me
that you don't want Jane back.
Mr. Tuttle.
You need to know
if I'm staying with the firm
because if I left,
it would affect our insurance.
I'm telling you without hesitation
I'm not going anywhere.
My client's best man
hired the prostitute,
and he is willing to plead guilty.
I'll even go to jail.
Robert is innocent. I swear.
And I don't believe you.
This isn't the first time
a well-intentioned friend
offered to take the heat for
someone facing a harsh penalty,
such as deportation.
The immigration charge
should have no bearing
on how you handle this case.
I won't drop the charges
against your client,
but I will offer him a deal...
no jail time
in exchange for a guilty plea.
Well, unfortunately,
we can't take that deal.
Solicitation gets my client deported.
Then I have no choice.
I'll see you in court.
We went into the suite's bedroom,
and I ran his card
on my phone's payment app.
$250 is my rate for bobbing for apples,
if you know what I mean.
I believe I do.
No further questions.
Ms. Lassider, after you left the hotel,
weren't you arrested for...
"Bobbing for apples"
with a different man
three hours after you claimed
you "bobbed" with my client?
Yeah. They busted us in his prius.
And yet you aren't being charged
for any crimes that night,
as part of your immunity deal.
Yeah, but I'm telling the truth.
Credit cards don't lie.
Um...
You know what, you're right.
Credit cards don't lie.
People's exhibit 3...
your credit-card receipt
complete with time... 11:03 P.M.
That's relevant why?
I would like to introduce into evidence
defendant's exhibit 7 and 8...
time-stamped photographs of my client
taken the night of the alleged crime.
Tina, those photographs show
that my client
was passed out at 10:48 P.M.
And still passed out at 11:22 P.M.
I imagine the hotel room was dark.
Could you have "bobbed"
for someone else's apple
and confused him for my client?
That's the guy. If it helps,
I remember he was wearing
blue boxer briefs.
Blue boxer briefs?
I... I find it interesting because
when my client was arrested,
he was wearing plaid boxers,
as noted in defendant's exhibit 4...
the federal intake report.
At this time, I would like to ask Keith,
Robert's best man, to please stand up.
What color and style
of underwear do you wear?
See for yourself.
Blue boxer briefs.
I move to dismiss
all charges against my client.
Motion granted. This case is dismissed.
We are done for the day.
Your Honor, what about
the false-representation charge?
My docket's full.
Soonest I'd be able to hear this
is two weeks.
No. No, no, no.
See, my client's
getting married tomorrow.
There's nothing I can do.
Uh, excuse me, Your Honor?
I believe I have an at-liberty defendant
scheduled to appear before you
tomorrow morning.
I'd be delighted to adjourn that matter
in order to clear time
for Ms. Bingum's case.
Works for me.
We're adjourned till tomorrow.
Thank you so much.
How can I ever repay you?
Um, have dinner with me tonight?
- Okay.
Professor Sharf,
you have a PHD in literature
from Stanford University?
That's correct.
And you've read both the novel
and the online book.
Every page.
Did you find them to be
substantially similar?
Yes.
Uh, characters, tone, scene structure,
even the basic plot.
And how do you explain that?
Whoever wrote "The Naughty Earl"
first read "The Randy Baron"
and copied it.
Nothing further.
Professor Sharf, are you familiar with
the software program
called Plagiarismnet?
Yes. It's the gold standard
to prove plagiarism.
I'd like to introduce into
evidence a Plagiarismnet report
comparing "The Naughty Earl"
to "The Randy Baron."
- Objection.
- Your Honor, Ms. Kaswell
can produce 100 experts
who will say that
these two books
are substantially similar.
I can produce 100 more
that say they're not.
We contend that this software
is an objective way
to provide the truth.
The objection is overruled.
Professor, I have the results
of a Plagiarismnet comparison
of these two novels.
Could you please read the results?
The report shows a score of 41%.
Can you explain what that means?
It means there's a 41% chance
that the work was plagiarized.
The burden of proof for the plaintiff
is a preponderance of the evidence.
If there's only a 41% chance
that the work was plagiarized,
you need to side with my client.
Well, hold on.
We request time to review the report.
You have one night.
- Dinner was delicious.
- Yeah.
Oh, and I loved that story
about your roommate.
Oh, well, it's totally true.
I mean, she created a business
out of half a pie and half a cake.
Amazing.
All right, Luis,
so tell me all your secrets.
How do I win my case? You stay on point.
The law wasn't meant
to keep good people like Robert
out of the country.
You know, I'm free tomorrow morning
if you'd like for me to sit in
as your unofficial second chair?
Yeah! Your stature could really
help out with the judge.
Thank you.
Okay.
Enough shop talk. Tell me about you.
Uh, well, there's...
there's not much to tell.
Oh, I find that hard to believe.
Jane, you realize that Long Beach
isn't that far from L.A.
Oh.
Oh. Um...
I'm not really in a...
in a place for... for dating.
Oh. You're seeing someone.
- Well, not exactly. It's...
- No?
Mm!
Oh.
You know what? I think I'm gonna go.
- Is that okay?
- I'm sorry.
I'm fine. It's gonna be fine.
- Yeah? I'll see you.
- Okay.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, no problem.
Hi.
Can I go to the beach?
I thought you said that
asians don't like the beach.
They don't like the sun,
but I like the surfers.
What are you looking at?
The video of Robert's arrest.
It's 15 seconds long.
Can you go to immigration?
Ask if they have anything
that came before or after it?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
But first, is there
anything you want to tell me?
Rumor has it you were
chowing on pasta primavera
with a charming Latin lawyer.
Well, that's true.
- And he kissed me.
- Jane Bingum, I'm impressed.
Luis is smart,
and passionate, and single,
and I felt absolutely nothing.
I'm serious, not even a flutter.
When we get back to L.A.,
I'm gonna set you up
with my sex therapist.
Maybe you need to open up
your sex chakra.
No. I think my sex chakra's fine.
Look, we both know what's going on here.
The question is
what are you gonna do about it?
This is about Grayson.
It's always been about Grayson.
It's always gonna be about Grayson.
I love him, Teri.
Finally. You said it out loud.
Now, why are you telling me and not him?
Well...
Emma, you okay?
- I'll follow up on that video.
- Thanks.
If Robert can't go back
to the United States, I'll die.
- Emma.
- I love him so much.
I know it sounds sappy,
but the minute I met him,
I knew we'd be married.
I knew we'd be together forever.
And now I just...
I can't bear the thought that...
My mother is sick.
She lives with us,
and I take care of her.
If Robert gets stuck in Mexico,
I can't just go with him.
Please tell me that we're gonna win.
Well, can't you challenge
the Plagiarismnet report?
We won't prevail. It's been
independently verified.
I'm sorry.
Look, Cindy... this might
not bring much solace,
but I've read your e-rom,
and you have talent.
Don't let those thieves dissuade
you from writing another book.
You don't understand.
My book is personal.
You lost me.
It sounds crazy, I know.
But my book is based on
my life with Howard.
I changed the names.
I changed the settings
and obviously put it
in a different time period,
but all of those scenes...
Howard and I lived them.
Look, Kim, the only way
that I was able to
write that book so quickly
is because it is inspired by my life.
Can you prove it?
Yeah, I... I kept a journal.
Cindy, we're going back to court.
Stacy.
Hey. Uh, what are you doing here?
I'm pink. I... I mean,
my ovulation stick is pink.
- I'm ovulating!
- Oh! Okay. Uh, great.
I'll... I'll go to the clinic
right after work.
No, no, we need to go now.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. I can't.
I... I have a new-client meeting at 2:00,
and I... I abso... what is that?
Well, if you can't go to the clinic,
I'll bring the clinic to you.
Uh, where exactly am
I supposed to go to fill this?
There's a bathroom down the hall.
- Seriously?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, I also... I bought you
a magazine for inspiration.
The girl on the cover has lovely skin.
So, I'll be downstairs
getting frozen yogurt,
and you just give me a call
when the deed is done.
I hope I didn't offend you.
Clearly, I misread the situation.
Oh, no offense taken.
United States v. Robert Medina.
And we are back in session.
As you are aware,
my client has been cleared of
the state's solicitation charge,
and given that he has no record...
This statute is being used as a weapon
to victimize innocent,
law-abiding legal residents.
- Uh, Luis, please let me finish.
- The A.U.S.A.'s targeting
certain groups under orders
from their Washington superiors
who have an anti-immigration
agenda, and I...
Whoa! I am not alleging
anything like that.
Can we get back to discussing
my client's lack of intent?
Sit down!
Mr. Vega, are you suggesting that
I'm part of some
anti-immigration witch hunt?
- No!
- Yes!
I object!
You can't object to your co-counsel.
You're on the same side.
Well, I'm not so sure about that.
Counsel is seeking to use this case
to grandstand for political purposes.
And now we are asking for
a lifetime of exclusion
from the United States.
Your Honor, a recess, please.
30 minutes.
How dare you!
Hijacking my case
to set up a federal appeal?!
We need to get this statute overturned.
It is not being used
to keep out illegal aliens,
but rather to deport
legal residents like Robert,
who simply walked on to the wrong line!
I am sympathetic, but my objective
is to free my client
in time for his wedding!
I'm not here to change federal law!
Robert's a perfect case for appeal.
I mean, under this law, he could
end up in some foreign country
where he doesn't even
speak the language!
Yeah. That's why I'm trying to
keep him from getting deported.
Good luck with your crusade.
But please, stay away from my client...
and me.
Uh, Your Honor, before you rule,
we are amending our complaint
to add a conversion claim,
as we can prove that Hudson Lake Press
interfered with our client's
ownership of her life rights.
There are no life rights in this case.
My client's e-book is based on her...
rather adventurous sex life.
Howard, please stand.
Your Honor, Howard Kasper
is the Lord of Sussex,
the Randy Baron,
and Cindy is his mistress,
the Countess of Chestny, Lady Climoria.
You've got to be kidding.
Oh, I would never kid about sex.
We'd like to introduce into evidence
plaintiff's exhibit 11...
Cindy Kasper's journal.
We need time to read the journal.
We'll resume in one hour.
Owen? Owen, listen to me!
I was wrong.
The egg is not in the basket.
Keep the fish in the pond.
Fish in the pond!
Why are you screaming about fish?
I was... buying an aquarium.
Is Owen in there?
He's behind you.
Thank you.
Owen.
Please tell me you haven't.
I haven't.
Are we talking about the same thing?
I tried. Twice.
I can't do it at work.
Thank God. I'm not ovulating.
You said the stick was pink.
Actually, I was wearing
my new rose-tinted sunglasses,
and I misread the stick.
Sorry about the false alarm.
You know what? You can have this back.
- Oh.
- If we're gonna do this,
we're gonna do this
the old-fashioned way.
No, no, no!
In a small, windowless room in
a hospital's fertility clinic.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, Teri. I got your text.
Talk fast.
I'm due back in court in five.
I thought you'd want to see this.
Good! Yes! The additional
footage from immigration.
- No, not from immigration.
- Okay.
U.S. immigration only had the 15 seconds
the A.U.S.A. supplied at discovery.
But borders have two sides.
You got footage from Mexico?
My ex-boy toy Manuel has
a cousin at the consulate.
- Check this out.
- Okay.
- And now we know when he puked.
I'm failing to see the relevance.
Stay focused, Jane. Watch this.
Wait a minute.
He did not intentionally walk
into that U.S. citizen's line.
He was guided there.
Ahh!
I thought you'd be happy.
Can I go flirt with surfers now?
I bought a big straw hat
and Margarita shaker.
Yes, Teri. Go.
I am gonna get my client to his wedding.
Mrs. Kasper, as I understand it,
chapter 7 of your online book
is based on a swinger party
you and your husband attended
in Van Nuys?
That's true.
Can you please read
the highlighted journal entry?
"I brought a casserole
to the Bosnak housewarming,"
"and the next thing I knew,
the caterers were naked,"
"and we were in the middle of an orgy"
"in their converted garage."
Grayson, will you please read
the first few lines of chapter 7
of Cindy's online book,
"The Randy Baron"?
"I brought a welsh pudding
to the Vickford's new manor."
"Our garments were torn from us
by their scantily clad servants"
"as we were thrown into
the most splendid of orgies"
"in the smoking room."
Cindy, regarding
the Bosnak casserole party,
how does your journal entry conclude?
"I was incredibly turned on,"
"especially when Stanley Bosnak
picked me up"
"and lifted me onto his body."
"To think, I was worried
my casserole wouldn't go over."
Grayson, the, uh... the last few lines
of the Welsh pudding party, please.
"My lady pot was dripping with desire"
"as the Squire lifted me
upon his throbbing kingdom."
"To think, only that morn"
"I worried my welsh pudding
had chiggers."
Your Honor, obviously,
the correlation is, uh... um...
The correlation is... um...
Ohh!
You okay?
- Ms. Kaswell?
- I'm so sorry.
It appears, um... my water just broke.
But let's move on.
Um, Cindy, please read
your next journal entry
regarding the Jacobsen key party.
- Kim, you're in labor.
- No, no, no. I'm fine.
I'm fine. Just... just read it.
Ms. Kaswell,
I think we'd better adjourn.
Do you need medical assistance?
I don't... I don't think so.
No, not yet.
I just will request a 30-minute recess,
and then I'd like
to jump right to my closing.
You're having a baby.
I'm fine, really.
30 minutes... if you're available.
- But right now you need to go.
- Okay. Thank you.
My client did not intend
to get into the wrong line.
He was placed there by
a well-meaning Mexican official.
We never received this footage.
Oh, well, that's 'cause
you never asked for it.
It's from the Mexican consulate.
Judge, I am so sorry.
The footage is indisputable.
The defendant shall be released.
Now, one final point, Your Honor.
Go ahead, Ms. Kaswell.
And for the record,
I only agreed to this
so I wouldn't have to argue with you.
Sorry. Sorry.
One... one second!
Ohh!
Sorry.
The standard of proof for conversion
is also a preponderance of the evidence.
Based on my client's testimony,
as well as her journal,
it's clear that we've met that burden!
I agree. I find for the plaintiff.
- Aah!
- Whoo!
Now go, please. Have that baby.
Thanks, Kim!
Ohh. You're welcome.
Now get me the damn epidural!
Oh, you look beautiful!
Well, so do you!
I love getting ready for weddings.
Although I will say this one
took a little too much effort.
So I want to know more
about the hot lawyer.
He kissed you, and you felt nothing?
Zero.
But nobody could make me
feel anything except...
Grayson.
Yeah.
You know, the whole time
I was in San Diego,
I thought about him.
Because you love him
and you should be with him.
- What is that?
- Uh, it's my timer.
I set my phone to ring every three hours
to remind me to pee on a stick.
Excuse me.
That's me.
Hey.
Okay.
Yes.
That's great news.
Okay. Bye.
Stace.
Kim is at Roosevelt Hospital.
She just had her baby.
- She had a boy.
- Ohh!
That's awesome! Let's go.
You want to visit Kim?
I need to meet Owen there.
The fertility clinic
is on the third floor,
and I'm officially ovulating.
Okay.
All right, here we go.
Congratulations!
Hey. I thought you were in San Diego.
I just got back.
For the baby.
Ohh.
Let me guess. There must be
a sale at the gift shop.
Uh...
Grayson got me that one.
Well, it was between that or spongebob.
Is Grayson still here?
Yeah, he, um... he went to see
the baby in the nursery.
They took him away so I could sleep,
but, uh... I miss him already.
You look pretty.
Uh, thank you.
I'm going to a wedding.
And you came by to see me? Thank you.
Oh, sure.
Well, I'm also here because
Stacy is getting inseminated.
Oh. Eee!
Oh, well, uh, two birds, one stone.
How efficient.
Yeah.
Oh. That's actually Stacy.
She wants to see me.
But congratulations again, Kim.
Thank you.
I'm really gonna miss you!
What?
I don't know why I said that.
I'm obviously still hormonal.
Okay.
It's okay, Kim.
Just... just go home and...
and enjoy that baby.
You'll hold down the fort?
Oh, believe me, all the chaos
will still be here when you get back.
Thanks, Jane.
- Bye.
- Hey.
Um, I just heard from Stacy.
I assume you did your part?
- You assume correctly.
- Okay.
Uh, she's got to stay in there
for like another half-hour or so.
How did San Diego go?
Did you save the groom?
I did, yes.
Actually, Emma should be walking
down the aisle right about now.
- Good work.
- Thanks.
Well, I'll see you later.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Uh, Mr. French.
If you don't mind, I'd like
a word with you and Ms. Kaswell.
Uh, of course.
Thank you, Mr. Tuttle,
but why are you here?
Well, I hadn't planned to
tell you this in the hospital,
but it can't wait.
What can't wait?
My purpose in evaluating the firm
wasn't for malpractice insurance.
It was to appraise it... for a sale.
What?
Wait, hold on. Parker wants a buyout?
He's making a new life for himself,
and he wants an accurate
evaluation of the firm.
It's all here
in the notice of dissolution.
Harrison & Parker will be sold
to the highest bidder.
Congratulations on the baby.
- Uh...
- Hmm!
I hate that you look good
from every angle.
I need to keep my legs up
for another 20 minutes.
I can't believe I could actually
be getting pregnant right now.
I'm thinking positive thoughts for you.
Thank you.
And I'm doing the same for you.
Why me?
Well, for you and Grayson.
I mean, Jane, he's crazy about you.
And as far as I'm concerned,
any day you're not with him
is a wasted day.
I mean, take it from someone
who loves and respects you.
You need to go to him
and tell him how you feel.
But...
Mnh-mnh. Stop with the excuses.
The man told you he loves you,
and the only reason
you didn't say it back
is because you were consumed with guilt.
Jane, do you know where he is right now?
Yes, he went to the nursery
to see Kim's baby.
So you need to go to him.
Life is too short.
Don't waste another minute.
You of all people should know this.
Okay.
I'm really gonna do this, you know.
Thank you.
Hello, there.
Hey.
Oh, he is so cute.
Yeah. Look at those tiny hands.
"Every child begins the world again."
Henry David Thoreau.
"Burp 'em once, then burp 'em again."
My grandma Ruth.
What about you, Grayson?
Do you want kids?
Enough for a basketball team.
How about you?
Absolutely...
Oh, yeah?
...as soon as I find the right guy.
Sync and corrections by atrn97g
for www.addic7ed.com