All right, Raj has played
his phantom warlord card,
and I am going to back him up
with my strangling vines.
Choke on that, sucka.
Okay, well, then I'll just cut
your vines with my ruby sword.
That's right, I did it. I cut 'em.
I have a question.
Warlord beats troll, troll beats elf,
elf beats water sprite,
and basically everything
beats enchanted bunny.
Unless you have the carrot opower.
Okay, I've got another question.
When does this get fun?
Are we going to talk or are we going
to play "Mystic Warlords of Ka-ah"?
Just play potion card.
Which one?
It doesn't matter.
You can't possibly win.
- Sheldon, don't ruin the game.
- How could he ruin the game?
Given the cards
that have been played,
Penny can only be holding
necromancer potions,
which are only effective against
wraiths and day- walkers,
and there are no more left.
The cards remaining in
the undrawn stack are:
four fire weapons, a troll,
two ogres and the jewel of osiris.
See? Ruined.
Sheldon, that is incredible.
From your vantage point,
it certainly must seem so.
Sheldon has kind of
a photographic memory.
"Photographic" is a misnomer.
I have an eidetic memory,
as I've told you many times.
Most recently last year during lunch
on the afternoon of may seventh.
You had turkey
and complained it was dry.
Well, I guess game's over.
Really? Oh, great.
I mean, aw.
- Okay, I gotta go.
- Why?
Because the last me I didn't go,
I ended up playing
"Mystic Warlords of Ka."
Not "Ka. Ka-ah. "
Buh-eye.
See ya.
Still can't believe
she's going out with me.
Nobody can.
That reminds me
I have a bone to pick with you.
- What?
- You and I made a pact
that if either of us
ever got a hot girlfriend,
that person would have his girlfriend
hook the other guy up
with one of her girlfriends.
I don't remember that.
June 30th, 2004.
Opening day of Spider-Man 2
at the AMC Pasadena.
They only had red icees, no blue.
So you've been with Penny
for like a month and a half now.
Where's my shorty, morty?
Howard, you can't hold me to that.
- Why not?
- When I made that agreement,
I didn't think I'd ever have one.
And I was positive you never would.
Hey, how come
I wasn't part of this deal?
You had left the refreshment stand
in order to indulge
in your customary
preemptive pre-show urination.
So that's how it works?
I have a teeny bladder
and I don't get a hot girlfriend?
Yeah, Raj.
That's how it works.
Damn.
Episode 305:
The Creepy Candy Coating Corollary
Sync: Golgi, Jess, Linwelin
Can I have a napkin?
I'm sorry, no.
But you have whole bunch of 'em.
Yes, I've moved
to a four-napkin system.
Lap, hands, face
and personal emergency.
If you like, starting tomorrow,
I'll add a guest napkin,
but I'afraid there's nothing
I can do for you today.
Good luck.
That's the face napkin.
So, have you talked to Penny yet?
No, I haven't.
Why not?
Because I've been busy, I haven't
figured out a way to bring it up,
and mostly... and I can't
stress how key this is...
Because I don't want to.
Leonard, a pact is a pact.
You have to get Penny to fix me up.
It's not simple.
What am I supposed to say?
"Penny, do you have any friends
you'd like to never hear from again?"
Come on, I'm smart,
I have good job and I have
only three percent body fat.
It's true. I've seen him at the beach.
He's like a human chicken wing.
Leonard, come on.
Fine. I'll ask
if she has a friend for you.
Hot friend.
- Right.
- And tall.
I want our kids to be able to ride
space mountain before they're 20.
I wanti'll see what I can do.
Sheldon, guess what I heard?
I'd imagine you heard
any number of things today.
When you arrived, you heard
"Hello, Raj. How are you, Raj?"
Since you're wearing a new sweater-vest,
you may have heard "New sweater-vest?"
and possibly, though far less likely,
"Nice sweater-vest. "
Why don't I just tell you
what I heard today.
That would probably
save us some time.
Saturday, at comic book store, there's
a "Mystic Warlords of Ka-ah" tournament.
First prize is $500.
If we team up, we'd be unstoppable.
I'm sorry, Raj,
but I have no interest
in playing a game
in which I find no challenge.
- What about the money?
- I have money.
This is other money.
How does it differ
from the money I have?
Half of it will be mine.
Do you need it to buy
a less disturbing sweater-vest?
- Leonard, help.
- Are you kidding?
I couldn't even talk him into giving me
one of his freakin' napkins.
You really are a genius.
Not really.
I Googled how to do that.
So, listen...
Have you ever made a pact
with someone?
You mean like a pinky swear?
Okay, fine, like a pinky swear.
In the first grade,
my friend Rosie and I
made a pact to marry Bert and Ernie.
- You know, from Sesame Street?
- I'm familiar with Bert and Ernie.
Then we found out
we both wanted Ernie.
We didn't speak against
until middle school.
Over puppets?
The heart wants
what the heart wants, Leonard.
Speaking of what the heart wants...
A long time ago,
I made a pact with Wolowitz
that kind of involves you.
I don't know where
you're going with this,
but tread carefully because it may be
the last conversation we ever have.
Nothing like that.
The deal was that if either
of us ever got a girlfriend,
we'd have her fix the other one
up with one of her friends.
You thought a good time to bring this up
would be right after sex?
I sure as hell
wasn't going to bring it up before sex
And during, I was trying to remember
what I read on Google, so...
I'm not hooking Wolowitz up
with one of my friends.
It doesn't have to be a good friend.
And you know that deep down inside,
Howard's a really nice guy.
The problem isn't
what's on the inside.
It's the creepy candy coating.
Will you at least think about it?
Just as a favor to me?
Great thing about Ernie,
was he never asked me for anything.
He just gave.
Got it. Got it.
Betty and Veronica?
Sheldon, the new Greenlantern
figurine's coming in tomorrow.
- Want me to set one aside for you?
- Thank you.
You just robbed me ofhe opportunity
to stumble upon the figurine
and make the oh-so-satisfying journey
from discovery to desire to possession.
- I won't set one aside for you.
- But I must have it.
- Okay I'll set one aside for you.
- Thank you.
I can buy all these things online.
I come here for the personal service.
Is the Wil Wheaton signed up
for the Mystic Warlords tournament
the Wil Wheaton from Star Trek?
He lives around here. Big gamer.
Excuse me.
Are you saying that Wil Wheaton
AKA ensign Wesley Crusher
on Star Trek: The Next Generation
is going to be participating?
Sorry, did I rob you of the opportunity
to stumble onto that for yourself?
You don't understand.
Growing up,
I idolizedle Wil Wheaton.
Wesley Crusher had an eidetic memory
just like me.
Maybe you can discuss that with him
while you're playing in the tournament.
- Sign here.
- I was such a fan
that in 1995,
I traveled ten hours by bus
to a sci-fi convention
in Jakson, Mississippi,
wearing my Star Flee Academy
cadet uniform
in order to meet Wil Wheaton
and get him to autograph
my mint in-package
Wesley Crusher action figure.
It'll be ke a reunion then.
Sign here.
My arduous journey,
however, was for naught.
Although advertised to appear,
he did not show up.
It was at that moment,
I vowed eternal hatred for Wil Wheaton.
Great, you can tell him you hate him.
Sign here.
It might also interest you to know
that Wil Wheaton
currently ranks sixth
on my all-time enemies list...
Between director Joel Schumacher,
who nearly destroyed
the Batman movie franchise,
And Billy Sparks,
who lived down the street from me
and put dog poop
on the handles of my bicycle.
I get it. He's a bad guy.
Sign here.
In the words of Khan Noonien Singh
in the immortal wrath of Khan,
"He tasks me.
"He tasks me and I shall have him."
No doubt, sign here.
"Rom hell's heart, I stab at thee."
All right, Raj,
looks like you're teamed up with
"Die, Wil Wheaton, die."
So, tell me more
about the future mother of my children.
She's adorable, Howard.
I think you'll like her.
Great.
So what did you tell her about me?
Did you mention the body fat?
I thought that would be
a nice surprise for her.
Good, good.
I told her you're an aerospace engineer,
you speak five languages...
Six if you count Klingon.
Girls don't count Klingon, Howard.
- Right?
- Right.
And I told her you have
an unhealthy attachment to your mother.
- What?
- I'm kidding.
Another delightful surprise for her.
Sheldon, it's your play.
My enchanted troll bludgeons
your screaming harpy with a cursed mace.
Game.
Sorry, boys. Say hi to your mother
when she picks you up.
Or I could just tell her
later tonight!
We pwned them, dude! Up top!
Look at him.
Wil Wheaton, my old friend.
I have chased you
'round the moons of Nibia
and 'round the Antares maelstrom
and 'round perdition's flames!
You keep quoting Wrath of Khan,
but he was in Next Generation.
It's a different set of chacters.
Silence!
How much longer must I wait
for my revenge?
If Wil Wheaton and Stuart
win their match
and we beat lonely Larry and
captain sweatpants in the next round,
we'll face off for the championship.
So, my path
to satisfaction is blocked
by lonely Larry
and captain sweatpants.
Very well.
They must be destroyed.
You have to stop talking like that.
It's really lame.
Silence!
So, Penny tells me
you're working as a waitress
to put yourself through grad school.
That's pretty great.
What are you sdying?
Microbiology.
Oh, cool.
So you could study me.
I don't understand.
Microbiology is the study
of tiny living things.
I know, I'm studying it.
And I said you could study me
'cause I'm a tiny living thing.
- It's a joke.
- Are you sure?
Do you like science fiction?
Role-playing games?
Like in the bedroom
or like Dungeons and Dragons?
Either.
Gonna be a long night.
It's your fault.
I had to ask.
You didn't have to say yes.
- You like magic?
- Not really.
A long, long night.
I play my endless serpent.
Raj will play ecstatic frenzy,
which means Larry
will have to play chaos overlord.
Then captain sweatpants,
molten river.
I play nightshade dryad.
Game, set and match.
Now fetch me Wil Wheaton!
Did that guy just say
"revenge is a dish best served cold"
in Klingon?
I believe so.
What is wrong with him?
Everyone has a different theory.
How about computers?
Do you like computers?
I use them.
I don't like them.
Puppies?
Where do you stand on puppies?
A puppy once bit my face.
Of course it did.
How about that?
Einstein was wrong.
Approaching the speed of light
doesn't slow down time.
Approaching them does.
Excuse me.
Damn, it's my mother.
- Are you going to answer it?
- I'm torn.
She might be dying, and, you know,
I wouldn't want to miss that.
But if I let it go to voicemail,
I could play it over and over.
I know how you feel.
My mother makes me crazy.
Not as crazy as my mother makes me.
Does your mother call
you every day at work
to see if you've had
a healthy lunch?
My mother calls me at work to see
if I had a healthy bowel movement.
Okay, does she lay out
your clothes for you in the morning
like you're nine years old?
You live with your mother?
No. That's the sad part.
Rough. Okay, check this out.
My mother made me wear
rubber gloves to kindergarten
so I wouldn't pick up a disease
from the other children.
That's nothing.
I couldn't ride a bicycle
'cause my mother was afraid
I'd hit a bump and lose my virginity.
You didn't, did you?
Not on a bicycle.
In a Camry.
Corolla!
- More wine?
- I'd love some.
You have to come
to Shabbat dinner
at my house sometime.
Why?
A catholic girl like you
wearing a big cross
might just give my mother
the big brain aneurysm
I've been hoping for.
Okay, but only if you come
to Sunday dinner at my house
wearing a yarmulke.
It's a date.
Am I a matchmaker or what?
Lava serpent.
Nest of snakes.
Underworld guardian.
We skirmish to the death.
Invisibility spell.
Luminescence spell.
- Water nymph.
- Fire demon.
- Two-headed tiger.
- Three-headed lion.
- Sulphur.
- Brimstone.
Problem, Wil Wheaton?
- Hang on.
- You have two moderate spell cards,
a small rock and a potion of Zancor
which will be about as much help
as an air conditioner
on the ice planet Hoth.
Your only move is
to play the potion, lose the skirmish,
and two moves later, the game.
I think he's got me.
The year was 1995.
The place: Jackson, Mississippi.
Having spent ten hours on a bus,
during which I had to twice violate
my personal rule
against relieving myself
on board a moving vehicle...
I finally arrived at the fourth annual
Dixie-Trek convention
only to find that my idol,
Wil Wheaton,
decided he had better things to do
than to show up
and sign my action figure.
What?
You betrayed me, Wil Wheaton.
And now...
I have my revenge.
You went to the '95 Dixie-Trek?
Oh, dude,
my grandmother had just died,
and I had to go to her funeral.
Your mee-maw died?
That's terrible.
Yeah, it was.
But I'm really sorry
that I disappointed you.
No, no, I understand.
If anything happened to my mee-maw,
I'd be one inconsolable moon pie.
I should clarify that statement
by explaining that she calls me
"moon pie."
It's a special relationship, isn't it,
between a boy and his grandmother?
Oh, yes.
Great, everybody
loves their grandmas!
Now, come on, Sheldon,
finish him off!
It's okay, Sheldon.
I let you down.
I deserve it.
Potion of Zancor.
What are you waiting for?!
Kill Wil Wheaton!
From hell's heart, stab at him!
I can't.
Sure you can. Do it! Do it!
I came here to defeat Wil Wheaton,
the man who destroyed my dreams.
But I can't defeat Wil Wheaton,
the man who loved his mee-maw.
Enchanted bunny.
Not enchanted bunny!
I call my mee-maw "nana."
And she's going to be very happy
to hear that my small rock kills
your enchanted bunny.
Game over, moon pie.
I don't understand.
Your grandmother's alive?
You catch on quick.
Come on, Stewie,
let's get our prize money.
That was fun.
Wheaton!